,num,sentence,tag
0,1,This,O
1,1,was,O
2,1,a,O
3,1,great,O
4,1,place,O
5,1,to,O
6,1,stay,O
7,1,The,O
8,1,host,O
9,1,was,O
10,1,friendly,O
11,1,and,O
12,1,welcoming,O
13,1,and,O
14,1,the,O
15,1,room,O
16,1,was,O
17,1,very,O
18,1,comfortable,O
19,1,.,O
20,1,Moreover,O
21,1,the,O
22,1,location,O
23,1,was,O
24,1,perfect,O
25,1,there,O
26,1,was,O
27,1,so,O
28,1,much,O
29,1,to,O
30,1,see,O
31,1,within,O
32,1,walking,O
33,1,distance,O
34,1,in,O
35,1,Chinatown,B-gpe
36,1,",",O
37,1,and,O
38,1,the,O
39,1,apartment,O
40,1,was,O
41,1,also,O
42,1,right,O
43,1,on,O
44,1,top,O
45,1,of,O
46,1,the,O
47,1,Chinatown,B-gpe
48,1,MRT,O
49,1,station,O
50,1,",",O
51,1,giving,O
52,1,easy,O
53,1,access,O
54,1,to,O
55,1,the,O
56,1,whole,O
57,1,city,O
58,1,.,O
59,1,Highly,O
60,1,recommended,O
61,2,Value,O
62,2,for,O
63,2,money,O
64,2,",",O
65,2,walking,O
66,2,distance,O
67,2,to,O
68,2,Chinatown,B-gpe
69,2,MRT,O
70,2,",",O
71,2,hawker,O
72,2,centre,O
73,2,",",O
74,2,7E,O
75,2,.,O
76,2,Great,O
77,2,accommodation,O
78,2,with,O
79,2,aircond,O
80,2,",",O
81,2,wifi,O
82,2,.,O
83,2,Comfortable,O
84,2,stay,O
85,2,and,O
86,2,clean,O
87,2,place,O
88,2,.,O
89,3,I,O
90,3,was,O
91,3,transferred,O
92,3,to,O
93,3,the,O
94,3,Tanjong,B-geo
95,3,Pagar,I-geo
96,3,location,O
97,3,instead,O
98,3,of,O
99,3,Chinatown,B-gpe
100,3,maybe,O
101,3,I,O
102,3,lucked,O
103,3,out,O
104,3,",",O
105,3,it,O
106,3,was,O
107,3,a,O
108,3,perfect,O
109,3,location,O
110,3,.,O
111,3,The,O
112,3,room,O
113,3,was,O
114,3,small,O
115,3,but,O
116,3,very,O
117,3,very,O
118,3,clean,O
119,3,and,O
120,3,comfortable,O
121,3,.,O
122,3,Was,O
123,3,nervous,O
124,3,about,O
125,3,shared,O
126,3,bathroom,O
127,3,but,O
128,3,rarely,O
129,3,did,O
130,3,I,O
131,3,see,O
132,3,anyone,O
133,3,else,O
134,3,in,O
135,3,there,O
136,3,and,O
137,3,it,O
138,3,seemed,O
139,3,the,O
140,3,toilets,O
141,3,and,O
142,3,shower,O
143,3,were,O
144,3,freshly,O
145,3,cleaned,O
146,3,any,O
147,3,time,O
148,3,I,O
149,3,went,O
150,3,in,O
151,3,.,O
152,3,The,O
153,3,showers,O
154,3,have,O
155,3,a,O
156,3,personal,O
157,3,little,O
158,3,changing,O
159,3,area,O
160,3,too,O
161,3,",",O
162,3,very,O
163,3,hot,O
164,3,water,O
165,3,and,O
166,3,nice,O
167,3,waterfall,O
168,3,shower,O
169,3,head,O
170,3,.,O
171,3,Great,O
172,3,price,O
173,3,for,O
174,3,Singapore,B-geo
175,3,",",O
176,3,would,O
177,3,stay,O
178,3,here,O
179,3,again,O
180,3,.,O
181,3,Also,O
182,3,enjoyed,O
183,3,the,O
184,3,free,O
185,3,coffee,O
186,3,and,O
187,3,filtered,O
188,3,water,O
189,4,Great,O
190,4,staff,O
191,4,and,O
192,4,nice,O
193,4,place,O
194,4,.,O
195,4,The,O
196,4,photos,O
197,4,equal,O
198,4,100,O
199,4,the,O
200,4,real,O
201,4,room,O
202,4,.,O
203,4,The,O
204,4,Hotel,O
205,4,is,O
206,4,located,O
207,4,in,O
208,4,Chinatown,B-gpe
209,4,very,O
210,4,easy,O
211,4,to,O
212,4,get,O
213,4,around,O
214,4,",",O
215,4,also,O
216,4,the,O
217,4,check,O
218,4,in,O
219,4,and,O
220,4,check,O
221,4,out,O
222,4,was,O
223,4,great,O
224,4,and,O
225,4,easy,O
226,4,.,O
227,4,Almost,O
228,4,everything,O
229,4,was,O
230,4,super,O
231,4,clean,O
232,4,.,O
233,4,You,O
234,4,will,O
235,4,enjoy,O
236,4,the,O
237,4,stay,O
238,4,at,O
239,4,Fangs,B-org
240,4,Hotel,I-org
241,5,I,O
242,5,had,O
243,5,a,O
244,5,nice,O
245,5,stay,O
246,5,at,O
247,5,Atlantis,B-org
248,5,Pods,I-org
249,5,Chinatown,I-org
250,5,.,O
251,5,Pretty,O
252,5,much,O
253,5,what,O
254,5,I,O
255,5,d,O
256,5,expected,O
257,5,from,O
258,5,a,O
259,5,hostel,O
260,5,capsule,O
261,5,pods,O
262,5,.,O
263,5,The,O
264,5,place,O
265,5,is,O
266,5,in,O
267,5,the,O
268,5,heart,O
269,5,of,O
270,5,chinatown,B-gpe
271,5,",",O
272,5,very,O
273,5,near,O
274,5,Chinatown,B-gpe
275,5,MRT,O
276,5,station,O
277,5,A,O
278,5,gate,O
279,5,.,O
280,5,Swiftly,O
281,5,checked,O
282,5,in,O
283,5,",",O
284,5,the,O
285,5,capsule,O
286,5,room,O
287,5,itself,O
288,5,is,O
289,5,not,O
290,5,too,O
291,5,claustrophobic,O
292,5,",",O
293,5,and,O
294,5,not,O
295,5,hot,O
296,5,.,O
297,5,They,O
298,5,provided,O
299,5,toast,O
300,5,",",O
301,5,and,O
302,5,cereal,O
303,5,breakfast,O
304,5,.,O
305,5,Budget,O
306,5,friendly,O
307,5,I,O
308,5,will,O
309,5,be,O
310,5,back,O
311,5,for,O
312,5,sure,O
313,5,.,O
314,5,Wish,O
315,5,for,O
316,5,a,O
317,5,better,O
318,5,pillow,O
319,5,",",O
320,5,and,O
321,5,cleaner,O
322,5,bedding,O
323,5,next,O
324,5,time,O
325,5,.,O
326,6,1,O
327,6,.,O
328,6,Nearby,O
329,6,to,O
330,6,Little,B-gpe
331,6,India,I-gpe
331,6,",",O
332,6,Jalan,B-geo
333,6,Besar,I-geo
334,6,MRT,O
335,6,station,O
336,6,.,O
337,6,2,O
338,6,.,O
339,6,Suitable,O
340,6,for,O
341,6,short,O
342,6,stay,O
343,6,3,O
344,6,.,O
345,6,Bunk,O
346,6,bed,O
347,6,was,O
348,6,comfy,O
349,6,but,O
350,6,the,O
351,6,room,O
352,6,was,O
353,6,a,O
354,6,bit,O
355,6,small,O
356,6,.,O
357,6,Rather,O
358,6,difficult,O
359,6,to,O
360,6,get,O
361,6,up,O
362,6,.,O
363,6,4,O
364,6,.,O
365,6,Bathroom,O
366,6,also,O
367,6,a,O
368,6,bit,O
369,6,small,O
370,6,rather,O
371,6,basic,O
372,6,toiletries,O
373,7,We,O
374,7,had,O
375,7,a,O
376,7,really,O
377,7,nice,O
378,7,stay,O
379,7,here,O
380,7,.,O
381,7,The,O
382,7,location,O
383,7,is,O
384,7,super,O
385,7,convenient,O
386,7,to,O
387,7,get,O
388,7,to,O
389,7,",",O
390,7,close,O
391,7,to,O
392,7,three,O
393,7,different,O
394,7,subway,O
395,7,stations,O
396,7,subway,O
397,7,lines,O
398,7,",",O
399,7,and,O
400,7,really,O
401,7,close,O
402,7,to,O
403,7,Clarke,B-geo
404,7,Quay,I-geo
405,7,and,O
406,7,City,B-geo
407,7,Hall,I-geo
408,7,Chijmes,B-org
409,7,area,O
410,7,",",O
411,7,but,O
412,7,also,O
413,7,very,O
414,7,quiet,O
415,7,and,O
416,7,pleasant,O
417,7,with,O
418,7,the,O
419,7,garden,O
420,7,in,O
421,7,the,O
422,7,complex,O
423,7,.,O
424,7,The,O
425,7,host,O
426,7,is,O
427,7,very,O
428,7,nice,O
429,7,",",O
430,7,gave,O
431,7,us,O
432,7,a,O
433,7,lot,O
434,7,of,O
435,7,good,O
436,7,advice,O
437,7,and,O
438,7,was,O
439,7,very,O
440,7,quick,O
441,7,to,O
442,7,respond,O
443,7,to,O
444,7,our,O
445,7,requests,O
446,7,.,O
447,8,This,O
448,8,room,O
449,8,is,O
450,8,very,O
451,8,good,O
452,8,",",O
453,8,close,O
454,8,to,O
455,8,MRT,O
456,8,Bras,B-geo
457,8,Basah,I-geo
458,8,",",O
459,8,Bencoolen,B-geo
460,8,",",O
461,8,Bugis,B-geo
462,8,",",O
463,8,eats,O
464,8,Food,O
465,8,Center,O
466,8,downstairs,O
467,8,or,O
468,8,near,O
469,8,Yakun,B-org
470,8,",",O
471,8,Toast,B-org
472,8,Box,I-org
473,8,or,O
474,8,Bugis,B-geo
475,8,Street,I-geo
476,8,to,O
477,8,eat,O
478,8,",",O
479,8,do,O
480,8,not,O
481,8,take,O
482,8,a,O
483,8,few,O
484,8,minutes,O
485,8,Buying,O
486,8,daily,O
487,8,necessities,O
488,8,or,O
489,8,fresh,O
490,8,fruits,O
491,8,and,O
492,8,vegetables,O
493,8,can,O
494,8,go,O
495,8,to,O
496,8,Cold,B-org
497,8,Storage,I-org
498,8,or,O
499,8,Fair,B-org
500,8,Price,I-org
501,8,Express,I-org
502,8,is,O
503,8,nearby,O
504,8,And,O
505,8,in,O
506,8,the,O
507,8,school,O
508,8,district,O
509,8,",",O
510,8,the,O
511,8,security,O
512,8,is,O
513,8,relatively,O
514,8,better,O
515,8,",",O
516,8,and,O
517,8,I,O
518,8,do,O
519,8,not,O
520,8,have,O
521,8,to,O
522,8,be,O
523,8,too,O
524,8,afraid,O
525,8,.,O
526,8,However,O
527,8,",",O
528,8,small,O
529,8,disadvantages,O
530,8,are,O
531,8,that,O
532,8,small,O
533,8,a,O
534,8,room,O
535,8,sometimes,O
536,8,lives,O
537,8,more,O
538,8,than,O
539,8,a,O
540,8,dozen,O
541,8,people,O
542,8,.,O
543,8,The,O
544,8,bathroom,O
545,8,is,O
546,8,sometimes,O
547,8,waiting,O
548,8,for,O
549,8,a,O
550,8,while,O
551,8,",",O
552,8,otherwise,O
553,8,sometimes,O
554,8,there,O
555,8,are,O
556,8,people,O
557,8,who,O
558,8,speak,O
559,8,in,O
560,8,the,O
561,8,kitchen,O
562,8,in,O
563,8,the,O
564,8,middle,O
565,8,of,O
566,8,the,O
567,8,night,O
568,8,.,O
569,8,The,O
570,8,sound,O
571,8,insulation,O
572,8,is,O
573,8,not,O
574,8,very,O
575,8,good,O
576,8,.,O
577,8,In,O
578,8,addition,O
579,8,",",O
580,8,there,O
581,8,is,O
582,8,no,O
583,8,big,O
584,8,problem,O
585,8,.,O
586,8,In,O
587,8,short,O
588,8,",",O
589,8,this,O
590,8,house,O
591,8,is,O
592,8,good,O
593,8,",",O
594,8,excellent,O
595,8,geographical,O
596,8,location,O
597,8,",",O
598,8,kitchen,O
599,8,can,O
600,8,be,O
601,8,used,O
602,8,free,O
603,9,Best,O
604,9,place,O
605,9,for,O
606,9,family,O
607,9,holidays,O
608,9,in,O
609,9,Singapore,B-geo
610,9,.,O
611,9,Located,O
612,9,very,O
613,9,close,O
614,9,to,O
615,9,Downtown,B-geo
616,9,MRT,O
617,9,",",O
618,9,so,O
619,9,we,O
620,9,could,O
621,9,reach,O
622,9,Little,B-gpe
623,9,India,I-gpe
624,9,in,O
625,9,10,O
626,9,minutes,O
627,9,",",O
628,9,Chinatown,B-gpe
629,9,in,O
630,9,20,O
631,9,min,O
632,9,",",O
633,9,Bugis,B-geo
634,9,and,O
635,9,Bayfront,B-geo
636,9,in,O
637,9,15,O
638,9,minutes,O
639,9,.,O
640,9,We,O
641,9,could,O
642,9,cover,O
643,9,more,O
644,9,because,O
645,9,of,O
646,9,the,O
647,9,location,O
648,9,.,O
649,10,We,O
650,10,had,O
651,10,a,O
652,10,pleasant,O
653,10,stay,O
654,10,in,O
655,10,the,O
656,10,apartment,O
657,10,.,O
658,10,The,O
659,10,host,O
660,10,is,O
661,10,very,O
662,10,nice,O
663,10,.,O
664,10,The,O
665,10,apartment,O
666,10,was,O
667,10,very,O
668,10,clean,O
669,10,and,O
670,10,neat,O
671,10,.,O
672,10,There,O
673,10,are,O
674,10,some,O
675,10,local,O
676,10,food,O
677,10,stalls,O
678,10,and,O
679,10,buses,O
680,10,to,O
681,10,Chinatown,B-gpe
682,10,or,O
683,10,other,O
684,10,places,O
685,10,near,O
686,10,the,O
687,10,apartment,O
688,10,.,O
689,10,Taking,O
690,10,buses,O
691,10,is,O
692,10,more,O
693,10,convenient,O
694,10,than,O
695,10,taking,O
696,10,MRT,O
697,10,as,O
698,10,the,O
699,10,apartment,O
700,10,is,O
701,10,a,O
702,10,bit,O
703,10,far,O
704,10,from,O
705,10,the,O
706,10,nearby,O
707,10,MRT,O
708,10,station,O
709,10,on,O
710,10,foot,O
711,10,.,O
712,10,Also,O
713,10,",",O
714,10,the,O
715,10,wifi,O
716,10,is,O
717,10,a,O
718,10,bit,O
719,10,weak,O
720,10,.,O
721,10,Except,O
722,10,these,O
723,10,",",O
724,10,others,O
725,10,are,O
726,10,good,O
727,11,The,O
728,11,hotel,O
729,11,is,O
730,11,in,O
731,11,a,O
732,11,perfect,O
733,11,location,O
734,11,",",O
735,11,Chinatown,B-gpe
736,11,",",O
737,11,Clarke,B-geo
738,11,Qual,I-geo
739,11,",",O
740,11,Marina,B-geo
741,11,Bay,I-geo
742,11,",",O
743,11,Merlion,B-gpe
744,11,are,O
745,11,all,O
746,11,within,O
747,11,a,O
748,11,20,O
749,11,minute,O
750,11,walk,O
751,11,.,O
752,11,The,O
753,11,area,O
754,11,is,O
755,11,safe,O
756,11,and,O
757,11,easy,O
758,11,to,O
759,11,get,O
760,11,in,O
761,11,and,O
762,11,out,O
763,11,of,O
764,11,the,O
765,11,hotel,O
766,11,.,O
767,11,The,O
768,11,room,O
769,11,I,O
770,11,had,O
771,11,didn,O
772,11,t,O
773,11,have,O
774,11,a,O
775,11,good,O
776,11,view,O
777,11,",",O
778,11,I,O
779,11,would,O
780,11,recommend,O
781,11,to,O
782,11,stay,O
783,11,here,O
784,11,only,O
785,11,to,O
786,11,sleep,O
787,11,",",O
788,11,rest,O
789,11,and,O
790,11,shower,O
791,11,.,O
792,11,The,O
793,11,rooms,O
794,11,are,O
795,11,pretty,O
796,11,small,O
797,11,and,O
798,11,only,O
799,11,two,O
800,11,fit,O
801,11,comfortably,O
802,11,.,O
803,11,The,O
804,11,staff,O
805,11,is,O
806,11,very,O
807,11,nice,O
808,11,and,O
809,11,helpful,O
810,12,Everything,O
811,12,is,O
812,12,as,O
813,12,expected,O
814,12,",",O
815,12,as,O
816,12,described,O
817,12,.,O
818,12,The,O
819,12,place,O
820,12,is,O
821,12,not,O
822,12,so,O
823,12,far,O
824,12,from,O
825,12,Holland,B-geo
826,12,Village,I-geo
827,12,MRT,O
828,12,and,O
829,12,just,O
830,12,a,O
831,12,few,O
832,12,minutes,O
833,12,of,O
834,12,walking,O
835,12,away,O
836,12,from,O
837,12,a,O
838,12,supermarket,O
839,12,.,O
840,12,The,O
841,12,responses,O
842,12,from,O
843,12,the,O
844,12,host,O
845,12,were,O
846,12,very,O
847,12,fast,O
848,12,and,O
849,12,detail,O
850,12,.,O
851,13,I,O
852,13,would,O
853,13,like,O
854,13,to,O
855,13,recommend,O
856,13,everyone,O
857,13,to,O
858,13,stay,O
859,13,in,O
860,13,Wu,O
861,13,Daxia,O
862,13,is,O
863,13,house,O
864,13,and,O
865,13,thank,O
866,13,you,O
867,13,Thank,O
868,13,you,O
869,13,for,O
870,13,your,O
871,13,convenience,O
872,13,of,O
873,13,traveling,O
874,13,us,O
875,13,.,O
876,13,Although,O
877,13,the,O
878,13,location,O
879,13,of,O
880,13,the,O
881,13,house,O
882,13,is,O
883,13,not,O
884,13,close,O
885,13,to,O
886,13,the,O
887,13,subway,O
888,13,",",O
889,13,the,O
890,13,bus,O
891,13,around,O
892,13,the,O
893,13,truth,O
894,13,is,O
895,13,convenient,O
896,13,",",O
897,13,basically,O
898,13,can,O
899,13,be,O
900,13,covered,O
901,13,to,O
902,13,all,O
903,13,",",O
904,13,and,O
905,13,we,O
906,13,will,O
907,13,basically,O
908,13,rely,O
909,13,on,O
910,13,the,O
911,13,bus,O
912,13,.,O
913,13,Also,O
914,13,thank,O
915,13,the,O
916,13,Heroes,O
917,13,to,O
918,13,provide,O
919,13,the,O
920,13,traffic,O
921,13,card,O
922,13,",",O
923,13,just,O
924,13,make,O
925,13,the,O
926,13,balance,O
927,13,of,O
928,13,the,O
929,13,balance,O
930,13,as,O
931,13,long,O
932,13,as,O
933,13,it,O
934,13,go,O
935,13,back,O
936,13,.,O
937,13,The,O
938,13,first,O
939,13,two,O
940,13,days,O
941,13,of,O
942,13,travel,O
943,13,selection,O
944,13,to,O
945,13,Sentosa,B-geo
946,13,",",O
947,13,downstairs,O
948,13,bus,O
949,13,direct,O
950,13,Vivocity,B-org
951,13,and,O
952,13,walk,O
953,13,the,O
954,13,cross,O
955,13,sea,O
956,13,trail,O
957,13,can,O
958,13,enter,O
959,13,the,O
960,13,island,O
961,13,.,O
962,13,After,O
963,13,three,O
964,13,days,O
965,13,",",O
966,13,we,O
967,13,went,O
968,13,to,O
969,13,the,O
970,13,bull,O
971,13,is,O
972,13,water,O
973,13,small,B-gpe
974,13,India,I-gpe
975,13,Arab,B-geo
976,13,Street,I-geo
977,13,and,O
978,13,other,O
979,13,places,O
980,13,Finally,O
981,13,",",O
982,13,I,O
983,13,also,O
984,13,prepared,O
985,13,a,O
986,13,big,O
987,13,breakfast,O
988,13,for,O
989,13,us,O
990,13,on,O
991,13,that,O
992,13,day,O
993,13,Thank,O
994,13,you,O
995,13,for,O
996,13,your,O
997,13,help,O
998,13,",",O
999,13,you,O
1000,13,also,O
1001,13,welcome,O
1002,13,your,O
1003,13,own,O
1004,13,opportunity,O
1005,13,to,O
1006,13,come,O
1007,13,to,O
1008,13,Beijing,B-geo
1009,13,.,O
1010,14,Overall,O
1011,14,",",O
1012,14,David,B-per
1013,14,s,O
1014,14,place,O
1015,14,is,O
1016,14,great,O
1017,14,My,O
1018,14,family,O
1019,14,and,O
1020,14,I,O
1021,14,had,O
1022,14,a,O
1023,14,superb,O
1024,14,time,O
1025,14,.,O
1026,14,Instructions,O
1027,14,and,O
1028,14,descriptions,O
1029,14,of,O
1030,14,room,O
1031,14,were,O
1032,14,very,O
1033,14,accurate,O
1034,14,.,O
1035,14,It,O
1036,14,is,O
1037,14,very,O
1038,14,convenient,O
1039,14,and,O
1040,14,near,O
1041,14,Chinatown,B-gpe
1042,14,MRT,O
1043,14,.,O
1044,14,This,O
1045,14,home,O
1046,14,is,O
1047,14,highly,O
1048,14,recommended,O
1049,14,.,O
1050,15,Kel,B-per
1051,15,was,O
1052,15,most,O
1053,15,accommodating,O
1054,15,and,O
1055,15,flexible,O
1056,15,with,O
1057,15,our,O
1058,15,request,O
1059,15,for,O
1060,15,early,O
1061,15,checkin,O
1062,15,and,O
1063,15,late,O
1064,15,checkout,O
1065,15,for,O
1066,15,a,O
1067,15,nominal,O
1068,15,fee,O
1069,15,.,O
1070,15,He,O
1071,15,was,O
1072,15,punctual,O
1073,15,with,O
1074,15,the,O
1075,15,keys,O
1076,15,and,O
1077,15,instructions,O
1078,15,for,O
1079,15,the,O
1080,15,facilities,O
1081,15,.,O
1082,15,The,O
1083,15,apartment,O
1084,15,has,O
1085,15,a,O
1086,15,great,O
1087,15,layout,O
1088,15,with,O
1089,15,adequate,O
1090,15,facilities,O
1091,15,.,O
1092,15,The,O
1093,15,location,O
1094,15,is,O
1095,15,central,O
1096,15,with,O
1097,15,great,O
1098,15,restaurants,O
1099,15,",",O
1100,15,shopping,O
1101,15,mall,O
1102,15,",",O
1103,15,local,O
1104,15,food,O
1105,15,stalls,O
1106,15,and,O
1107,15,public,O
1108,15,buses,O
1109,15,to,O
1110,15,Orchard,B-geo
1111,15,Road,I-geo
1112,15,and,O
1113,15,the,O
1114,15,CBD,O
1115,15,.,O
1116,15,A,O
1117,15,must,O
1118,15,try,O
1119,15,is,O
1120,15,Bistro,B-org
1121,15,du,I-org
1122,15,Vin,I-org
1123,15,.,O
1124,16,The,O
1125,16,best,O
1126,16,choice,O
1127,16,for,O
1128,16,tourists,O
1129,16,Especially,O
1130,16,for,O
1131,16,people,O
1132,16,who,O
1133,16,want,O
1134,16,to,O
1135,16,look,O
1136,16,around,O
1137,16,the,O
1138,16,city,O
1139,16,on,O
1140,16,foot,O
1141,16,.,O
1142,16,Since,O
1143,16,it,O
1144,16,s,O
1145,16,located,O
1146,16,in,O
1147,16,the,O
1148,16,very,O
1149,16,center,O
1150,16,of,O
1151,16,the,O
1152,16,city,O
1153,16,just,O
1154,16,5,O
1155,16,10mins,O
1156,16,walk,O
1157,16,from,O
1158,16,MRT,O
1159,16,Bugis,B-geo
1160,16,station,O
1161,16,",",O
1162,16,I,O
1163,16,could,O
1164,16,get,O
1165,16,to,O
1166,16,almost,O
1167,16,all,O
1168,16,the,O
1169,16,scenic,O
1170,16,places,O
1171,16,within,O
1172,16,30mins,O
1173,16,on,O
1174,16,foot,O
1175,16,.,O
1176,16,Of,O
1177,16,course,O
1178,16,you,O
1179,16,can,O
1180,16,get,O
1181,16,there,O
1182,16,much,O
1183,16,faster,O
1184,16,by,O
1185,16,MRT,O
1186,16,",",O
1187,16,though,O
1188,16,.,O
1189,16,The,O
1190,16,room,O
1191,16,was,O
1192,16,spacious,O
1193,16,",",O
1194,16,neat,O
1195,16,and,O
1196,16,clean,O
1197,16,.,O
1198,16,Basic,O
1199,16,kitchen,O
1200,16,and,O
1201,16,laundry,O
1202,16,facility,O
1203,16,are,O
1204,16,available,O
1205,16,.,O
1206,16,And,O
1207,16,importantly,O
1208,16,",",O
1209,16,the,O
1210,16,hosts,O
1211,16,were,O
1212,16,so,O
1213,16,kind,O
1214,16,and,O
1215,16,helpful,O
1216,16,.,O
1217,16,They,O
1218,16,re,O
1219,16,managing,O
1220,16,pretty,O
1221,16,well,O
1222,16,",",O
1223,16,I,O
1224,16,think,O
1225,16,.,O
1226,16,Thank,O
1227,16,you,O
1228,16,Hope,O
1229,16,to,O
1230,16,see,O
1231,16,you,O
1232,16,again,O
1233,16,",",O
1234,16,guys,O
1235,17,Great,O
1236,17,location,O
1237,17,",",O
1238,17,close,O
1239,17,to,O
1240,17,Little,B-gpe
1241,17,India,I-gpe
1242,17,and,O
1243,17,Chinatown,B-gpe
1244,17,.,O
1245,17,Cheap,O
1246,17,rides,O
1247,17,to,O
1248,17,Marina,B-geo
1249,17,Bay,I-geo
1250,17,or,O
1251,17,botanic,B-org
1252,17,gardens,I-org
1253,17,.,O
1254,17,Clean,O
1255,17,room,O
1256,17,",",O
1257,17,equipped,O
1258,17,with,O
1259,17,everything,O
1260,17,needed,O
1261,17,.,O
1262,17,Will,O
1263,17,definitely,O
1264,17,recommend,O
1265,17,it,O
1266,18,Great,O
1267,18,host,O
1268,18,",",O
1269,18,as,O
1270,18,beautiful,O
1271,18,as,O
1272,18,in,O
1273,18,the,O
1274,18,photos,O
1275,18,",",O
1276,18,near,O
1277,18,MRT,O
1278,18,station,O
1279,18,Farrer,B-geo
1280,18,Park,I-geo
1281,18,but,O
1282,18,few,O
1283,18,choices,O
1284,18,of,O
1285,18,restaurant,O
1286,18,.,O
1287,18,Great,O
1288,18,stay,O
1289,18,in,O
1290,18,Singapore,B-geo
1291,18,.,O
1292,18,.,O
1293,19,Great,O
1294,19,place,O
1295,19,to,O
1296,19,stay,O
1297,19,near,O
1298,19,Little,B-gpe
1299,19,India,I-gpe
1300,19,.,O
1301,19,Amazing,O
1302,19,and,O
1303,19,cheap,O
1304,19,restaurants,O
1305,19,all,O
1306,19,around,O
1307,19,.,O
1308,19,Studio,O
1309,19,is,O
1310,19,nice,O
1311,19,",",O
1312,19,although,O
1313,19,small,O
1314,19,which,O
1315,19,is,O
1316,19,normal,O
1317,19,for,O
1318,19,Singapore,B-geo
1319,19,I,O
1320,19,guess,O
1321,19,.,O
1322,19,Well,O
1323,19,insulated,O
1324,19,from,O
1325,19,the,O
1326,19,street,O
1327,19,.,O
1328,19,Just,O
1329,19,next,O
1330,19,to,O
1331,19,a,O
1332,19,metro,O
1333,19,station,O
1334,19,.,O
1335,19,There,O
1336,19,is,O
1337,19,washing,O
1338,19,machine,O
1339,19,",",O
1340,19,dryer,O
1341,19,and,O
1342,19,iron,O
1343,19,",",O
1344,19,which,O
1345,19,is,O
1346,19,very,O
1347,19,convenient,O
1348,19,.,O
1349,19,I,O
1350,19,did,O
1351,19,not,O
1352,19,use,O
1353,19,the,O
1354,19,common,O
1355,19,space,O
1356,19,kitchen,O
1357,19,it,O
1358,19,is,O
1359,19,outdoors,O
1360,19,and,O
1361,19,it,O
1362,19,was,O
1363,19,too,O
1364,19,hot,O
1365,19,but,O
1366,19,it,O
1367,19,is,O
1368,19,a,O
1369,19,nice,O
1370,19,touch,O
1371,19,.,O
1372,20,Great,O
1373,20,location,O
1374,20,Just,O
1375,20,around,O
1376,20,150m,O
1377,20,",",O
1378,20,3,O
1379,20,mins,O
1380,20,walk,O
1381,20,from,O
1382,20,Kallang,B-geo
1383,20,Station,O
1384,20,",",O
1385,20,8,O
1386,20,9,O
1387,20,stations,O
1388,20,away,O
1389,20,from,O
1390,20,Changi,B-org
1391,20,Airport,I-org
1392,20,.,O
1393,20,The,O
1394,20,hostel,O
1395,20,is,O
1396,20,clean,O
1397,20,and,O
1398,20,tidy,O
1399,20,Will,O
1400,20,definitely,O
1401,20,stay,O
1402,20,here,O
1403,20,again,O
1404,20,on,O
1405,20,my,O
1406,20,next,O
1407,20,visit,O
1408,20,to,O
1409,20,Singapore,B-geo
1410,20,.,O
1411,21,Interesting,O
1412,21,concept,O
1413,21,of,O
1414,21,living,O
1415,21,room,O
1416,21,and,O
1417,21,bedroom,O
1418,21,here,O
1419,21,.,O
1420,21,Clean,O
1421,21,room,O
1422,21,and,O
1423,21,good,O
1424,21,aircon,O
1425,21,.,O
1426,21,On,O
1427,21,the,O
1428,21,highest,O
1429,21,floor,O
1430,21,of,O
1431,21,Chinatown,B-gpe
1432,21,apartment,O
1433,21,here,O
1434,21,right,O
1435,21,above,O
1436,21,Chinatown,B-gpe
1437,21,MRT,O
1438,21,means,O
1439,21,great,O
1440,21,convenience,O
1441,21,and,O
1442,21,well,O
1443,21,connected,O
1444,21,to,O
1445,21,any,O
1446,21,part,O
1447,21,of,O
1448,21,Singapore,B-geo
1449,21,.,O
1450,21,Security,O
1451,21,on,O
1452,21,the,O
1453,21,ground,O
1454,21,floor,O
1455,21,offers,O
1456,21,some,O
1457,21,friendly,O
1458,21,security,O
1459,21,.,O
1460,21,Plenty,O
1461,21,of,O
1462,21,budget,O
1463,21,friendly,O
1464,21,food,O
1465,21,24hrs,O
1466,21,nearby,O
1467,21,here,O
1468,21,works,O
1469,21,for,O
1470,21,us,O
1471,21,or,O
1472,21,anyone,O
1473,21,.,O
1474,21,check,O
1475,21,in,O
1476,21,was,O
1477,21,self,O
1478,21,DIY,O
1479,21,and,O
1480,21,works,O
1481,21,well,O
1482,21,.,O
1483,21,communications,O
1484,21,mainly,O
1485,21,via,O
1486,21,messaging,O
1487,21,to,O
1488,21,host,O
1489,21,and,O
1490,21,works,O
1491,21,pretty,O
1492,21,well,O
1493,22,Best,O
1494,22,place,O
1495,22,about,O
1496,22,this,O
1497,22,location,O
1498,22,was,O
1499,22,the,O
1500,22,local,O
1501,22,food,O
1502,22,centre,O
1503,22,about,O
1504,22,a,O
1505,22,5min,O
1506,22,walk,O
1507,22,away,O
1508,22,Great,O
1509,22,local,O
1510,22,food,O
1511,22,and,O
1512,22,did,O
1513,22,not,O
1514,22,see,O
1515,22,a,O
1516,22,single,O
1517,22,other,O
1518,22,tourist,O
1519,22,at,O
1520,22,East,B-geo
1521,22,Coast,I-geo
1522,22,Park,I-geo
1523,22,.,O
1524,22,The,O
1525,22,MRT,O
1526,22,station,O
1527,22,was,O
1528,22,about,O
1529,22,a,O
1530,22,15,O
1531,22,20min,O
1532,22,walk,O
1533,22,away,O
1534,22,.,O
1535,22,.,O
1536,22,.good,O
1537,22,line,O
1538,22,to,O
1539,22,be,O
1540,22,on,O
1541,22,since,O
1542,22,the,O
1543,22,North,O
1544,22,East,O
1545,22,line,O
1546,22,leads,O
1547,22,to,O
1548,22,Clarke,B-geo
1549,22,Quay,I-geo
1550,22,",",O
1551,22,Chinatown,B-gpe
1552,22,",",O
1553,22,and,O
1554,22,Little,B-gpe
1555,22,India,I-gpe
1556,22,",",O
1557,22,but,O
1558,22,not,O
1559,22,the,O
1560,22,closest,O
1561,22,location,O
1562,22,to,O
1563,22,the,O
1564,22,MRT,O
1565,23,Great,O
1566,23,location,O
1567,23,",",O
1568,23,walking,O
1569,23,distance,O
1570,23,from,O
1571,23,Chinatown,B-gpe
1572,23,and,O
1573,23,other,O
1574,23,hot,O
1575,23,spots,O
1576,23,in,O
1577,23,Singapore,B-geo
1578,23,The,O
1579,23,rooms,O
1580,23,are,O
1581,23,lovely,O
1582,23,",",O
1583,23,clean,O
1584,23,",",O
1585,23,and,O
1586,23,nicely,O
1587,23,designed,O
1588,23,Would,O
1589,23,recommend,O
1590,24,Jiayi,B-per
1591,24,is,O
1592,24,space,O
1593,24,was,O
1594,24,a,O
1595,24,great,O
1596,24,home,O
1597,24,away,O
1598,24,from,O
1599,24,home,O
1600,24,for,O
1601,24,our,O
1602,24,trip,O
1603,24,.,O
1604,24,I,O
1605,24,enjoyed,O
1606,24,the,O
1607,24,shared,O
1608,24,pool,O
1609,24,and,O
1610,24,the,O
1611,24,outdoor,O
1612,24,bathroom,O
1613,24,it,O
1614,24,is,O
1615,24,private,O
1616,24,.,O
1617,24,The,O
1618,24,space,O
1619,24,is,O
1620,24,pretty,O
1621,24,close,O
1622,24,to,O
1623,24,Little,B-gpe
1624,24,India,I-gpe
1625,24,MRT,O
1626,24,stop,O
1627,24,as,O
1628,24,well,O
1629,24,.,O
1630,24,Jiayi,B-per
1631,24,was,O
1632,24,super,O
1633,24,quick,O
1634,24,to,O
1635,24,respond,O
1636,24,to,O
1637,24,messages,O
1638,24,and,O
1639,24,made,O
1640,24,the,O
1641,24,process,O
1642,24,very,O
1643,24,easy,O
1644,24,.,O
1645,24,Thank,O
1646,24,you,O
1647,25,The,O
1648,25,place,O
1649,25,is,O
1650,25,very,O
1651,25,clean,O
1652,25,",",O
1653,25,cozy,O
1654,25,and,O
1655,25,the,O
1656,25,staff,O
1657,25,respond,O
1658,25,quickly,O
1659,25,to,O
1660,25,all,O
1661,25,queries,O
1662,25,.,O
1663,25,Great,O
1664,25,location,O
1665,25,",",O
1666,25,easy,O
1667,25,to,O
1668,25,access,O
1669,25,from,O
1670,25,Bugis,B-geo
1671,25,with,O
1672,25,plenty,O
1673,25,of,O
1674,25,food,O
1675,25,places,O
1676,25,around,O
1677,25,.,O
1678,25,It,O
1679,25,would,O
1680,25,be,O
1681,25,great,O
1682,25,if,O
1683,25,the,O
1684,25,TV,O
1685,25,could,O
1686,25,access,O
1687,25,Netflix,B-org
1688,25,as,O
1689,25,currently,O
1690,25,there,O
1691,25,is,O
1692,25,a,O
1693,25,compatibility,O
1694,25,issue,O
1695,25,.,O
1696,25,Apart,O
1697,25,from,O
1698,25,that,O
1699,25,I,O
1700,25,think,O
1701,25,this,O
1702,25,is,O
1703,25,a,O
1704,25,perfect,O
1705,25,spot,O
1706,25,for,O
1707,25,a,O
1708,25,staycation,O
1709,25,.,O
1710,25,Thank,O
1711,25,you,O
1712,25,for,O
1713,25,hosting,O
1714,25,us,O
1715,26,Martin,B-per
1716,26,is,O
1717,26,apt,O
1718,26,worked,O
1719,26,out,O
1720,26,great,O
1721,26,for,O
1722,26,us,O
1723,26,.,O
1724,26,The,O
1725,26,location,O
1726,26,is,O
1727,26,excellent,O
1728,26,",",O
1729,26,only,O
1730,26,a,O
1731,26,block,O
1732,26,off,O
1733,26,the,O
1734,26,river,O
1735,26,at,O
1736,26,Robertson,B-geo
1737,26,Quay,I-geo
1738,26,and,O
1739,26,easy,O
1740,26,access,O
1741,26,to,O
1742,26,MRT,O
1743,26,",",O
1744,26,taxis,O
1745,26,",",O
1746,26,tons,O
1747,26,of,O
1748,26,restaurants,O
1749,26,",",O
1750,26,grocery,O
1751,26,store,O
1752,26,and,O
1753,26,even,O
1754,26,walking,O
1755,26,distance,O
1756,26,to,O
1757,26,Orchard,B-geo
1758,26,Road,I-geo
1759,26,15,O
1760,26,min,O
1761,26,.,O
1762,26,The,O
1763,26,apt,O
1764,26,was,O
1765,26,comfortable,O
1766,26,and,O
1767,26,had,O
1768,26,everything,O
1769,26,we,O
1770,26,needed,O
1771,26,.,O
1772,26,We,O
1773,26,enjoyed,O
1774,26,the,O
1775,26,little,O
1776,26,outside,O
1777,26,patio,O
1778,26,.,O
1779,26,We,O
1780,26,recommended,O
1781,26,staying,O
1782,26,here,O
1783,27,Good,O
1784,27,location,O
1785,27,",",O
1786,27,close,O
1787,27,to,O
1788,27,Orchard,B-geo
1789,27,rd,I-geo
1790,27,and,O
1791,27,Clarke,B-geo
1792,27,Quay,I-geo
1793,27,.,O
1794,27,Nice,O
1795,27,building,O
1796,27,",",O
1797,27,good,O
1798,27,air,O
1799,27,con,O
1800,27,and,O
1801,27,facilities,O
1802,27,e,O
1803,27,.g,O
1804,27,.,O
1805,27,fridge,O
1806,27,",",O
1807,27,microwave,O
1808,27,",",O
1809,27,cutlery,O
1810,27,",",O
1811,27,kettle,O
1812,27,",",O
1813,27,washing,O
1814,27,machine,O
1815,27,.,O
1816,27,Would,O
1817,27,be,O
1818,27,good,O
1819,27,if,O
1820,27,they,O
1821,27,left,O
1822,27,the,O
1823,27,washing,O
1824,27,machine,O
1825,27,dryer,O
1826,27,instructions,O
1827,27,though,O
1828,27,Recommend,O
1829,27,this,O
1830,27,place,O
1831,28,Go,O
1832,28,for,O
1833,28,it,O
1834,28,",",O
1835,28,it,O
1836,28,is,O
1837,28,a,O
1838,28,great,O
1839,28,place,O
1840,28,Perfect,O
1841,28,location,O
1842,28,in,O
1843,28,the,O
1844,28,middle,O
1845,28,of,O
1846,28,Chinatown,B-gpe
1847,28,",",O
1848,28,just,O
1849,28,10,O
1850,28,seconds,O
1851,28,away,O
1852,28,from,O
1853,28,the,O
1854,28,mrt,O
1855,28,",",O
1856,28,you,O
1857,28,can,O
1858,28,also,O
1859,28,walk,O
1860,28,to,O
1861,28,the,O
1862,28,Buddha,B-org
1863,28,Tooth,I-org
1864,28,Relic,I-org
1865,28,Temple,I-org
1866,28,.,O
1867,28,The,O
1868,28,place,O
1869,28,was,O
1870,28,very,O
1871,28,clean,O
1872,28,",",O
1873,28,and,O
1874,28,A,O
1875,28,LOT,O
1876,28,of,O
1877,28,shampoos,O
1878,28,",",O
1879,28,soaps,O
1880,28,",",O
1881,28,etc,O
1882,28,were,O
1883,28,available,O
1884,28,for,O
1885,28,us,O
1886,28,.,O
1887,28,Our,O
1888,28,room,O
1889,28,had,O
1890,28,a,O
1891,28,great,O
1892,28,view,O
1893,28,over,O
1894,28,the,O
1895,28,city,O
1896,28,.,O
1897,28,There,O
1898,28,is,O
1899,28,a,O
1900,28,nice,O
1901,28,atmosphere,O
1902,28,both,O
1903,28,in,O
1904,28,the,O
1905,28,apartment,O
1906,28,and,O
1907,28,in,O
1908,28,the,O
1909,28,neighborhood,O
1910,28,.,O
1911,28,The,O
1912,28,host,O
1913,28,also,O
1914,28,sent,O
1915,28,us,O
1916,28,many,O
1917,28,pictures,O
1918,28,to,O
1919,28,smooth,O
1920,28,our,O
1921,28,arrival,O
1922,28,",",O
1923,28,making,O
1924,28,it,O
1925,28,very,O
1926,28,easy,O
1927,28,to,O
1928,28,find,O
1929,28,and,O
1930,28,stress,O
1931,28,free,O
1932,28,.,O
1933,28,Definitely,O
1934,28,recommend,O
1935,29,Eric,B-per
1936,29,is,O
1937,29,place,O
1938,29,is,O
1939,29,cozy,O
1940,29,",",O
1941,29,very,O
1942,29,comfortable,O
1943,29,and,O
1944,29,and,O
1945,29,has,O
1946,29,cooking,O
1947,29,facilities,O
1948,29,.,O
1949,29,It,O
1950,29,is,O
1951,29,in,O
1952,29,a,O
1953,29,perfect,O
1954,29,location,O
1955,29,near,O
1956,29,Somerset,B-geo
1957,29,MRT,O
1958,29,",",O
1959,29,opposite,O
1960,29,a,O
1961,29,supermarket,O
1962,29,",",O
1963,29,and,O
1964,29,with,O
1965,29,many,O
1966,29,eateries,O
1967,29,locally,O
1968,29,.,O
1969,29,It,O
1970,29,was,O
1971,29,just,O
1972,29,what,O
1973,29,I,O
1974,29,was,O
1975,29,after,O
1976,29,",",O
1977,29,and,O
1978,29,I,O
1979,29,would,O
1980,29,not,O
1981,29,hesitate,O
1982,29,to,O
1983,29,stay,O
1984,29,again,O
1985,29,.,O
1986,30,Great,O
1987,30,location,O
1988,30,in,O
1989,30,Chinatown,B-gpe
1990,30,and,O
1991,30,close,O
1992,30,to,O
1993,30,the,O
1994,30,metro,O
1995,30,.,O
1996,30,Friendly,O
1997,30,staff,O
1998,30,",",O
1999,30,simple,O
2000,30,and,O
2001,30,nice,O
2002,30,accommodation,O
2003,30,.,O
2004,31,Great,O
2005,31,place,O
2006,31,in,O
2007,31,the,O
2008,31,heart,O
2009,31,of,O
2010,31,Clarke,B-geo
2011,31,Quay,I-geo
2012,31,.,O
2013,31,Very,O
2014,31,clean,O
2015,31,",",O
2016,31,everything,O
2017,31,works,O
2018,31,.,O
2019,31,People,O
2020,31,warm,O
2021,31,and,O
2022,31,friendly,O
2023,32,The,O
2024,32,location,O
2025,32,of,O
2026,32,this,O
2027,32,place,O
2028,32,is,O
2029,32,perfect,O
2030,32,directly,O
2031,32,in,O
2032,32,Chinatown,B-gpe
2033,32,with,O
2034,32,the,O
2035,32,metro,O
2036,32,literally,O
2037,32,next,O
2038,32,to,O
2039,32,the,O
2040,32,apartment,O
2041,32,and,O
2042,32,great,O
2043,32,food,O
2044,32,options,O
2045,32,around,O
2046,32,.,O
2047,33,My,O
2048,33,partner,O
2049,33,and,O
2050,33,I,O
2051,33,stayed,O
2052,33,here,O
2053,33,for,O
2054,33,our,O
2055,33,week,O
2056,33,long,O
2057,33,stay,O
2058,33,in,O
2059,33,Singapore,B-geo
2060,33,.,O
2061,33,This,O
2062,33,was,O
2063,33,a,O
2064,33,great,O
2065,33,budget,O
2066,33,accommodation,O
2067,33,option,O
2068,33,",",O
2069,33,very,O
2070,33,centrally,O
2071,33,located,O
2072,33,to,O
2073,33,Chinatown,B-gpe
2074,33,and,O
2075,33,the,O
2076,33,MRT,O
2077,33,station,O
2078,33,.,O
2079,33,The,O
2080,33,space,O
2081,33,was,O
2082,33,quite,O
2083,33,large,O
2084,33,and,O
2085,33,was,O
2086,33,perfect,O
2087,33,for,O
2088,33,us,O
2089,33,to,O
2090,33,wind,O
2091,33,down,O
2092,33,after,O
2093,33,a,O
2094,33,day,O
2095,33,exploring,O
2096,33,.,O
2097,33,Alex,O
2098,33,was,O
2099,33,very,O
2100,33,responsive,O
2101,33,to,O
2102,33,messages,O
2103,33,and,O
2104,33,very,O
2105,33,accommodating,O
2106,33,.,O
2107,33,Overall,O
2108,33,",",O
2109,33,we,O
2110,33,were,O
2111,33,very,O
2112,33,happy,O
2113,33,to,O
2114,33,stay,O
2115,33,here,O
2116,33,and,O
2117,33,would,O
2118,33,so,O
2119,33,again,O
2120,33,.,O
2121,33,I,O
2122,33,would,O
2123,33,highly,O
2124,33,recommend,O
2125,33,this,O
2126,33,accommodation,O
2127,33,option,O
2128,33,.,O
2129,34,It,O
2130,34,is,O
2131,34,a,O
2132,34,really,O
2133,34,good,O
2134,34,hostel,O
2135,34,.,O
2136,34,It,O
2137,34,was,O
2138,34,convenient,O
2139,34,to,O
2140,34,move,O
2141,34,to,O
2142,34,Clarkie,O
2143,34,",",O
2144,34,Orchard,B-geo
2145,34,Road,I-geo
2146,34,",",O
2147,34,which,O
2148,34,is,O
2149,34,located,O
2150,34,opposite,O
2151,34,the,O
2152,34,Chinatown,B-gpe
2153,34,MRT,O
2154,34,.,O
2155,34,I,O
2156,34,do,O
2157,34,not,O
2158,34,think,O
2159,34,it,O
2160,34,is,O
2161,34,not,O
2162,34,a,O
2163,34,local,O
2164,34,",",O
2165,34,not,O
2166,34,a,O
2167,34,local,O
2168,34,",",O
2169,34,not,O
2170,34,a,O
2171,34,local,O
2172,34,",",O
2173,34,not,O
2174,34,a,O
2175,34,local,O
2176,34,",",O
2177,34,which,O
2178,34,is,O
2179,34,not,O
2180,34,a,O
2181,34,local,O
2182,34,",",O
2183,34,but,O
2184,34,it,O
2185,34,is,O
2186,34,a,O
2187,34,big,O
2188,34,Merit,O
2189,34,.,O
2190,34,But,O
2191,34,I,O
2192,34,have,O
2193,34,not,O
2194,34,loud,O
2195,34,",",O
2196,34,but,O
2197,34,I,O
2198,34,have,O
2199,34,been,O
2200,34,sleeping,O
2201,34,well,O
2202,34,.,O
2203,34,I,O
2204,34,bought,O
2205,34,a,O
2206,34,ticket,O
2207,34,on,O
2208,34,my,O
2209,34,neighborhood,O
2210,34,",",O
2211,34,I,O
2212,34,went,O
2213,34,to,O
2214,34,eat,O
2215,34,Yun,O
2216,34,Tost,O
2217,34,every,O
2218,34,morning,O
2219,34,and,O
2220,34,I,O
2221,34,bought,O
2222,34,a,O
2223,34,table,O
2224,34,in,O
2225,34,the,O
2226,34,seawheel,O
2227,34,trading,O
2228,34,.,O
2229,34,Just,O
2230,34,below,O
2231,34,the,O
2232,34,convenience,O
2233,34,store,O
2234,34,is,O
2235,34,located,O
2236,34,.,O
2237,34,The,O
2238,34,picture,O
2239,34,comes,O
2240,34,out,O
2241,34,so,O
2242,34,",",O
2243,34,and,O
2244,34,it,O
2245,34,is,O
2246,34,actually,O
2247,34,in,O
2248,34,practice,O
2249,34,",",O
2250,34,the,O
2251,34,bathroom,O
2252,34,is,O
2253,34,moderately,O
2254,34,large,O
2255,34,.,O
2256,34,I,O
2257,34,think,O
2258,34,two,O
2259,34,people,O
2260,34,were,O
2261,34,really,O
2262,34,comfortable,O
2263,34,and,O
2264,34,good,O
2265,34,in,O
2266,34,the,O
2267,34,stay,O
2268,34,.,O
2269,34,If,O
2270,34,you,O
2271,34,come,O
2272,34,back,O
2273,34,to,O
2274,34,Singapore,B-geo
2275,34,",",O
2276,34,it,O
2277,34,is,O
2278,34,a,O
2279,34,hostel,O
2280,34,that,O
2281,34,you,O
2282,34,want,O
2283,34,to,O
2284,34,come,O
2285,34,again,O
2286,34,.,O
2287,35,I,O
2288,35,recommend,O
2289,35,7,B-org
2290,35,Wonders,I-org
2291,35,Hostel,I-org
2292,35,situated,O
2293,35,at,O
2294,35,Upper,B-geo
2295,35,Dickson,I-geo
2296,35,Rd,I-geo
2297,35,",",O
2298,35,it,O
2299,35,is,O
2300,35,just,O
2301,35,13,O
2302,35,mins,O
2303,35,walk,O
2304,35,to,O
2305,35,Bugis,B-geo
2306,35,Street,I-geo
2307,35,",",O
2308,35,close,O
2309,35,to,O
2310,35,some,O
2311,35,restaurants,O
2312,35,.,O
2313,36,Excellent,O
2314,36,place,O
2315,36,to,O
2316,36,stay,O
2317,36,.,O
2318,36,Lovely,O
2319,36,owner,O
2320,36,",",O
2321,36,good,O
2322,36,and,O
2323,36,cheap,O
2324,36,restaurants,O
2325,36,around,O
2326,36,",",O
2327,36,clean,O
2328,36,and,O
2329,36,nice,O
2330,36,rooms,O
2331,36,and,O
2332,36,close,O
2333,36,to,O
2334,36,Bugis,B-org
2334,36,Junction,I-org
2335,36,.,O
2336,36,Perfect,O
2337,37,Great,O
2338,37,location,O
2339,37,right,O
2340,37,at,O
2341,37,MRT,O
2342,37,Chinatown,B-gpe
2343,37,for,O
2344,37,the,O
2345,37,location,O
2346,37,great,O
2347,37,value,O
2348,37,for,O
2349,37,money,O
2350,37,offer,O
2351,37,very,O
2352,37,attentive,O
2353,37,and,O
2354,37,friendly,O
2355,37,staff,O
2356,38,Stylish,O
2357,38,space,O
2358,38,",",O
2359,38,thoughtful,O
2360,38,and,O
2361,38,thorough,O
2362,38,communication,O
2363,38,for,O
2364,38,check,O
2365,38,in,O
2366,38,",",O
2367,38,responsive,O
2368,38,when,O
2369,38,asked,O
2370,38,questions,O
2371,38,",",O
2372,38,AMAZING,O
2373,38,location,O
2374,38,just,O
2375,38,a,O
2376,38,short,O
2377,38,walk,O
2378,38,to,O
2379,38,the,O
2380,38,centre,O
2381,38,of,O
2382,38,Orchard,B-geo
2383,38,",",O
2384,38,would,O
2385,38,totally,O
2386,38,recommend,O
2387,39,Great,O
2388,39,place,O
2389,39,to,O
2390,39,stay,O
2391,39,if,O
2392,39,you,O
2393,39,re,O
2394,39,new,O
2395,39,to,O
2396,39,SG,B-geo
2397,39,.,O
2398,39,Because,O
2399,39,it,O
2400,39,is,O
2401,39,a,O
2402,39,services,O
2403,39,apartment,O
2404,39,everything,O
2405,39,from,O
2406,39,dishes,O
2407,39,to,O
2408,39,basic,O
2409,39,toiletries,O
2410,39,are,O
2411,39,taken,O
2412,39,care,O
2413,39,of,O
2414,39,for,O
2415,39,you,O
2416,39,.,O
2417,39,The,O
2418,39,location,O
2419,39,is,O
2420,39,also,O
2421,39,very,O
2422,39,very,O
2423,39,convenient,O
2424,39,.,O
2425,39,Very,O
2426,39,close,O
2427,39,to,O
2428,39,the,O
2429,39,MRT,O
2430,39,at,O
2431,39,Somerset,B-geo
2432,39,",",O
2433,39,the,O
2434,39,shops,O
2435,39,at,O
2436,39,Orchard,B-geo
2437,39,Rd,I-geo
2438,39,",",O
2439,39,as,O
2440,39,well,O
2441,39,as,O
2442,39,some,O
2443,39,cheaper,O
2444,39,options,O
2445,39,on,O
2446,39,Killiney,B-geo
2447,39,for,O
2448,39,food,O
2449,39,",",O
2450,39,groceries,O
2451,39,",",O
2452,39,etc,O
2453,39,.,O
2454,40,You,O
2455,40,can,O
2456,40,walk,O
2457,40,to,O
2458,40,the,O
2459,40,Orchard,B-geo
2460,40,",",O
2461,40,Clarke,B-geo
2462,40,Quay,I-geo
2463,40,and,O
2464,40,lots,O
2465,40,of,O
2466,40,restaurants,O
2467,40,.,O
2468,40,Receptionist,O
2469,40,helps,O
2470,40,you,O
2471,40,for,O
2472,40,24,O
2473,40,hours,O
2474,40,and,O
2475,40,was,O
2476,40,very,O
2477,40,helpful,O
2478,40,.,O
2479,41,Very,O
2480,41,well,O
2481,41,located,O
2482,41,accommodation,O
2483,41,",",O
2484,41,close,O
2485,41,to,O
2486,41,two,O
2487,41,metro,O
2488,41,stations,O
2489,41,and,O
2490,41,within,O
2491,41,walking,O
2492,41,distance,O
2493,41,of,O
2494,41,Chinatown,B-gpe
2495,41,and,O
2496,41,Little,B-gpe
2497,41,India,I-gpe
2498,41,neighborhoods,O
2499,41,.,O
2500,41,SK,O
2501,41,is,O
2502,41,very,O
2503,41,kind,O
2504,41,and,O
2505,41,it,O
2506,41,has,O
2507,41,been,O
2508,41,very,O
2509,41,available,O
2510,41,.,O
2511,42,A,O
2512,42,good,O
2513,42,place,O
2514,42,to,O
2515,42,stay,O
2516,42,if,O
2517,42,would,O
2518,42,like,O
2519,42,to,O
2520,42,feel,O
2521,42,like,O
2522,42,home,O
2523,42,where,O
2524,42,you,O
2525,42,can,O
2526,42,cook,O
2527,42,and,O
2528,42,watch,O
2529,42,Apple,B-org
2530,42,TV,O
2531,42,and,O
2532,42,Netflix,B-org
2533,42,too,O
2534,42,.,O
2535,42,Location,O
2536,42,is,O
2537,42,good,O
2538,42,and,O
2539,42,surrounds,O
2540,42,with,O
2541,42,lots,O
2542,42,of,O
2543,42,amenities,O
2544,42,and,O
2545,42,eat,O
2546,42,drink,O
2547,42,and,O
2548,42,shopping,O
2549,42,malls,O
2550,42,Raffles,B-org
2551,42,City,I-org
2552,42,Bugis,B-org
2553,42,Junction,I-org
2554,42,are,O
2555,42,just,O
2556,42,few,O
2557,42,minutes,O
2558,42,walking,O
2559,42,distance,O
2560,42,.,O
2561,42,A,O
2562,42,place,O
2563,42,that,O
2564,42,worth,O
2565,42,the,O
2566,42,value,O
2567,43,Amazing,O
2568,43,location,O
2569,43,in,O
2570,43,Tanjong,B-geo
2571,43,Pagar,I-geo
2572,43,",",O
2573,43,close,O
2574,43,enough,O
2575,43,to,O
2576,43,the,O
2577,43,bustle,O
2578,43,but,O
2579,43,quiet,O
2580,43,on,O
2581,43,nights,O
2582,43,and,O
2583,43,weekends,O
2584,43,as,O
2585,43,it,O
2586,43,is,O
2587,43,in,O
2588,43,CBD,O
2589,43,The,O
2590,43,unit,O
2591,43,itself,O
2592,43,is,O
2593,43,clean,O
2594,43,and,O
2595,43,it,O
2596,43,was,O
2597,43,lovely,O
2598,43,having,O
2599,43,the,O
2600,43,balcony,O
2601,43,that,O
2602,43,faces,O
2603,43,the,O
2604,43,harbor,O
2605,43,of,O
2606,43,Boat,B-geo
2606,43,Quay,I-geo
2607,43,.,O
2608,44,The,O
2609,44,place,O
2610,44,was,O
2611,44,very,O
2612,44,strategic,O
2613,44,",",O
2614,44,very,O
2615,44,near,O
2616,44,Mustafa,B-org
2617,44,Center,I-org
2618,44,and,O
2619,44,the,O
2620,44,Farrer,B-geo
2621,44,Park,I-geo
2622,44,Train,O
2623,44,Station,O
2624,44,.,O
2625,44,Also,O
2626,44,",",O
2627,44,there,O
2628,44,are,O
2629,44,eateries,O
2630,44,just,O
2631,44,below,O
2632,44,the,O
2633,44,apartment,O
2634,44,so,O
2635,44,you,O
2636,44,can,O
2637,44,easily,O
2638,44,grab,O
2639,44,some,O
2640,44,munch,O
2641,44,for,O
2642,44,breakfast,O
2643,44,dinner,O
2644,44,.,O
2645,44,The,O
2646,44,host,O
2647,44,was,O
2648,44,very,O
2649,44,informative,O
2650,44,when,O
2651,44,it,O
2652,44,comes,O
2653,44,to,O
2654,44,check,O
2655,44,in,O
2656,44,and,O
2657,44,also,O
2658,44,provided,O
2659,44,very,O
2660,44,helpful,O
2661,44,details,O
2662,44,before,O
2663,44,we,O
2664,44,even,O
2665,44,arrived,O
2666,44,in,O
2667,44,Singapore,B-geo
2668,44,.,O
2669,44,It,O
2670,44,was,O
2671,44,enough,O
2672,44,space,O
2673,44,for,O
2674,44,two,O
2675,44,people,O
2676,44,to,O
2677,44,stay,O
2678,44,and,O
2679,44,sleep,O
2680,44,in,O
2681,44,.,O
2682,44,The,O
2683,44,design,O
2684,44,was,O
2685,44,very,O
2686,44,chic,O
2687,44,",",O
2688,44,too,O
2689,44,.,O
2690,44,Will,O
2691,44,definitely,O
2692,44,come,O
2693,44,back,O
2694,44,here,O
2695,44,on,O
2696,44,my,O
2697,44,next,O
2698,44,SG,B-geo
2699,44,trip,O
2700,45,Have,O
2701,45,a,O
2702,45,wonderful,O
2703,45,week,O
2704,45,at,O
2705,45,Mich,B-per
2706,45,s,O
2707,45,place,O
2708,45,.,O
2709,45,The,O
2710,45,apartment,O
2711,45,is,O
2712,45,very,O
2713,45,nice,O
2714,45,",",O
2715,45,clean,O
2716,45,and,O
2717,45,near,O
2718,45,all,O
2719,45,the,O
2720,45,public,O
2721,45,transportations,O
2722,45,in,O
2723,45,Singapore,B-geo
2724,45,.,O
2725,45,I,O
2726,45,can,O
2727,45,access,O
2728,45,Orchards,B-geo
2729,45,and,O
2730,45,other,O
2731,45,places,O
2732,45,around,O
2733,45,10,O
2734,45,15min,O
2735,45,using,O
2736,45,SMRT,O
2737,45,or,O
2738,45,Taxi,O
2739,45,.,O
2740,45,Chinatown,B-gpe
2741,45,is,O
2742,45,nearby,O
2743,45,so,O
2744,45,I,O
2745,45,can,O
2746,45,visit,O
2747,45,it,O
2748,45,almost,O
2749,45,everyday,O
2750,45,.,O
2751,45,Definitely,O
2752,45,will,O
2753,45,book,O
2754,45,Mich,B-per
2755,45,s,O
2756,45,place,O
2757,45,again,O
2758,45,next,O
2759,45,time,O
2760,45,we,O
2761,45,visit,O
2762,45,Singapore,B-geo
2763,46,Great,O
2764,46,space,O
2765,46,in,O
2766,46,a,O
2767,46,v,O
2768,46,.,O
2769,46,central,O
2770,46,area,O
2771,46,close,O
2772,46,to,O
2773,46,metro,O
2774,46,station,O
2775,46,.,O
2776,46,Close,O
2777,46,to,O
2778,46,Little,B-gpe
2779,46,India,I-gpe
2780,46,and,O
2781,46,Kampong,B-geo
2782,46,Glam,I-geo
2783,46,.,O
2784,46,Lots,O
2785,46,of,O
2786,46,amazing,O
2787,46,food,O
2788,46,Banana,O
2789,46,Leaf,O
2790,46,in,O
2791,46,these,O
2792,46,busy,O
2793,46,and,O
2794,46,diverse,O
2795,46,neighbourhoods,O
2796,46,",",O
2797,46,but,O
2798,46,far,O
2799,46,enough,O
2800,46,away,O
2801,46,that,O
2802,46,I,O
2803,46,was,O
2804,46,not,O
2805,46,troubled,O
2806,46,by,O
2807,46,noise,O
2808,46,",",O
2809,46,so,O
2810,46,I,O
2811,46,could,O
2812,46,sleep,O
2813,46,in,O
2814,46,.,O
2815,46,Didn,O
2816,46,t,O
2817,46,meet,O
2818,46,Jiayi,O
2819,46,but,O
2820,46,communication,O
2821,46,was,O
2822,46,smooth,O
2823,46,and,O
2824,46,quick,O
2825,46,and,O
2826,46,she,O
2827,46,was,O
2828,46,able,O
2829,46,to,O
2830,46,easily,O
2831,46,accommodate,O
2832,46,my,O
2833,46,post,O
2834,46,midnight,O
2835,46,check,O
2836,46,in,O
2837,46,.,O
2838,46,I,O
2839,46,would,O
2840,46,happily,O
2841,46,stay,O
2842,46,here,O
2843,46,again,O
2844,46,.,O
2845,47,I,O
2846,47,highly,O
2847,47,recommend,O
2848,47,Nanda,B-per
2849,47,is,O
2850,47,place,O
2851,47,because,O
2852,47,he,O
2853,47,is,O
2854,47,a,O
2855,47,gracious,O
2856,47,host,O
2857,47,and,O
2858,47,his,O
2859,47,place,O
2860,47,is,O
2861,47,very,O
2862,47,accessible,O
2863,47,.,O
2864,47,Nanda,B-per
2865,47,replied,O
2866,47,to,O
2867,47,all,O
2868,47,out,O
2869,47,queries,O
2870,47,via,O
2871,47,SMS,O
2872,47,or,O
2873,47,Viber,B-org
2874,47,.,O
2875,47,He,O
2876,47,also,O
2877,47,had,O
2878,47,housekeepers,O
2879,47,who,O
2880,47,were,O
2881,47,very,O
2882,47,helpful,O
2883,47,.,O
2884,47,The,O
2885,47,place,O
2886,47,is,O
2887,47,near,O
2888,47,the,O
2889,47,Farrer,B-geo
2890,47,Park,I-geo
2891,47,MRT,O
2892,47,station,O
2893,47,",",O
2894,47,near,O
2895,47,City,B-org
2896,47,Square,I-org
2897,47,mall,I-org
2898,47,where,O
2899,47,you,O
2900,47,will,O
2901,47,have,O
2902,47,a,O
2903,47,lot,O
2904,47,of,O
2905,47,food,O
2906,47,choices,O
2907,47,.,O
2908,47,There,O
2909,47,is,O
2910,47,also,O
2911,47,a,O
2912,47,caf,O
2913,47,downstairs,O
2914,47,where,O
2915,47,you,O
2916,47,can,O
2917,47,grab,O
2918,47,a,O
2919,47,quick,O
2920,47,bite,O
2921,47,.,O
2922,48,Jan,O
2923,48,s,O
2924,48,place,O
2925,48,really,O
2926,48,makes,O
2927,48,you,O
2928,48,feel,O
2929,48,like,O
2930,48,a,O
2931,48,second,O
2932,48,home,O
2933,48,",located",O
2934,48,near,O
2935,48,Raffles,B-org
2936,48,city,I-org
2937,48,",",O
2938,48,Bugis,B-org
2940,48,Junction,I-org
2941,48,and,O
2942,48,more,O
2943,48,",",O
2944,48,apartment,O
2945,48,is,O
2946,48,cleaned,O
2947,48,and,O
2948,48,well,O
2949,48,maintain,O
2950,48,Will,O
2951,48,stay,O
2952,48,again,O
2953,48,in,O
2954,48,this,O
2955,48,excellent,O
2956,48,apartment,O
2957,48,on,O
2958,48,my,O
2959,48,next,O
2960,48,tip,O
2961,48,to,O
2962,48,Singapore,B-geo
2963,48,.,O
2964,49,Great,O
2965,49,apartment,O
2966,49,located,O
2967,49,in,O
2968,49,Chinatown,B-gpe
2969,49,.,O
2970,49,Walking,O
2971,49,distance,O
2972,49,to,O
2973,49,Maxwell,B-org
2974,49,Food,I-org
2975,49,Centre,I-org
2976,49,for,O
2977,49,some,O
2978,49,great,O
2979,49,hawker,O
2980,49,street,O
2981,49,food,O
2982,49,.,O
2983,49,Air,O
2984,49,conditioned,O
2985,49,with,O
2986,49,a,O
2987,49,lovely,O
2988,49,pool,O
2989,49,to,O
2990,49,cool,O
2991,49,off,O
2992,49,after,O
2993,49,a,O
2994,49,long,O
2995,49,day,O
2996,49,sightseeing,O
2997,49,.,O
2998,49,Apartment,O
2999,49,was,O
3000,49,comfortable,O
3001,49,for,O
3002,49,a,O
3003,49,family,O
3004,49,of,O
3005,49,two,O
3006,49,adults,O
3007,49,and,O
3008,49,two,O
3009,49,young,O
3010,49,children,O
3011,49,.,O
3012,49,Located,O
3013,49,above,O
3014,49,the,O
3015,49,MRT,O
3016,49,you,O
3017,49,are,O
3018,49,easily,O
3019,49,able,O
3020,49,to,O
3021,49,get,O
3022,49,anywhere,O
3023,49,in,O
3024,49,Singapore,O
3025,49,.,O
3026,50,Location,O
3027,50,access,O
3028,50,was,O
3029,50,extremely,O
3030,50,convenient,O
3031,50,and,O
3032,50,easy,O
3033,50,and,O
3034,50,the,O
3035,50,24,O
3036,50,hour,O
3037,50,security,O
3038,50,was,O
3039,50,very,O
3040,50,polite,O
3041,50,and,O
3042,50,helpful,O
3043,50,.,O
3044,50,The,O
3045,50,space,O
3046,50,was,O
3047,50,very,O
3048,50,clean,O
3049,50,and,O
3050,50,had,O
3051,50,an,O
3052,50,easy,O
3053,50,layout,O
3054,50,with,O
3055,50,easy,O
3056,50,to,O
3057,50,use,O
3058,50,amenities,O
3059,50,.,O
3060,50,The,O
3061,50,location,O
3062,50,is,O
3063,50,in,O
3064,50,the,O
3065,50,Little,B-gpe
3066,50,India,I-gpe
3067,50,neighborhood,O
3068,50,and,O
3069,50,was,O
3070,50,not,O
3071,50,a,O
3072,50,well,O
3073,50,known,O
3074,50,location,O
3075,50,to,O
3076,50,my,O
3077,50,taxi,O
3078,50,driver,O
3079,50,or,O
3080,50,local,O
3081,50,friends,O
3082,50,but,O
3083,50,they,O
3084,50,had,O
3085,50,little,O
3086,50,trouble,O
3087,50,finding,O
3088,50,it,O
3089,50,when,O
3090,50,using,O
3091,50,GPS,O
3092,50,.,O
3093,50,Short,O
3094,50,10,O
3095,50,minute,O
3096,50,walk,O
3097,50,to,O
3098,50,the,O
3099,50,SMRT,O
3100,50,.,O
3101,50,Stephenie,B-per
3102,50,quickly,O
3103,50,responded,O
3104,50,to,O
3105,50,the,O
3106,50,few,O
3107,50,questions,O
3108,50,I,O
3109,50,had,O
3110,50,and,O
3111,50,made,O
3112,50,it,O
3113,50,very,O
3114,50,simple,O
3115,50,for,O
3116,50,me,O
3117,50,to,O
3118,50,get,O
3119,50,in,O
3120,50,and,O
3121,50,out,O
3122,50,on,O
3123,50,my,O
3124,50,time,O
3125,50,.,O
3126,50,Thanks,O
3127,51,We,O
3128,51,had,O
3129,51,a,O
3130,51,very,O
3131,51,nice,O
3132,51,stay,O
3133,51,with,O
3134,51,Studios,O
3135,51,57,O
3136,51,.,O
3137,51,We,O
3138,51,were,O
3139,51,welcomed,O
3140,51,and,O
3141,51,the,O
3142,51,host,O
3143,51,show,O
3144,51,us,O
3145,51,the,O
3146,51,place,O
3147,51,.,O
3148,51,We,O
3149,51,used,O
3150,51,the,O
3151,51,provided,O
3152,51,washing,O
3153,51,machine,O
3154,51,.,O
3155,51,We,O
3156,51,could,O
3157,51,use,O
3158,51,the,O
3159,51,kitchen,O
3160,51,",",O
3161,51,but,O
3162,51,we,O
3163,51,did,O
3164,51,not,O
3165,51,have,O
3166,51,to,O
3167,51,.,O
3168,51,The,O
3169,51,apartment,O
3170,51,is,O
3171,51,very,O
3172,51,close,O
3173,51,of,O
3174,51,Sultan,B-geo
3175,51,Mosque,I-geo
3176,51,.,O
3177,51,Many,O
3178,51,places,O
3179,51,to,O
3180,51,eat,O
3181,51,.,O
3182,51,Recommend,O
3183,52,Gayang,O
3184,52,and,O
3185,52,Hostel,O
3186,52,can,O
3187,52,reach,O
3188,52,Marina,B-geo
3189,52,Bay,I-geo
3190,52,or,O
3191,52,Chinatown,B-gpe
3192,52,for,O
3193,52,about,O
3194,52,20,O
3195,52,30,O
3196,52,to,O
3197,52,approximately,O
3198,52,20,O
3199,52,30,O
3200,52,to,O
3201,52,GRAB,B-org
3202,52,.,O
3203,52,Taxi,O
3204,52,or,O
3205,52,Grab,B-org
3206,52,arrived,O
3207,52,in,O
3208,52,5,O
3209,52,minutes,O
3210,52,and,O
3211,52,went,O
3212,52,to,O
3213,52,a,O
3214,52,big,O
3215,52,uncomfortable,O
3216,52,.,O
3217,52,There,O
3218,52,are,O
3219,52,a,O
3220,52,lot,O
3221,52,of,O
3222,52,restaurants,O
3223,52,and,O
3224,52,affordable,O
3225,52,convenience,O
3226,52,stores,O
3227,52,.,O
3228,52,It,O
3229,52,is,O
3230,52,very,O
3231,52,good,O
3232,52,with,O
3233,52,shower,O
3234,52,facilities,O
3235,52,.,O
3236,53,The,O
3237,53,place,O
3238,53,is,O
3239,53,clean,O
3240,53,and,O
3241,53,in,O
3242,53,the,O
3243,53,heart,O
3244,53,of,O
3245,53,Chinatown,B-gpe
3246,53,.,O
3247,53,Staff,O
3248,53,are,O
3249,53,friendly,O
3250,53,and,O
3251,53,place,O
3252,53,is,O
3253,53,calm,O
3254,53,after,O
3255,53,hours,O
3256,53,.,O
3257,53,I,O
3258,53,can,O
3259,53,recommend,O
3260,53,fully,O
3261,53,.,O
3262,54,The,O
3263,54,place,O
3264,54,is,O
3265,54,even,O
3266,54,better,O
3267,54,in,O
3268,54,real,O
3269,54,life,O
3270,54,.,O
3271,54,Everything,O
3272,54,is,O
3273,54,perfect,O
3274,54,.,O
3275,54,The,O
3276,54,host,O
3277,54,is,O
3278,54,also,O
3279,54,very,O
3280,54,quick,O
3281,54,to,O
3282,54,respond,O
3283,54,as,O
3284,54,well,O
3285,54,as,O
3286,54,Bobby,O
3287,54,who,O
3288,54,took,O
3289,54,care,O
3290,54,of,O
3291,54,us,O
3292,54,during,O
3293,54,our,O
3294,54,stay,O
3295,54,.,O
3296,54,Request,O
3297,54,for,O
3298,54,additional,O
3299,54,pillows,O
3300,54,was,O
3301,54,granted,O
3302,54,without,O
3303,54,hesitation,O
3304,54,.,O
3305,54,My,O
3306,54,wife,O
3307,54,who,O
3308,54,is,O
3309,54,very,O
3310,54,picky,O
3311,54,with,O
3312,54,the,O
3313,54,places,O
3314,54,we,O
3315,54,rent,O
3316,54,out,O
3317,54,is,O
3318,54,very,O
3319,54,impressed,O
3320,54,.,O
3321,54,Location,O
3322,54,is,O
3323,54,also,O
3324,54,superb,O
3325,54,as,O
3326,54,it,O
3327,54,is,O
3328,54,next,O
3329,54,to,O
3330,54,a,O
3331,54,Hawkers,O
3332,54,center,O
3333,54,about,O
3334,54,3,O
3335,54,minute,O
3336,54,walk,O
3337,54,and,O
3338,54,is,O
3339,54,near,O
3340,54,to,O
3341,54,Orchard,B-geo
3342,54,Road,I-geo
3343,54,and,O
3344,54,Marina,B-geo
3345,54,Bay,I-geo
3346,54,.,O
3347,54,Highly,O
3348,54,recommended,O
3349,54,and,O
3350,54,well,O
3351,54,surely,O
3352,54,book,O
3353,54,this,O
3354,54,again,O
3355,54,in,O
3356,54,the,O
3357,54,future,O
3358,54,.,O
3359,54,Thanks,O
3360,54,Simon,O
3361,54,and,O
3362,54,Bobby,O
3363,55,Elizabeth,O
3364,55,was,O
3365,55,a,O
3366,55,nice,O
3367,55,and,O
3368,55,flexible,O
3369,55,host,O
3370,55,",",O
3371,55,she,O
3372,55,was,O
3373,55,there,O
3374,55,when,O
3375,55,we,O
3376,55,arrived,O
3377,55,and,O
3378,55,made,O
3379,55,sure,O
3380,55,we,O
3381,55,had,O
3382,55,everything,O
3383,55,we,O
3384,55,needed,O
3385,55,.,O
3386,55,The,O
3387,55,place,O
3388,55,is,O
3389,55,well,O
3390,55,located,O
3391,55,and,O
3392,55,within,O
3393,55,walking,O
3394,55,distance,O
3395,55,to,O
3396,55,Orchard,B-geo
3397,55,and,O
3398,55,Little,B-gpe
3399,55,India,I-gpe
3400,55,",",O
3401,55,taxi,O
3402,55,from,O
3403,55,the,O
3404,55,airport,O
3405,55,is,O
3406,55,less,O
3407,55,than,O
3408,55,20,O
3409,55,.,O
3410,55,The,O
3411,55,house,O
3412,55,is,O
3413,55,not,O
3414,55,new,O
3415,55,but,O
3416,55,everything,O
3417,55,worked,O
3418,55,.,O
3419,55,Tall,O
3420,55,travellers,O
3421,55,over,O
3422,55,6,O
3423,55,might,O
3424,55,find,O
3425,55,the,O
3426,55,bed,O
3427,55,to,O
3428,55,be,O
3429,55,on,O
3430,55,the,O
3431,55,short,O
3432,55,side,O
3433,55,.,O
3434,56,This,O
3435,56,is,O
3436,56,a,O
3437,56,great,O
3438,56,place,O
3439,56,.,O
3440,56,Nice,O
3441,56,",",O
3442,56,modern,O
3443,56,",",O
3444,56,chic,O
3445,56,apartment,O
3446,56,.,O
3447,56,Very,O
3448,56,central,O
3449,56,location,O
3450,56,",",O
3451,56,walkable,O
3452,56,to,O
3453,56,Orchard,B-geo
3454,56,Road,I-geo
3455,56,.,O
3456,56,And,O
3457,56,always,O
3458,56,quick,O
3459,56,communication,O
3460,56,from,O
3461,56,Darrick,B-per
3462,56,",",O
3463,56,whose,O
3464,56,staff,O
3465,56,were,O
3466,56,very,O
3467,56,helpful,O
3468,56,on,O
3469,56,our,O
3470,56,arrival,O
3471,56,and,O
3472,56,checkout,O
3473,56,.,O
3474,56,Recommended,O
3475,56,.,O
3476,57,is,O
3477,57,a,O
3478,57,very,O
3479,57,nice,O
3480,57,host,O
3481,57,.,O
3482,57,She,O
3483,57,share,O
3484,57,their,O
3485,57,food,O
3486,57,with,O
3487,57,us,O
3488,57,as,O
3489,57,if,O
3490,57,we,O
3491,57,are,O
3492,57,their,O
3493,57,family,O
3494,57,.,O
3495,57,She,O
3496,57,helps,O
3497,57,us,O
3498,57,find,O
3499,57,nearby,O
3500,57,places,O
3501,57,to,O
3502,57,eat,O
3503,57,.,O
3504,57,The,O
3505,57,place,O
3506,57,is,O
3507,57,very,O
3508,57,beautiful,O
3509,57,.,O
3510,57,There,O
3511,57,is,O
3512,57,swimming,O
3513,57,pool,O
3514,57,and,O
3515,57,gym,O
3516,57,.,O
3517,57,The,O
3518,57,place,O
3519,57,is,O
3520,57,also,O
3521,57,near,O
3522,57,the,O
3523,57,Singapore,B-org
3524,57,Botanic,I-org
3525,57,Gardens,I-org
3526,57,.,O
3527,57,Our,O
3528,57,stay,O
3529,57,in,O
3530,57,is,O
3531,57,place,O
3532,57,is,O
3533,57,worth,O
3534,57,the,O
3535,57,money,O
3536,57,we,O
3537,57,spent,O
3538,57,.,O
3539,58,A,O
3540,58,great,O
3541,58,stay,O
3542,58,and,O
3543,58,loft,O
3544,58,at,O
3545,58,Elise,B-per
3546,58,is,O
3547,58,place,O
3548,58,.,O
3549,58,Gemmill,B-geo
3550,58,lane,I-geo
3551,58,is,O
3552,58,a,O
3553,58,gem,O
3554,58,Nice,O
3555,58,restaurants,O
3556,58,and,O
3557,58,foot,O
3558,58,massage,O
3559,58,place,O
3560,58,24,O
3561,58,hours,O
3562,58,after,O
3563,58,lots,O
3564,58,of,O
3565,58,walking,O
3566,58,and,O
3567,58,near,O
3568,58,Chinatown,B-gpe
3569,58,.,O
3570,58,Tips,O
3571,58,For,O
3572,58,hot,O
3573,58,water,O
3574,58,for,O
3575,58,the,O
3576,58,shower,O
3577,58,simply,O
3578,58,turn,O
3579,58,on,O
3580,58,the,O
3581,58,water,O
3582,58,heater,O
3583,58,switch,O
3584,58,near,O
3585,58,the,O
3586,58,bathroom,O
3587,58,lightswitch,O
3588,58,",",O
3589,58,prepare,O
3590,58,for,O
3591,58,some,O
3592,58,stairs,O
3593,58,to,O
3594,58,the,O
3595,58,entrance,O
3596,58,and,O
3597,58,if,O
3598,58,you,O
3599,58,have,O
3600,58,the,O
3601,58,locker,O
3602,58,room,O
3603,58,",",O
3604,58,they,O
3605,58,allow,O
3606,58,luggage,O
3607,58,storage,O
3608,58,in,O
3609,58,the,O
3610,58,walkway,O
3611,58,area,O
3612,58,and,O
3613,58,the,O
3614,58,AC,O
3615,58,helps,O
3616,58,for,O
3617,58,a,O
3618,58,hot,O
3619,58,day,O
3620,58,.,O
3621,58,Bring,O
3622,58,own,O
3623,58,amenities,O
3624,58,like,O
3625,58,shampoo,O
3626,58,and,O
3627,58,soaps,O
3628,58,.,O
3629,59,A,O
3630,59,very,O
3631,59,lovely,O
3632,59,and,O
3633,59,well,O
3634,59,equipped,O
3635,59,accommodation,O
3636,59,in,O
3637,59,Singapore,B-geo
3638,59,.,O
3639,59,Location,O
3640,59,is,O
3641,59,exactly,O
3642,59,opposite,O
3643,59,the,O
3644,59,new,O
3645,59,MRT,O
3646,59,station,O
3647,59,which,O
3648,59,will,O
3649,59,operate,O
3650,59,starting,O
3651,59,October,O
3652,59,21st,O
3653,59,",",O
3654,59,2017,O
3655,59,.,O
3656,59,Little,B-gpe
3657,59,India,I-gpe
3658,59,is,O
3659,59,just,O
3660,59,right,O
3661,59,behind,O
3662,59,with,O
3663,59,plenty,O
3664,59,of,O
3665,59,food,O
3666,59,choices,O
3667,59,available,O
3668,59,in,O
3669,59,the,O
3670,59,neighborhood,O
3671,59,.,O
3672,59,The,O
3673,59,host,O
3674,59,was,O
3675,59,very,O
3676,59,helpful,O
3677,59,in,O
3678,59,assisting,O
3679,59,us,O
3680,59,in,O
3681,59,checking,O
3682,59,in,O
3683,59,",",O
3684,59,bringing,O
3685,59,us,O
3686,59,through,O
3687,59,the,O
3688,59,amenities,O
3689,59,facilities,O
3690,59,available,O
3691,59,and,O
3692,59,provided,O
3693,59,us,O
3694,59,with,O
3695,59,useful,O
3696,59,information,O
3697,59,on,O
3698,59,the,O
3699,59,surrounding,O
3700,59,places,O
3701,59,of,O
3702,59,attraction,O
3703,59,.,O
3704,59,The,O
3705,59,room,O
3706,59,is,O
3707,59,clean,O
3708,59,and,O
3709,59,very,O
3710,59,spacious,O
3711,59,for,O
3712,59,Singapore,B-geo
3713,59,is,O
3714,59,standard,O
3715,59,.,O
3716,59,Highly,O
3717,59,recommended,O
3718,59,and,O
3719,59,hope,O
3720,59,to,O
3721,59,visit,O
3722,59,again,O
3723,59,soon,O
3724,59,.,O
3725,60,It,O
3726,60,is,O
3727,60,a,O
3728,60,nice,O
3729,60,studio,O
3730,60,in,O
3731,60,a,O
3732,60,very,O
3733,60,good,O
3734,60,location,O
3735,60,.,O
3736,60,Only,O
3737,60,a,O
3738,60,few,O
3739,60,meters,O
3740,60,from,O
3741,60,Telok,B-geo
3742,60,Ayer,I-geo
3743,60,food,O
3744,60,market,O
3745,60,and,O
3746,60,also,O
3747,60,very,O
3748,60,close,O
3749,60,to,O
3750,60,the,O
3751,60,river,O
3752,60,and,O
3753,60,all,O
3754,60,the,O
3755,60,sights,O
3756,60,and,O
3757,60,restaurants,O
3758,60,there,O
3759,60,.,O
3760,60,Kendra,B-per
3761,60,was,O
3762,60,a,O
3763,60,very,O
3764,60,friendly,O
3765,60,and,O
3766,60,very,O
3767,60,helpful,O
3768,60,hostess,O
3769,60,.,O
3770,60,We,O
3771,60,enjoyed,O
3772,60,the,O
3773,60,stay,O
3774,60,very,O
3775,60,much,O
3776,60,.,O
3777,61,The,O
3778,61,space,O
3779,61,is,O
3780,61,as,O
3781,61,advertised,O
3782,61,a,O
3783,61,bit,O
3784,61,small,O
3785,61,",",O
3786,61,but,O
3787,61,fine,O
3788,61,because,O
3789,61,we,O
3790,61,were,O
3791,61,really,O
3792,61,only,O
3793,61,in,O
3794,61,the,O
3795,61,apartment,O
3796,61,to,O
3797,61,shower,O
3798,61,and,O
3799,61,sleep,O
3800,61,.,O
3801,61,The,O
3802,61,location,O
3803,61,is,O
3804,61,fantastic,O
3805,61,Hawker,O
3806,61,centers,O
3807,61,and,O
3808,61,Chinatown,B-gpe
3809,61,all,O
3810,61,within,O
3811,61,short,O
3812,61,walking,O
3813,61,distance,O
3814,61,.,O
3815,61,We,O
3816,61,decided,O
3817,61,to,O
3818,61,use,O
3819,61,taxis,O
3820,61,for,O
3821,61,MBS,B-org
3822,61,and,O
3823,61,Gardens,B-org
3824,61,by,I-org
3825,61,the,I-org
3826,61,Bay,I-org
3827,61,",",O
3828,61,but,O
3829,61,could,O
3830,61,have,O
3831,61,walked,O
3832,61,the,O
3833,61,30,O
3834,61,minutes,O
3835,61,or,O
3836,61,so,O
3837,61,it,O
3838,61,would,O
3839,61,have,O
3840,61,taken,O
3841,61,to,O
3842,61,get,O
3843,61,there,O
3844,61,if,O
3845,61,it,O
3846,61,weren,O
3847,61,t,O
3848,61,for,O
3849,61,the,O
3850,61,heat,O
3851,61,.,O
3852,61,Space,O
3853,61,is,O
3854,61,clean,O
3855,61,and,O
3856,61,comes,O
3857,61,with,O
3858,61,basic,O
3859,61,amenities,O
3860,61,",",O
3861,61,but,O
3862,61,no,O
3863,61,shampoo,O
3864,61,soap,O
3865,61,",",O
3866,61,so,O
3867,61,be,O
3868,61,sure,O
3869,61,to,O
3870,61,bring,O
3871,61,your,O
3872,61,own,O
3873,62,nice,O
3874,62,place,O
3875,62,convenient,O
3876,62,",",O
3877,62,just,O
3878,62,five,O
3879,62,mins,O
3880,62,walk,O
3881,62,to,O
3882,62,Chinatown,B-gpe
3883,62,mrt,O
3884,62,small,O
3885,62,but,O
3886,62,clean,O
3887,62,suitable,O
3888,62,for,O
3889,62,short,O
3890,62,stay,O
3891,63,David,O
3892,63,has,O
3893,63,worked,O
3894,63,hard,O
3895,63,to,O
3896,63,make,O
3897,63,his,O
3898,63,home,O
3899,63,a,O
3900,63,great,O
3901,63,experience,O
3902,63,for,O
3903,63,travelers,O
3904,63,.,O
3905,63,Even,O
3906,63,providing,O
3907,63,many,O
3908,63,items,O
3909,63,that,O
3910,63,traveling,O
3911,63,lite,O
3912,63,you,O
3913,63,would,O
3914,63,wish,O
3915,63,that,O
3916,63,you,O
3917,63,packed,O
3918,63,but,O
3919,63,could,O
3920,63,not,O
3921,63,sacrifice,O
3922,63,the,O
3923,63,weight,O
3924,63,and,O
3925,63,space,O
3926,63,in,O
3927,63,your,O
3928,63,luggage,O
3929,63,.,O
3930,63,Located,O
3931,63,in,O
3932,63,the,O
3933,63,heart,O
3934,63,of,O
3935,63,Chinatown,B-gpe
3936,63,",",O
3937,63,there,O
3938,63,is,O
3939,63,never,O
3940,63,a,O
3941,63,shortage,O
3942,63,of,O
3943,63,amazing,O
3944,63,food,O
3945,63,even,O
3946,63,Michelin,B-org
3947,63,Star,O
3948,63,rated,O
3949,63,food,O
3950,63,.,O
3951,63,And,O
3952,63,you,O
3953,63,are,O
3954,63,literally,O
3955,63,a,O
3956,63,hop,O
3957,63,away,O
3958,63,from,O
3959,63,transit,O
3960,63,on,O
3961,63,the,O
3962,63,MRT,O
3963,63,",",O
3964,63,so,O
3965,63,easy,O
3966,63,to,O
3967,63,get,O
3968,63,to,O
3969,63,where,O
3970,63,you,O
3971,63,would,O
3972,63,want,O
3973,63,to,O
3974,63,go,O
3975,63,.,O
3976,63,The,O
3977,63,apartment,O
3978,63,is,O
3979,63,compact,O
3980,63,",",O
3981,63,but,O
3982,63,has,O
3983,63,all,O
3984,63,that,O
3985,63,you,O
3986,63,would,O
3987,63,need,O
3988,63,for,O
3989,63,a,O
3990,63,comfortable,O
3991,63,trip,O
3992,63,.,O
3993,64,Super,O
3994,64,affordable,O
3995,64,and,O
3996,64,in,O
3997,64,a,O
3998,64,great,O
3999,64,part,O
4000,64,of,O
4001,64,town,O
4002,64,",",O
4003,64,Arab,B-geo
4004,64,Street,I-geo
4005,64,is,O
4006,64,a,O
4007,64,personal,O
4008,64,fave,O
4009,64,of,O
4010,64,mine,O
4011,64,for,O
4012,64,food,O
4013,64,and,O
4014,64,Bugis,B-geo
4015,64,MRT,O
4016,64,is,O
4017,64,a,O
4018,64,5,O
4019,64,minute,O
4020,64,walk,O
4021,64,away,O
4022,64,.,O
4023,65,Clean,O
4024,65,and,O
4025,65,has,O
4026,65,everything,O
4027,65,you,O
4028,65,need,O
4029,65,for,O
4030,65,a,O
4031,65,simple,O
4032,65,and,O
4033,65,comfortable,O
4034,65,stay,O
4035,65,.,O
4036,65,I,O
4037,65,really,O
4038,65,like,O
4039,65,the,O
4040,65,Bugis,O
4041,65,area,O
4042,65,lots,O
4043,65,of,O
4044,65,good,O
4045,65,food,O
4046,65,around,O
4047,65,and,O
4048,65,very,O
4049,65,convenient,O
4050,65,location,O
4051,65,for,O
4052,65,exploring,O
4053,65,the,O
4054,65,city,O
4055,65,.,O
4056,66,The,O
4057,66,place,O
4058,66,is,O
4059,66,awesome,O
4060,66,specially,O
4061,66,the,O
4062,66,neighborhood,O
4063,66,.,O
4064,66,Very,O
4065,66,close,O
4066,66,to,O
4067,66,Tiong,B-geo
4068,66,Bahru,I-geo
4069,66,food,O
4070,66,market,O
4071,66,.,O
4072,66,Love,O
4073,66,the,O
4074,66,place,O
4075,66,",",O
4076,66,very,O
4077,66,quite,O
4078,66,you,O
4079,66,can,O
4080,66,really,O
4081,66,have,O
4082,66,a,O
4083,66,good,O
4084,66,sleep,O
4085,66,after,O
4086,66,all,O
4087,66,day,O
4088,66,of,O
4089,66,walking,O
4090,66,around,O
4091,66,singapore,B-geo
4092,66,.,O
4093,66,Definitely,O
4094,66,recommend,O
4095,67,The,O
4096,67,room,O
4097,67,is,O
4098,67,very,O
4099,67,clean,O
4100,67,",",O
4101,67,the,O
4102,67,facilities,O
4103,67,are,O
4104,67,all,O
4105,67,available,O
4106,67,",",O
4107,67,and,O
4108,67,even,O
4109,67,the,O
4110,67,conversion,O
4111,67,plugs,O
4112,67,do,O
4113,67,not,O
4114,67,need,O
4115,67,you,O
4116,67,to,O
4117,67,prepare,O
4118,67,The,O
4119,67,geographical,O
4120,67,location,O
4121,67,is,O
4122,67,also,O
4123,67,very,O
4124,67,good,O
4125,67,.,O
4126,67,Because,O
4127,67,of,O
4128,67,the,O
4129,67,long,O
4130,67,selling,O
4131,67,",",O
4132,67,there,O
4133,67,is,O
4134,67,no,O
4135,67,subway,O
4136,67,to,O
4137,67,call,O
4138,67,the,O
4139,67,car,O
4140,67,with,O
4141,67,a,O
4142,67,GRAB,B-org
4143,67,",",O
4144,67,go,O
4145,67,to,O
4146,67,the,O
4147,67,airport,O
4148,67,17,O
4149,67,new,O
4150,67,coins,O
4151,67,",",O
4152,67,non,O
4153,67,peak,O
4154,67,period,O
4155,67,to,O
4156,67,Singapore,B-org
4157,67,Zoo,I-org
4158,67,18,O
4159,67,new,O
4160,67,coins,O
4161,67,",",O
4162,67,to,O
4163,67,Orchard,B-geo
4164,67,Road,I-geo
4165,67,Ion8,O
4166,67,block,O
4167,67,",",O
4168,67,Binhai,B-geo
4169,67,Garden,I-geo
4170,67,11,O
4171,67,",",O
4172,67,USS13.00,O
4173,67,",",O
4174,67,you,O
4175,67,can,O
4176,67,give,O
4177,67,you,O
4178,67,a,O
4179,67,reference,O
4180,67,It,O
4181,67,is,O
4182,67,also,O
4183,67,very,O
4184,67,convenient,O
4185,67,to,O
4186,67,eat,O
4187,67,in,O
4188,67,the,O
4189,67,footage,O
4190,67,.,O
4191,67,There,O
4192,67,is,O
4193,67,a,O
4194,67,chart,O
4195,67,in,O
4196,67,the,O
4197,67,street,O
4198,67,",",O
4199,67,there,O
4200,67,is,O
4201,67,a,O
4202,67,porridge,O
4203,67,to,O
4204,67,eat,O
4205,67,a,O
4206,67,small,O
4207,67,dish,O
4208,67,",",O
4209,67,next,O
4210,67,to,O
4211,67,a,O
4212,67,shop,O
4213,67,can,O
4214,67,eat,O
4215,67,Guangdong,B-geo
4216,67,",",O
4217,67,go,O
4218,67,forward,O
4219,67,for,O
4220,67,five,O
4221,67,or,O
4222,67,six,O
4223,67,minutes,O
4224,67,There,O
4225,67,is,O
4226,67,a,O
4227,67,street,O
4228,67,in,O
4229,67,the,O
4230,67,bridge,O
4231,67,",",O
4232,67,about,O
4233,67,four,O
4234,67,or,O
4235,67,five,O
4236,67,restaurants,O
4237,67,",",O
4238,67,there,O
4239,67,are,O
4240,67,northeast,O
4241,67,dishes,O
4242,67,",",O
4243,67,chicken,O
4244,67,citizens,O
4245,67,",",O
4246,67,vegetable,O
4247,67,fast,O
4248,67,food,O
4249,67,",",O
4250,67,juice,O
4251,67,soy,O
4252,67,milk,O
4253,67,",",O
4254,67,7,O
4255,67,11,O
4256,67,",",O
4257,67,there,O
4258,67,is,O
4259,67,no,O
4260,67,big,O
4261,67,store,O
4262,67,",",O
4263,67,there,O
4264,67,is,O
4265,67,an,O
4266,67,ATM,O
4267,67,machine,O
4268,67,outside,O
4269,67,.,O
4270,67,In,O
4271,67,short,O
4272,67,",",O
4273,67,Very,O
4274,67,convenient,O
4275,67,",",O
4276,67,family,O
4277,67,travel,O
4278,67,is,O
4279,67,highly,O
4280,67,recommended,O
4281,67,.,O
4282,67,The,O
4283,67,landlord,O
4284,67,is,O
4285,67,also,O
4286,67,very,O
4287,67,nice,O
4288,67,",",O
4289,67,there,O
4290,67,is,O
4291,67,a,O
4292,67,question,O
4293,67,",",O
4294,67,and,O
4295,67,the,O
4296,67,reply,O
4297,67,is,O
4298,67,very,O
4299,67,timely,O
4300,67,.,O
4301,68,Excellent,O
4302,68,location,O
4303,68,two,O
4304,68,minutes,O
4305,68,away,O
4306,68,from,O
4307,68,Somerset,B-geo
4308,68,MRT,O
4309,68,and,O
4310,68,a,O
4311,68,string,O
4312,68,of,O
4313,68,amazing,O
4314,68,restaurants,O
4315,68,.,O
4316,68,Perfect,O
4317,68,for,O
4318,68,a,O
4319,68,single,O
4320,68,traveler,O
4321,68,or,O
4322,68,a,O
4323,68,couple,O
4324,68,.,O
4325,68,Eric,B-per
4326,68,and,O
4327,68,his,O
4328,68,team,O
4329,68,were,O
4330,68,lovely,O
4331,68,always,O
4332,68,ready,O
4333,68,with,O
4334,68,a,O
4335,68,great,O
4336,68,tip,O
4337,68,about,O
4338,68,the,O
4339,68,area,O
4340,68,",",O
4341,68,and,O
4342,68,extremely,O
4343,68,accommodating,O
4344,68,.,O
4345,69,Mr,B-per
4346,69,Ong,I-per
4347,69,ang,O
4348,69,Elle,B-per
4349,69,are,O
4350,69,very,O
4351,69,good,O
4352,69,hosts,O
4353,69,.,O
4354,69,They,O
4355,69,are,O
4356,69,very,O
4357,69,welcoming,O
4358,69,and,O
4359,69,heart,O
4360,69,warming,O
4361,69,.,O
4362,69,I,O
4363,69,got,O
4364,69,to,O
4365,69,meet,O
4366,69,Mr,B-per
4367,69,.,I-per
4368,69,Ong,I-per
4369,69,in,O
4370,69,person,O
4371,69,and,O
4372,69,we,O
4373,69,had,O
4374,69,dinner,O
4375,69,together,O
4376,69,Elle,B-per
4377,69,is,O
4378,69,always,O
4379,69,there,O
4380,69,willing,O
4381,69,to,O
4382,69,help,O
4383,69,if,O
4384,69,you,O
4385,69,have,O
4386,69,any,O
4387,69,questions,O
4388,69,.,O
4389,69,Room,O
4390,69,is,O
4391,69,exactly,O
4392,69,the,O
4393,69,same,O
4394,69,as,O
4395,69,shown,O
4396,69,in,O
4397,69,the,O
4398,69,picture,O
4399,69,.,O
4400,69,It,O
4401,69,is,O
4402,69,in,O
4403,69,the,O
4404,69,heart,O
4405,69,of,O
4406,69,the,O
4407,69,city,O
4408,69,",",O
4409,69,2,O
4410,69,mins,O
4411,69,away,O
4412,69,from,O
4413,69,Chinatown,B-gpe
4414,69,The,O
4415,69,bed,O
4416,69,is,O
4417,69,very,O
4418,69,comfortable,O
4419,69,and,O
4420,69,I,O
4421,69,slept,O
4422,69,very,O
4423,69,well,O
4424,69,during,O
4425,69,my,O
4426,69,stay,O
4427,69,Will,O
4428,69,recommend,O
4429,69,Mr,B-per
4430,69,Ong,I-per
4431,69,is,O
4432,69,place,O
4433,69,to,O
4434,69,anyone,O
4435,69,who,O
4436,69,is,O
4437,69,coming,O
4438,69,to,O
4439,69,Singapore,B-geo
4440,70,We,O
4441,70,had,O
4442,70,a,O
4443,70,really,O
4444,70,nice,O
4445,70,time,O
4446,70,in,O
4447,70,Singapour,B-geo
4448,70,.,O
4449,70,The,O
4450,70,appartment,O
4451,70,is,O
4452,70,cosy,O
4453,70,and,O
4454,70,has,O
4455,70,everything,O
4456,70,we,O
4457,70,may,O
4458,70,need,O
4459,70,.,O
4460,70,It,O
4461,70,is,O
4462,70,well,O
4463,70,located,O
4464,70,",",O
4465,70,perfect,O
4466,70,to,O
4467,70,go,O
4468,70,to,O
4469,70,the,O
4470,70,main,O
4471,70,areas,O
4472,70,such,O
4473,70,as,O
4474,70,Kampong,B-geo
4475,70,Glam,I-geo
4476,70,",",O
4477,70,Little,B-gpe
4478,70,India,I-gpe
4479,70,",",O
4480,70,Marina,B-geo
4481,70,Bay,I-geo
4482,70,",",O
4483,70,etc,O
4484,70,.,O
4485,70,Sk,O
4486,70,was,O
4487,70,a,O
4488,70,great,O
4489,70,host,O
4490,70,",",O
4491,70,really,O
4492,70,nice,O
4493,70,and,O
4494,70,helpful,O
4495,70,.,O
4496,70,I,O
4497,70,would,O
4498,70,definetely,O
4499,70,recommend,O
4500,70,this,O
4501,70,place,O
4502,70,.,O
4503,71,Very,O
4504,71,convenient,O
4505,71,location,O
4506,71,.,O
4507,71,It,O
4508,71,is,O
4509,71,close,O
4510,71,to,O
4511,71,MRT,O
4512,71,near,O
4513,71,Telok,B-geo
4514,71,Ayer,I-geo
4515,71,and,O
4516,71,Chinatown,B-gpe
4517,71,Downtown,B-geo
4518,71,line,O
4519,71,.,O
4520,71,The,O
4521,71,bar,O
4522,71,restaurant,O
4523,71,below,O
4524,71,is,O
4525,71,noisy,O
4526,71,on,O
4527,71,the,O
4528,71,weekend,O
4529,71,.,O
4530,72,Perfect,O
4531,72,tiny,O
4532,72,house,O
4533,72,in,O
4534,72,the,O
4535,72,absolute,O
4536,72,heart,O
4537,72,of,O
4538,72,Singapore,B-geo
4539,72,.,O
4540,72,Amazingly,O
4541,72,comfy,O
4542,72,bed,O
4543,72,",",O
4544,72,relaxing,O
4545,72,rainfall,O
4546,72,shower,O
4547,72,",",O
4548,72,if,O
4549,72,only,O
4550,72,there,O
4551,72,was,O
4552,72,cooler,O
4553,72,art,O
4554,72,up,O
4555,72,on,O
4556,72,the,O
4557,72,walls,O
4558,72,I,O
4559,72,would,O
4560,72,have,O
4561,72,no,O
4562,72,objections,O
4563,72,at,O
4564,72,all,O
4565,72,.,O
4566,72,The,O
4567,72,location,O
4568,72,is,O
4569,72,what,O
4570,72,is,O
4571,72,really,O
4572,72,killer,O
4573,72,though,O
4574,72,.,O
4575,72,I,O
4576,72,high,O
4577,72,recommend,O
4578,72,walking,O
4579,72,10,O
4580,72,min,O
4581,72,north,O
4582,72,to,O
4583,72,Esplanade,B-geo
4584,72,Park,I-geo
4585,72,among,O
4586,72,the,O
4587,72,best,O
4588,72,360,O
4589,72,views,O
4590,72,in,O
4591,72,SG,B-geo
4592,72,",",O
4593,72,spending,O
4594,72,an,O
4595,72,afternoon,O
4596,72,flaneuring,O
4597,72,around,O
4598,72,Marina,B-org
4599,72,Bay,I-org
4600,72,Sands,I-org
4601,72,",",O
4602,72,and,O
4603,72,grabbing,O
4604,72,breakfast,O
4605,72,at,O
4606,72,the,O
4607,72,Botanist,B-org
4608,72,cafe,I-org
4609,72,a,O
4610,72,short,O
4611,72,bike,O
4612,72,ride,O
4613,72,away,O
4614,72,.,O
4615,73,Regina,B-per
4616,73,s,O
4617,73,place,O
4618,73,is,O
4619,73,strategically,O
4620,73,located,O
4621,73,on,O
4622,73,Orchard,B-geo
4623,73,Road,I-geo
4624,73,in,O
4625,73,between,O
4626,73,Tangs,B-org
4627,73,and,O
4628,73,Paragon,B-org
4629,73,.,O
4630,73,.,O
4631,73,.Shopping,O
4632,73,and,O
4633,73,food,O
4634,73,are,O
4635,73,just,O
4636,73,a,O
4637,73,short,O
4638,73,walk,O
4639,73,away,O
4640,73,.,O
4641,73,You,O
4642,73,are,O
4643,73,able,O
4644,73,to,O
4645,73,drop,O
4646,73,your,O
4647,73,shopping,O
4648,73,at,O
4649,73,home,O
4650,73,halfway,O
4651,73,through,O
4652,73,the,O
4653,73,day,O
4654,73,and,O
4655,73,head,O
4656,73,back,O
4657,73,out,O
4658,73,again,O
4659,73,.,O
4660,73,.,O
4661,73,.,O
4662,73,.The,O
4663,73,place,O
4664,73,is,O
4665,73,really,O
4666,73,spacious,O
4667,73,and,O
4668,73,comfortable,O
4669,73,as,O
4670,73,well,O
4671,73,",",O
4672,73,beds,O
4673,73,enough,O
4674,73,for,O
4675,73,6,O
4676,73,.,O
4677,73,We,O
4678,73,really,O
4679,73,enjoyed,O
4680,73,our,O
4681,73,stay,O
4682,73,at,O
4683,73,her,O
4684,73,place,O
4685,73,as,O
4686,73,it,O
4687,73,is,O
4688,73,really,O
4689,73,convenient,O
4690,74,The,O
4691,74,apartment,O
4692,74,is,O
4693,74,nice,O
4694,74,and,O
4695,74,clean,O
4696,74,for,O
4697,74,Singapore,B-geo
4698,74,ratios,O
4699,74,.,O
4700,74,It,O
4701,74,is,O
4702,74,ideally,O
4703,74,located,O
4704,74,in,O
4705,74,Chinatown,B-gpe
4706,74,and,O
4707,74,the,O
4708,74,train,O
4709,74,there,O
4710,74,is,O
4711,74,no,O
4712,74,5,O
4713,74,minutes,O
4714,74,walk,O
4715,74,.,O
4716,74,The,O
4717,74,apartment,O
4718,74,is,O
4719,74,located,O
4720,74,at,O
4721,74,one,O
4722,74,end,O
4723,74,of,O
4724,74,Club,B-geo
4725,74,Street,I-geo
4726,74,.,O
4727,74,This,O
4728,74,is,O
4729,74,known,O
4730,74,for,O
4731,74,your,O
4732,74,many,O
4733,74,bars,O
4734,74,and,O
4735,74,restaurants,O
4736,74,.,O
4737,74,This,O
4738,74,is,O
4739,74,on,O
4740,74,the,O
4741,74,one,O
4742,74,hand,O
4743,74,super,O
4744,74,",",O
4745,74,on,O
4746,74,the,O
4747,74,other,O
4748,74,side,O
4749,74,you,O
4750,74,hear,O
4751,74,everything,O
4752,74,in,O
4753,74,the,O
4754,74,apartment,O
4755,74,weekdays,O
4756,74,it,O
4757,74,will,O
4758,74,be,O
4759,74,quiet,O
4760,74,between,O
4761,74,23,O
4762,74,and,O
4763,74,0,O
4764,74,of,O
4765,74,the,O
4766,74,clock,O
4767,74,",",O
4768,74,at,O
4769,74,the,O
4770,74,weekend,O
4771,74,at,O
4772,74,2am,O
4773,74,.,O
4774,74,So,O
4775,74,if,O
4776,74,you,O
4777,74,are,O
4778,74,looking,O
4779,74,for,O
4780,74,complete,O
4781,74,peace,O
4782,74,",",O
4783,74,is,O
4784,74,wrong,O
4785,74,here,O
4786,74,.,O
4787,74,Anyone,O
4788,74,who,O
4789,74,wants,O
4790,74,to,O
4791,74,be,O
4792,74,in,O
4793,74,the,O
4794,74,hustle,O
4795,74,and,O
4796,74,bustle,O
4797,74,is,O
4798,74,completely,O
4799,74,right,O
4800,74,here,O
4801,74,.,O
4802,75,1,O
4803,75,.,O
4804,75,The,O
4805,75,booking,O
4806,75,is,O
4807,75,clearly,O
4808,75,written,O
4809,75,in,O
4810,75,the,O
4811,75,Nearest,O
4812,75,MRT,O
4813,75,Queenstown,B-geo
4814,75,MRT,O
4815,75,5,O
4816,75,minutes,O
4817,75,walk,O
4818,75,",",O
4819,75,but,O
4820,75,the,O
4821,75,listings,O
4822,75,are,O
4823,75,not,O
4824,75,in,O
4825,75,this,O
4826,75,place,O
4827,75,",",O
4828,75,not,O
4829,75,only,O
4830,75,the,O
4831,75,nearest,O
4832,75,MRT,O
4833,75,subway,O
4834,75,station,O
4835,75,is,O
4836,75,Clementi,B-geo
4837,75,",",O
4838,75,but,O
4839,75,also,O
4840,75,is,O
4841,75,very,O
4842,75,far,O
4843,75,from,O
4844,75,the,O
4845,75,subway,O
4846,75,station,O
4847,75,",",O
4848,75,walking,O
4849,75,.,O
4850,75,Half,O
4851,75,hour,O
4852,75,.,O
4853,75,The,O
4854,75,description,O
4855,75,of,O
4856,75,the,O
4857,75,transportation,O
4858,75,with,O
4859,75,the,O
4860,75,page,O
4861,75,is,O
4862,75,completely,O
4863,75,incompatible,O
4864,75,0.2,O
4865,75,.,O
4866,75,The,O
4867,75,staff,O
4868,75,responsible,O
4869,75,for,O
4870,75,reception,O
4871,75,is,O
4872,75,bad,O
4873,75,",",O
4874,75,and,O
4875,75,the,O
4876,75,English,B-gpe
4877,75,accent,O
4878,75,is,O
4879,75,difficult,O
4880,75,to,O
4881,75,understand,O
4882,75,",",O
4883,75,and,O
4884,75,others,O
4885,75,cannot,O
4886,75,understand,O
4887,75,him,O
4888,75,.,O
4889,75,This,O
4890,75,listing,O
4891,75,has,O
4892,75,been,O
4893,75,reported,O
4894,75,.,O
4895,76,Fantastic,O
4896,76,location,O
4897,76,in,O
4898,76,the,O
4899,76,heart,O
4900,76,of,O
4901,76,Chinatown,B-gpe
4902,76,.,O
4903,76,Elle,B-per
4904,76,and,O
4905,76,her,O
4906,76,sister,O
4907,76,friendly,O
4908,76,",",O
4909,76,gave,O
4910,76,plenty,O
4911,76,of,O
4912,76,information,O
4913,76,on,O
4914,76,arrival,O
4915,76,.,O
4916,76,Small,O
4917,76,room,O
4918,76,but,O
4919,76,everything,O
4920,76,you,O
4921,76,need,O
4922,76,.,O
4923,76,Great,O
4924,76,Wifi,O
4925,76,.,O
4926,76,Shared,O
4927,76,toilet,O
4928,76,in,O
4929,76,wet,O
4930,76,room,O
4931,76,among,O
4932,76,3,O
4933,76,or,O
4934,76,4,O
4935,76,rooms,O
4936,76,not,O
4937,76,ideal,O
4938,76,but,O
4939,76,fine,O
4940,76,.,O
4941,76,Wonderful,O
4942,76,view,O
4943,76,from,O
4944,76,the,O
4945,76,stairwell,O
4946,76,.,O
4947,76,Will,O
4948,76,definitely,O
4949,76,look,O
4950,76,to,O
4951,76,stay,O
4952,76,again,O
4953,76,next,O
4954,76,time,O
4955,76,in,O
4956,76,Singapore,B-geo
4957,76,.,O
4958,77,If,O
4959,77,you,O
4960,77,are,O
4961,77,looking,O
4962,77,for,O
4963,77,a,O
4964,77,great,O
4965,77,place,O
4966,77,in,O
4967,77,the,O
4968,77,Chinatown,B-geo
4969,77,District,O
4970,77,",",O
4971,77,directly,O
4972,77,at,O
4973,77,a,O
4974,77,MRT,O
4975,77,station,O
4976,77,and,O
4977,77,like,O
4978,77,to,O
4979,77,enjoy,O
4980,77,a,O
4981,77,great,O
4982,77,view,O
4983,77,of,O
4984,77,Singapore,B-geo
4985,77,from,O
4986,77,your,O
4987,77,room,O
4988,77,",",O
4989,77,this,O
4990,77,is,O
4991,77,the,O
4992,77,one,O
4993,77,for,O
4994,77,you,O
4995,77,.,O
4996,78,First,O
4997,78,of,O
4998,78,all,O
4999,78,",",O
5000,78,I,O
5001,78,was,O
5002,78,clean,O
5003,78,and,O
5004,78,comfortable,O
5005,78,as,O
5006,78,a,O
5007,78,picture,O
5008,78,The,O
5009,78,response,O
5010,78,was,O
5011,78,also,O
5012,78,a,O
5013,78,quick,O
5014,78,and,O
5015,78,manager,O
5016,78,",",O
5017,78,the,O
5018,78,Zulhas,O
5019,78,was,O
5020,78,kind,O
5021,78,.,O
5022,78,Somerset,B-geo
5023,78,Station,O
5024,78,A,O
5025,78,Exit,O
5026,78,and,O
5027,78,it,O
5028,78,took,O
5029,78,a,O
5030,78,10,O
5031,78,minute,O
5032,78,distance,O
5033,78,",",O
5034,78,and,O
5035,78,it,O
5036,78,was,O
5037,78,easy,O
5038,78,to,O
5039,78,catch,O
5040,78,taxi,O
5041,78,.,O
5042,78,Our,O
5043,78,flight,O
5044,78,was,O
5045,78,late,O
5046,78,",",O
5047,78,so,O
5048,78,I,O
5049,78,was,O
5050,78,so,O
5051,78,good,O
5052,78,to,O
5053,78,leave,O
5054,78,the,O
5055,78,burgers,O
5056,78,.,O
5057,79,Such,O
5058,79,a,O
5059,79,nice,O
5060,79,and,O
5061,79,clean,O
5062,79,room,O
5063,79,.,O
5064,79,Everything,O
5065,79,in,O
5066,79,the,O
5067,79,room,O
5068,79,is,O
5069,79,perfect,O
5070,79,for,O
5071,79,me,O
5072,79,.,O
5073,79,Very,O
5074,79,near,O
5075,79,to,O
5076,79,the,O
5077,79,MRT,O
5078,79,station,O
5079,79,that,O
5080,79,can,O
5081,79,take,O
5082,79,you,O
5083,79,anywhere,O
5084,79,on,O
5085,79,the,O
5086,79,island,O
5087,79,",",O
5088,79,including,O
5089,79,the,O
5090,79,airport,O
5091,79,.,O
5092,79,Within,O
5093,79,walking,O
5094,79,distance,O
5095,79,to,O
5096,79,Bugis,B-geo
5097,79,and,O
5098,79,Kg,B-geo
5099,79,Glam,I-geo
5100,79,Hj,B-geo
5101,79,Lane,I-geo
5102,79,.,O
5103,79,A,O
5104,79,lot,O
5105,79,of,O
5106,79,restaurants,O
5107,79,in,O
5108,79,surrounding,O
5109,79,area,O
5110,79,so,O
5111,79,you,O
5112,79,would,O
5113,79,never,O
5114,79,get,O
5115,79,hungry,O
5116,79,.,O
5117,79,Overall,O
5118,79,",",O
5119,79,i,O
5120,79,am,O
5121,79,so,O
5122,79,amazed,O
5123,79,by,O
5124,79,Studios,O
5125,79,that,O
5126,79,i,O
5127,79,will,O
5128,79,certainly,O
5129,79,make,O
5130,79,future,O
5131,79,reservations,O
5132,79,when,O
5133,79,ever,O
5134,79,i,O
5135,79,ll,O
5136,79,be,O
5137,79,coming,O
5138,79,to,O
5139,79,Singapore,B-geo
5140,80,This,O
5141,80,is,O
5142,80,a,O
5143,80,great,O
5144,80,place,O
5145,80,.,O
5146,80,Hosts,O
5147,80,showed,O
5148,80,me,O
5149,80,around,O
5150,80,as,O
5151,80,soon,O
5152,80,as,O
5153,80,I,O
5154,80,got,O
5155,80,here,O
5156,80,.,O
5157,80,Very,O
5158,80,close,O
5159,80,to,O
5160,80,Tanjong,B-geo
5161,80,Pagar,I-geo
5162,80,MRT,O
5163,80,",",O
5164,80,Chinatown,B-gpe
5165,80,",",O
5166,80,Club,B-geo
5167,80,St,I-geo
5168,80,.,O
5169,80,and,O
5170,80,more,O
5171,80,.,O
5172,80,Would,O
5173,80,recommend,O
5174,80,this,O
5175,80,place,O
5176,80,for,O
5177,80,business,O
5178,80,travelers,O
5179,80,.,O
5180,81,Great,O
5181,81,homely,O
5182,81,place,O
5183,81,to,O
5184,81,stay,O
5185,81,with,O
5186,81,family,O
5187,81,.,O
5188,81,Location,O
5189,81,is,O
5190,81,perfect,O
5191,81,for,O
5192,81,and,O
5193,81,some,O
5194,81,of,O
5195,81,the,O
5196,81,places,O
5197,81,like,O
5198,81,National,B-org
5199,81,Museum,I-org
5200,81,",",O
5201,81,Little,B-gpe
5202,81,India,I-gpe
5203,81,",",O
5204,81,Bugis,B-geo
5205,81,",",O
5206,81,Clark,B-geo
5207,81,St,I-geo
5208,81,are,O
5209,81,at,O
5210,81,walking,O
5211,81,distance,O
5212,81,.,O
5213,81,All,O
5214,81,amenities,O
5215,81,in,O
5216,81,place,O
5217,81,and,O
5218,81,perfect,O
5219,81,.,O
5220,82,Very,O
5221,82,good,O
5222,82,value,O
5223,82,compared,O
5224,82,to,O
5225,82,low,O
5226,82,cost,O
5227,82,hotels,O
5228,82,.,O
5229,82,Good,O
5230,82,space,O
5231,82,and,O
5232,82,facilities,O
5233,82,",",O
5234,82,comfy,O
5235,82,bed,O
5236,82,and,O
5237,82,good,O
5238,82,bathroom,O
5239,82,.,O
5240,82,Tiong,O
5241,82,Bahru,O
5242,82,is,O
5243,82,a,O
5244,82,stylish,O
5245,82,",",O
5246,82,quiet,O
5247,82,area,O
5248,82,",",O
5249,82,with,O
5250,82,three,O
5251,82,storey,O
5252,82,houses,O
5253,82,.,O
5254,82,Good,O
5255,82,options,O
5256,82,for,O
5257,82,western,O
5258,82,eating,O
5259,82,",",O
5260,82,and,O
5261,82,Tanjung,B-geo
5261,82,Pagar,I-geo
5262,82,Market,O
5263,82,has,O
5264,82,an,O
5265,82,outstanding,O
5266,82,food,O
5267,82,court,O
5268,82,.,O
5269,82,Outram,B-geo
5270,82,Park,I-geo
5271,82,and,O
5272,82,Tiong,B-geo
5273,82,Bahru,I-geo
5274,82,a,O
5275,82,7min,O
5276,82,walk,O
5277,82,.,O
5278,82,Very,O
5279,82,helpful,O
5280,82,housekeeper,O
5281,82,.,O
5282,82,Good,O
5283,82,contact,O
5284,82,and,O
5285,82,directions,O
5286,82,from,O
5287,82,owner,O
5288,82,.,O
5289,82,We,O
5290,82,will,O
5291,82,use,O
5292,82,again,O
5293,82,on,O
5294,82,our,O
5295,82,next,O
5296,82,visit,O
5297,82,.,O
5298,83,Thank,O
5299,83,you,O
5300,83,Darrick,B-per
5301,83,team,O
5302,83,for,O
5303,83,another,O
5304,83,wonderful,O
5305,83,stay,O
5306,83,We,O
5307,83,ve,O
5308,83,stayed,O
5309,83,with,O
5310,83,you,O
5311,83,previously,O
5312,83,before,O
5313,83,back,O
5314,83,in,O
5315,83,March,O
5316,83,2015,O
5317,83,whilst,O
5318,83,travelling,O
5319,83,across,O
5320,83,Australia,B-geo
5321,83,",",O
5322,83,NZ,B-geo
5323,83,Singapore,B-geo
5324,83,.,O
5325,83,A,O
5326,83,little,O
5327,83,chance,O
5328,83,of,O
5329,83,home,O
5330,83,away,O
5331,83,from,O
5332,83,home,O
5333,83,.,O
5334,83,Again,O
5335,83,you,O
5336,83,and,O
5337,83,the,O
5338,83,team,O
5339,83,have,O
5340,83,been,O
5341,83,responsive,O
5342,83,",",O
5343,83,friendly,O
5344,83,",",O
5345,83,helpful,O
5346,83,and,O
5347,83,give,O
5348,83,great,O
5349,83,value,O
5350,83,for,O
5351,83,money,O
5352,83,in,O
5353,83,a,O
5354,83,safe,O
5355,83,and,O
5356,83,clean,O
5357,83,environment,O
5358,83,close,O
5359,83,to,O
5360,83,all,O
5361,83,the,O
5362,83,attractions,O
5363,83,of,O
5364,83,Clarke,B-geo
5365,83,Quay,I-geo
5366,83,and,O
5367,83,downtown,B-geo
5368,83,Singapore,B-geo
5369,83,.,O
5370,83,Thank,O
5371,83,you,O
5372,83,and,O
5373,83,hopefully,O
5374,83,see,O
5375,83,you,O
5376,83,again,O
5377,83,soon,O
5378,83,for,O
5379,83,another,O
5380,83,F1,O
5381,83,weekend,O
5382,83,.,O
5383,84,Nathan,B-per
5384,84,s,O
5385,84,cozy,O
5386,84,home,O
5387,84,is,O
5388,84,Fantastic,O
5389,84,It,O
5390,84,s,O
5391,84,the,O
5392,84,best,O
5393,84,choice,O
5394,84,for,O
5395,84,us,O
5396,84,to,O
5397,84,make,O
5398,84,to,O
5399,84,stay,O
5400,84,at,O
5401,84,this,O
5402,84,house,O
5403,84,.,O
5404,84,The,O
5405,84,department,O
5406,84,is,O
5407,84,very,O
5408,84,neat,O
5409,84,.,O
5410,84,From,O
5411,84,the,O
5412,84,windows,O
5413,84,u,O
5414,84,can,O
5415,84,see,O
5416,84,Marina,B-org
5417,84,Bay,I-org
5418,84,Sands,I-org
5419,84,.,O
5420,84,The,O
5421,84,host,O
5422,84,prepared,O
5423,84,a,O
5424,84,lot,O
5425,84,of,O
5426,84,things,O
5427,84,for,O
5428,84,us,O
5429,84,which,O
5430,84,is,O
5431,84,very,O
5432,84,considerably,O
5433,84,.Nathan,O
5434,84,is,O
5435,84,super,O
5436,84,friendly,O
5437,84,and,O
5438,84,hospitality,O
5439,84,.,O
5440,84,In,O
5441,84,the,O
5442,84,CBD,O
5443,84,area,O
5444,84,",",O
5445,84,very,O
5446,84,near,O
5447,84,to,O
5448,84,the,O
5449,84,Marina,B-org
5450,84,bay,I-org
5451,84,sands,I-org
5452,84,and,O
5453,84,Merlion,B-gpe
5454,84,statue,O
5455,84,.,O
5456,84,Also,O
5457,84,the,O
5458,84,famous,O
5459,84,old,O
5460,84,building,O
5461,84,as,O
5462,84,known,O
5463,84,as,O
5464,84,Lau,B-geo
5465,84,Pa,I-geo
5466,84,Sat,I-geo
5467,84,.,O
5468,84,We,O
5469,84,really,O
5470,84,love,O
5471,84,this,O
5472,84,house,O
5473,84,and,O
5474,84,also,O
5475,84,thanks,O
5476,84,Nathan,B-per
5477,85,Ben,B-per
5478,85,is,O
5479,85,apartment,O
5480,85,is,O
5481,85,very,O
5482,85,well,O
5483,85,located,O
5484,85,Located,O
5485,85,in,O
5486,85,the,O
5487,85,financial,O
5488,85,district,O
5489,85,of,O
5490,85,Singapore,B-geo
5491,85,",",O
5492,85,it,O
5493,85,is,O
5494,85,close,O
5495,85,to,O
5496,85,the,O
5497,85,subway,O
5498,85,and,O
5499,85,the,O
5500,85,Marina,B-org
5501,85,Bay,I-org
5502,85,Sands,I-org
5503,85,.,O
5504,85,The,O
5505,85,space,O
5506,85,is,O
5507,85,a,O
5508,85,little,O
5509,85,smaller,O
5510,85,than,O
5511,85,in,O
5512,85,the,O
5513,85,photos,O
5514,85,.,O
5515,85,The,O
5516,85,communication,O
5517,85,was,O
5518,85,very,O
5519,85,easy,O
5520,85,and,O
5521,85,quick,O
5522,86,Thoroughly,O
5523,86,enjoyed,O
5524,86,my,O
5525,86,stay,O
5526,86,here,O
5527,86,.,O
5528,86,Safe,O
5529,86,",",O
5530,86,clean,O
5531,86,",",O
5532,86,located,O
5533,86,in,O
5534,86,the,O
5535,86,centre,O
5536,86,of,O
5537,86,Chinatown,B-gpe
5538,86,next,O
5539,86,to,O
5540,86,amazing,O
5541,86,food,O
5542,86,and,O
5543,86,a,O
5544,86,really,O
5545,86,comfortable,O
5546,86,bed,O
5547,86,.,O
5548,86,Would,O
5549,86,definitely,O
5550,86,stay,O
5551,86,again,O
5552,86,if,O
5553,86,I,O
5554,86,am,O
5555,86,back,O
5556,86,in,O
5557,86,Singapore,B-geo
5558,86,.,O
5559,87,The,O
5560,87,host,O
5561,87,was,O
5562,87,great,O
5563,87,",",O
5564,87,Although,O
5565,87,the,O
5566,87,mrt,O
5567,87,is,O
5568,87,not,O
5569,87,like,O
5570,87,next,O
5571,87,door,O
5572,87,",",O
5573,87,but,O
5574,87,still,O
5575,87,easy,O
5576,87,to,O
5577,87,go,O
5578,87,to,O
5579,87,town,O
5580,87,or,O
5581,87,Orchard,B-geo
5582,87,",",O
5583,87,a,O
5584,87,cab,O
5585,87,can,O
5586,87,reached,O
5587,87,within,O
5588,87,15,O
5589,87,min,O
5590,87,.,O
5591,87,The,O
5592,87,location,O
5593,87,is,O
5594,87,next,O
5595,87,to,O
5596,87,a,O
5597,87,lot,O
5598,87,of,O
5599,87,famous,O
5600,87,eating,O
5601,87,place,O
5602,87,",",O
5603,87,especially,O
5604,87,local,O
5605,87,foods,O
5606,87,",",O
5607,87,too,O
5608,87,many,O
5609,87,stuff,O
5610,87,to,O
5611,87,eat,O
5612,87,.,O
5613,87,Will,O
5614,87,be,O
5615,87,back,O
5616,87,here,O
5617,87,next,O
5618,87,time,O
5619,88,Anna,B-per
5620,88,Chee,O
5621,88,Kiang,O
5622,88,is,O
5623,88,a,O
5624,88,great,O
5625,88,host,O
5626,88,.,O
5627,88,They,O
5628,88,are,O
5629,88,flexible,O
5630,88,and,O
5631,88,easy,O
5632,88,to,O
5633,88,contact,O
5634,88,.,O
5635,88,The,O
5636,88,room,O
5637,88,is,O
5638,88,a,O
5639,88,little,O
5640,88,bit,O
5641,88,small,O
5642,88,for,O
5643,88,me,O
5644,88,because,O
5645,88,I,O
5646,88,have,O
5647,88,a,O
5648,88,big,O
5649,88,luggage,O
5650,88,.,O
5651,88,However,O
5652,88,",",O
5653,88,if,O
5654,88,you,O
5655,88,re,O
5656,88,a,O
5657,88,light,O
5658,88,traveler,O
5659,88,",",O
5660,88,it,O
5661,88,would,O
5662,88,be,O
5663,88,comfortable,O
5664,88,.,O
5665,88,The,O
5666,88,location,O
5667,88,is,O
5668,88,strategic,O
5669,88,",",O
5670,88,there,O
5671,88,s,O
5672,88,bustop,O
5673,88,outside,O
5674,88,the,O
5675,88,condo,O
5676,88,and,O
5677,88,direct,O
5678,88,bus,O
5679,88,to,O
5680,88,Orchard,B-geo
5681,88,and,O
5682,88,other,O
5683,88,parts,O
5684,88,of,O
5685,88,Singapore,B-geo
5686,88,.,O
5687,88,Tiong,B-geo
5688,88,Bahru,I-geo
5689,88,is,O
5690,88,a,O
5691,88,few,O
5692,88,bus,O
5693,88,stops,O
5694,88,away,O
5695,88,too,O
5696,88,or,O
5697,88,you,O
5698,88,can,O
5699,88,walk,O
5700,88,if,O
5701,88,you,O
5702,88,want,O
5703,88,.,O
5704,88,The,O
5705,88,room,O
5706,88,is,O
5707,88,clean,O
5708,88,and,O
5709,88,the,O
5710,88,I,O
5711,88,love,O
5712,88,the,O
5713,88,mattress,O
5714,88,because,O
5715,88,it,O
5716,88,s,O
5717,88,firm,O
5718,88,.,O
5719,89,Fantastic,O
5720,89,location,O
5721,89,we,O
5722,89,loved,O
5723,89,how,O
5724,89,close,O
5725,89,Holland,B-geo
5726,89,Village,I-geo
5727,89,was,O
5728,89,.,O
5729,89,Communication,O
5730,89,excellent,O
5731,89,and,O
5732,89,so,O
5733,89,helpful,O
5734,89,.,O
5735,89,As,O
5736,89,a,O
5737,89,few,O
5738,89,reviews,O
5739,89,mentioned,O
5740,89,",",O
5741,89,the,O
5742,89,apartment,O
5743,89,is,O
5744,89,a,O
5745,89,little,O
5746,89,older,O
5747,89,dated,O
5748,89,but,O
5749,89,it,O
5750,89,was,O
5751,89,everything,O
5752,89,we,O
5753,89,needed,O
5754,89,and,O
5755,89,was,O
5756,89,perfect,O
5757,89,for,O
5758,89,our,O
5759,89,stay,O
5760,89,.,O
5761,89,Thank,O
5762,89,you,O
5763,89,Sue,O
5764,90,The,O
5765,90,house,O
5766,90,is,O
5767,90,clean,O
5768,90,and,O
5769,90,neat,O
5770,90,",",O
5771,90,close,O
5772,90,to,O
5773,90,Chinatown,B-gpe
5774,90,",",O
5775,90,there,O
5776,90,is,O
5777,90,a,O
5778,90,bus,O
5779,90,stop,O
5780,90,at,O
5781,90,the,O
5782,90,door,O
5783,90,.,O
5784,90,It,O
5785,90,is,O
5786,90,also,O
5787,90,very,O
5788,90,close,O
5789,90,to,O
5790,90,the,O
5791,90,subway,O
5792,90,.,O
5793,90,It,O
5794,90,is,O
5795,90,convenient,O
5796,90,.,O
5797,90,The,O
5798,90,staff,O
5799,90,is,O
5800,90,24,O
5801,90,hours,O
5802,90,off,O
5803,90,duty,O
5804,90,",",O
5805,90,the,O
5806,90,service,O
5807,90,is,O
5808,90,warm,O
5809,90,and,O
5810,90,patient,O
5811,90,",",O
5812,90,must,O
5813,90,be,O
5814,90,praised,O
5815,90,for,O
5816,90,him,O
5817,90,she,O
5818,90,The,O
5819,90,only,O
5820,90,shortcomings,O
5821,90,are,O
5822,90,required,O
5823,90,to,O
5824,90,fill,O
5825,90,in,O
5826,90,another,O
5827,90,website,O
5828,90,after,O
5829,90,filling,O
5830,90,in,O
5831,90,the,O
5832,90,information,O
5833,90,on,O
5834,90,aiRBNB,B-org
5835,90,",",O
5836,90,otherwise,O
5837,90,unable,O
5838,90,to,O
5839,90,stay,O
5840,90,.,O
5841,90,In,O
5842,90,China,B-geo
5843,90,",",O
5844,90,it,O
5845,90,is,O
5846,90,not,O
5847,90,successful,O
5848,90,",",O
5849,90,and,O
5850,90,finally,O
5851,90,",",O
5852,90,I,O
5853,90,finally,O
5854,90,gotten,O
5855,90,the,O
5856,90,scene,O
5857,90,after,O
5858,90,the,O
5859,90,help,O
5860,90,of,O
5861,90,the,O
5862,90,staff,O
5863,90,.,O
5864,90,I,O
5865,90,finally,O
5866,90,achieved,O
5867,90,it,O
5868,90,.,O
5869,90,Room,O
5870,90,password,O
5871,90,.,O
5872,90,Very,O
5873,90,influential,O
5874,90,",",O
5875,90,I,O
5876,90,hope,O
5877,90,the,O
5878,90,landlord,O
5879,90,can,O
5880,90,simplify,O
5881,90,check,O
5882,90,in,O
5883,90,procedures,O
5884,91,Very,O
5885,91,nice,O
5886,91,apartment,O
5887,91,",",O
5888,91,very,O
5889,91,well,O
5890,91,located,O
5891,91,in,O
5892,91,Chinatown,B-gpe
5893,91,",",O
5894,91,clean,O
5895,91,and,O
5896,91,big,O
5897,91,.,O
5898,91,we,O
5899,91,recommend,O
5900,91,it,O
5901,92,The,O
5902,92,apartment,O
5903,92,fulfills,O
5904,92,the,O
5905,92,expectations,O
5906,92,.,O
5907,92,The,O
5908,92,situation,O
5909,92,is,O
5910,92,very,O
5911,92,good,O
5912,92,",",O
5913,92,since,O
5914,92,you,O
5915,92,can,O
5916,92,walk,O
5917,92,to,O
5918,92,the,O
5919,92,Indian,B-gpe
5920,92,neighborhood,O
5921,92,and,O
5922,92,Arab,B-geo
5923,92,.,O
5924,92,Orchard,B-geo
5925,92,Street,I-geo
5926,92,and,O
5927,92,the,O
5928,92,Colonial,B-geo
5929,92,District,I-geo
5930,92,",",O
5931,92,although,O
5932,92,something,O
5933,92,more,O
5934,92,distant,O
5935,92,",",O
5936,92,are,O
5937,92,also,O
5938,92,at,O
5939,92,a,O
5940,92,distance,O
5941,92,to,O
5942,92,walk,O
5943,92,.,O
5944,92,Is,O
5945,92,opposite,O
5946,92,Sim,B-org
5947,92,Lim,I-org
5948,92,Square,I-org
5949,92,and,O
5950,92,in,O
5951,92,the,O
5952,92,neighborhood,O
5953,92,of,O
5954,92,Bugis,B-geo
5955,93,That,O
5956,93,Green,O
5957,93,Corner,O
5958,93,is,O
5959,93,one,O
5960,93,of,O
5961,93,the,O
5962,93,best,O
5963,93,unit,O
5964,93,available,O
5965,93,for,O
5966,93,travellers,O
5967,93,.,O
5968,93,the,O
5969,93,location,O
5970,93,is,O
5971,93,great,O
5972,93,",",O
5973,93,within,O
5974,93,walking,O
5975,93,distance,O
5976,93,to,O
5977,93,THREE,O
5978,93,MRT,O
5979,93,stations,O
5980,93,",",O
5981,93,with,O
5982,93,direct,O
5983,93,bus,O
5984,93,ride,O
5985,93,to,O
5986,93,Newton,B-geo
5987,93,Food,O
5988,93,Circle,O
5989,93,",",O
5990,93,City,B-gpe
5991,93,Hall,I-gpe
5992,93,",",O
5993,93,Dhoby,B-geo
5994,93,Ghaut,I-geo
5995,93,",",O
5996,93,and,O
5997,93,also,O
5998,93,walking,O
5999,93,distance,O
6000,93,to,O
6001,93,Bugis,B-geo
6002,93,the,O
6003,93,place,O
6004,93,is,O
6005,93,quiet,O
6006,93,",",O
6007,93,clean,O
6008,93,",",O
6009,93,tidy,O
6010,93,",",O
6011,93,and,O
6012,93,homey,O
6013,93,",",O
6014,93,you,O
6015,93,feel,O
6016,93,like,O
6017,93,staying,O
6018,93,at,O
6019,93,your,O
6020,93,own,O
6021,93,place,O
6022,93,.,O
6023,93,the,O
6024,93,host,O
6025,93,are,O
6026,93,nice,O
6027,93,and,O
6028,93,pleasant,O
6029,93,I,O
6030,93,really,O
6031,93,appreciate,O
6032,93,their,O
6033,93,hospitality,O
6034,93,and,O
6035,93,look,O
6036,93,forward,O
6037,93,to,O
6038,93,return,O
6039,93,on,O
6040,93,my,O
6041,93,next,O
6042,93,visit,O
6043,94,The,O
6044,94,room,O
6045,94,was,O
6046,94,great,O
6047,94,for,O
6048,94,what,O
6049,94,we,O
6050,94,needed,O
6051,94,Definitely,O
6052,94,a,O
6053,94,tight,O
6054,94,squeeze,O
6055,94,for,O
6056,94,two,O
6057,94,",",O
6058,94,but,O
6059,94,very,O
6060,94,clean,O
6061,94,and,O
6062,94,all,O
6063,94,amenities,O
6064,94,available,O
6065,94,.,O
6066,94,Location,O
6067,94,was,O
6068,94,easy,O
6069,94,to,O
6070,94,get,O
6071,94,to,O
6072,94,from,O
6073,94,the,O
6074,94,airport,O
6075,94,and,O
6076,94,a,O
6077,94,quick,O
6078,94,walk,O
6079,94,to,O
6080,94,Little,B-gpe
6081,94,India,I-gpe
6082,94,and,O
6083,94,Haji,B-geo
6084,94,Lane,I-geo
6085,94,.,O
6086,94,So,O
6087,94,close,O
6088,94,to,O
6089,94,the,O
6090,94,MRT,O
6091,94,station,O
6092,94,so,O
6093,94,it,O
6094,94,was,O
6095,94,easy,O
6096,94,to,O
6097,94,hop,O
6098,94,on,O
6099,94,and,O
6100,94,get,O
6101,94,wherever,O
6102,94,we,O
6103,94,wanted,O
6104,94,to,O
6105,94,go,O
6106,94,.,O
6107,94,Didn,O
6108,94,t,O
6109,94,spend,O
6110,94,too,O
6111,94,much,O
6112,94,time,O
6113,94,in,O
6114,94,the,O
6115,94,Airbnb,B-org
6116,94,as,O
6117,94,we,O
6118,94,were,O
6119,94,out,O
6120,94,and,O
6121,94,about,O
6122,94,most,O
6123,94,of,O
6124,94,the,O
6125,94,time,O
6126,94,.,O
6127,95,Location,O
6128,95,is,O
6129,95,excellent,O
6130,95,in,O
6131,95,front,O
6132,95,of,O
6133,95,Marina,B-org
6134,95,Bay,I-org
6134,95,Sands,I-org
6135,95,and,O
6136,95,nearby,O
6137,95,Downtown,B-geo
6138,95,metro,O
6139,95,station,O
6140,95,.,O
6141,96,Cozy,O
6142,96,little,O
6143,96,apartment,O
6144,96,in,O
6145,96,a,O
6146,96,fantastic,O
6147,96,location,O
6148,96,with,O
6149,96,many,O
6150,96,restaurants,O
6151,96,and,O
6152,96,bars,O
6153,96,just,O
6154,96,out,O
6155,96,the,O
6156,96,front,O
6157,96,door,O
6158,96,and,O
6159,96,a,O
6160,96,short,O
6161,96,walk,O
6162,96,to,O
6163,96,Chinatown,B-gpe
6164,96,.,O
6165,96,Off,O
6166,96,the,O
6167,96,street,O
6168,96,so,O
6169,96,none,O
6170,96,of,O
6171,96,the,O
6172,96,noise,O
6173,96,from,O
6174,96,nearby,O
6175,96,places,O
6176,96,although,O
6177,96,the,O
6178,96,aircon,O
6179,96,units,O
6180,96,outside,O
6181,96,can,O
6182,96,make,O
6183,96,some,O
6184,96,noise,O
6185,96,.,O
6186,97,This,O
6187,97,hotel,O
6188,97,listing,O
6189,97,was,O
6190,97,spotless,O
6191,97,and,O
6192,97,very,O
6193,97,pleasant,O
6194,97,.,O
6195,97,It,O
6196,97,is,O
6197,97,located,O
6198,97,in,O
