,num,sentence,tag
0,1,You,O
1,1,can,O
2,1,walk,O
3,1,to,O
4,1,the,O
5,1,Orchard,B-geo
6,1,",",O
7,1,Clarke,B-geo
8,1,Quay,I-geo
9,1,and,O
10,1,lots,O
11,1,of,O
12,1,restaurants,O
13,1,.,O
14,1,Receptionist,O
15,1,helps,O
16,1,you,O
17,1,for,O
18,1,24,B-tim
19,1,hours,I-tim
20,1,and,O
21,1,was,O
22,1,very,O
23,1,helpful,O
24,1,.,O
25,2,This,O
26,2,hotel,O
27,2,is,O
28,2,very,O
29,2,clean,O
30,2,and,O
31,2,in,O
32,2,an,O
33,2,excellent,O
34,2,location,O
35,2,in,O
36,2,the,O
37,2,heart,O
38,2,of,O
39,2,Chinatown,B-gpe
40,2,.,O
41,2,The,O
42,2,staff,O
43,2,are,O
44,2,very,O
45,2,friendly,O
46,2,and,O
47,2,helpful,O
48,2,.,O
49,2,The,O
50,2,only,O
51,2,issue,O
52,2,I,O
53,2,had,O
54,2,was,O
55,2,the,O
56,2,room,O
57,2,I,O
58,2,was,O
59,2,given,O
60,2,was,O
61,2,smaller,O
62,2,than,O
63,2,I,O
64,2,had,O
65,2,understood,O
66,2,from,O
67,2,the,O
68,2,photos,O
69,2,and,O
70,2,had,O
71,2,no,O
72,2,windows,O
73,2,which,O
74,2,would,O
75,2,be,O
76,2,okay,O
77,2,for,O
78,2,me,O
79,2,for,O
80,2,1,O
81,2,2,O
82,2,nights,O
83,2,but,O
84,2,not,O
85,2,longer,O
86,2,.,O
87,2,I,O
88,2,had,O
89,2,originally,O
90,2,booked,O
91,2,7,O
92,2,nights,O
93,2,but,O
94,2,only,O
95,2,stayed,O
96,2,1,O
97,2,night,O
98,2,.,O
99,3,I,O
100,3,stayed,O
101,3,at,O
102,3,Heritage,B-org
103,3,Apertments,I-org
104,3,Chinatown,I-org
105,3,.,O
106,3,The,O
107,3,unit,O
108,3,was,O
109,3,small,O
110,3,but,O
111,3,had,O
112,3,everything,O
113,3,I,O
114,3,needed,O
115,3,.,O
116,3,It,O
117,3,was,O
118,3,also,O
119,3,within,O
120,3,walking,O
121,3,distance,O
122,3,of,O
123,3,the,O
124,3,Chinatown,B-gpe
125,3,CBD,O
126,3,and,O
127,3,many,O
128,3,tourist,O
129,3,places,O
130,3,in,O
131,3,Chinatown,B-gpe
132,3,.,O
133,3,The,O
134,3,host,O
135,3,Mary,B-per
136,3,was,O
137,3,very,O
138,3,helpful,O
139,3,and,O
140,3,easy,O
141,3,to,O
142,3,communicate,O
143,3,with,O
144,3,.,O
145,4,The,O
146,4,home,O
147,4,is,O
148,4,about,O
149,4,10,B-tim
150,4,minutes,I-tim
151,4,from,O
152,4,the,O
153,4,Bugis,B-geo
154,4,Metro,O
155,4,",",O
156,4,but,O
157,4,there,O
158,4,will,O
159,4,be,O
160,4,a,O
161,4,new,O
162,4,place,O
163,4,to,O
164,4,export,O
165,4,",",O
166,4,and,O
167,4,the,O
168,4,line,O
169,4,will,O
170,4,arrive,O
171,4,in,O
172,4,the,O
173,4,past,O
174,4,1,B-tim
175,4,minute,I-tim
176,4,",",O
177,4,but,O
178,4,it,O
179,4,has,O
180,4,not,O
181,4,been,O
182,4,opened,O
183,4,when,O
184,4,I,O
185,4,live,O
186,4,.,O
187,4,I,O
188,4,am,O
189,4,a,O
190,4,vegetarian,O
191,4,",",O
192,4,living,O
193,4,here,O
194,4,is,O
195,4,super,O
196,4,convenient,O
197,4,",",O
198,4,traveling,O
199,4,a,O
200,4,Fortune,O
201,4,Center,O
202,4,for,O
203,4,about,O
204,4,5,O
205,4,minutes,O
206,4,",",O
207,4,there,O
208,4,are,O
209,4,about,O
210,4,more,O
211,4,than,O
212,4,10,O
213,4,different,O
214,4,vegetarian,O
215,4,restaurants,O
216,4,inside,O
217,4,.,O
218,4,Awes,O
219,4,The,O
220,4,landlord,O
221,4,is,O
222,4,also,O
223,4,very,O
224,4,happy,O
225,4,to,O
226,4,introduce,O
227,4,the,O
228,4,nearby,O
229,4,tourist,O
230,4,attractions,O
231,4,to,O
232,4,me,O
233,4,",",O
234,4,there,O
235,4,is,O
236,4,a,O
237,4,problem,O
238,4,asking,O
239,4,for,O
240,4,a,O
241,4,quick,O
242,4,reply,O
243,4,It,O
244,4,is,O
245,4,worth,O
246,4,recommending,O
247,4,to,O
248,4,everyone,O
249,4,Especially,O
250,4,vegetarians,O
251,5,Wonderful,O
252,5,place,O
253,5,Sue,B-per
254,5,is,O
255,5,very,O
256,5,quick,O
257,5,and,O
258,5,responsive,O
259,5,",",O
260,5,as,O
261,5,is,O
262,5,Virginy,O
263,5,.,O
264,5,The,O
265,5,house,O
266,5,is,O
267,5,clean,O
268,5,and,O
269,5,super,O
270,5,close,O
271,5,to,O
272,5,the,O
273,5,bus,O
274,5,stop,O
275,5,multiple,O
276,5,bus,O
277,5,lines,O
278,5,that,O
279,5,take,O
280,5,you,O
281,5,downtown,O
282,5,",",O
283,5,MRT,O
284,5,",",O
285,5,Botanic,B-geo
286,5,Gardens,I-geo
287,5,",",O
288,5,etc,O
289,5,.,O
290,5,",",O
291,5,and,O
292,5,the,O
293,5,Jelita,O
294,5,Cold,B-org
295,5,Storage,I-org
296,5,Supermarket,O
297,5,open,O
298,5,24,O
299,5,7,O
300,5,",",O
301,5,btw,O
302,5,.,O
303,5,The,O
304,5,Jelita,O
305,5,Cold,B-org
306,5,Storage,I-org
307,5,also,O
308,5,houses,O
309,5,a,O
310,5,medical,O
311,5,clinic,O
312,5,",",O
313,5,in,O
314,5,case,O
315,5,you,O
316,5,get,O
317,5,sick,O
318,5,.,O
319,5,Very,O
320,5,safe,O
321,5,and,O
322,5,quiet,O
323,5,neighborhood,O
324,5,.,O
325,5,I,O
326,5,really,O
327,5,have,O
328,5,no,O
329,5,complaints,O
330,6,The,O
331,6,place,O
332,6,was,O
333,6,great,O
334,6,",",O
335,6,well,O
336,6,set,O
337,6,up,O
338,6,in,O
339,6,a,O
340,6,convenient,O
341,6,location,O
342,6,near,O
343,6,Orchard,B-geo
344,6,shopping,O
345,6,malls,O
346,6,to,O
347,6,the,O
348,6,north,O
349,6,",",O
350,6,with,O
351,6,parks,O
352,6,and,O
353,6,some,O
354,6,stylish,O
355,6,cafes,O
356,6,to,O
357,6,the,O
358,6,south,O
359,6,.,O
360,6,Vanessa,B-per
361,6,was,O
362,6,helpful,O
363,6,and,O
364,6,responded,O
365,6,quickly,O
366,6,.,O
367,6,Really,O
368,6,enjoyed,O
369,6,my,O
370,6,stay,O
371,6,here,O
372,6,.,O
373,7,Alex,B-per
374,7,is,O
375,7,place,O
376,7,was,O
377,7,absolutely,O
378,7,fantastic,O
379,7,.,O
380,7,Looked,O
381,7,exactly,O
382,7,as,O
383,7,it,O
384,7,did,O
385,7,in,O
386,7,the,O
387,7,photos,O
388,7,",",O
389,7,clean,O
390,7,",",O
391,7,and,O
392,7,was,O
393,7,in,O
394,7,a,O
395,7,perfect,O
396,7,location,O
397,7,across,O
398,7,the,O
399,7,street,O
400,7,from,O
401,7,the,O
402,7,Chinatown,B-gpe
403,7,MRT,O
404,7,stop,O
405,7,.,O
406,7,Thanks,O
407,7,again,O
408,7,Alex,B-per
409,8,Location,O
410,8,can,O
411,8,t,O
412,8,be,O
413,8,beat,O
414,8,10,B-tim
415,8,mins,I-tim
416,8,from,O
417,8,Little,B-gpe
418,8,India,I-gpe
419,8,.,O
420,8,Highly,O
421,8,recommend,O
422,8,.,O
423,9,Great,O
424,9,place,O
425,9,to,O
426,9,stay,O
427,9,for,O
428,9,full,O
429,9,autonomy,O
430,9,Fantastic,O
431,9,location,O
432,9,2,B-tim
433,9,minute,I-tim
434,9,walk,O
435,9,to,O
436,9,MRT,O
437,9,station,O
438,9,",",O
439,9,across,O
440,9,the,O
441,9,road,O
442,9,from,O
443,9,Chinatown,B-org
444,9,Point,I-org
445,9,Mall,I-org
446,9,",",O
447,9,5,O
448,9,minute,O
449,9,walk,O
450,9,from,O
451,9,Chinatown,B-org
452,9,Street,I-org
453,9,Food,I-org
454,9,.,O
455,9,Apartment,O
456,9,has,O
457,9,the,O
458,9,bare,O
459,9,essentials,O
460,9,",",O
461,9,if,O
462,9,you,O
463,9,plan,O
464,9,on,O
465,9,cooking,O
466,9,your,O
467,9,own,O
468,9,food,O
469,9,",",O
470,9,you,O
471,9,will,O
472,9,need,O
473,9,to,O
474,9,stock,O
475,9,up,O
476,9,on,O
477,9,the,O
478,9,basics,O
479,9,.,O
480,9,.,O
481,9,.,O
482,9,But,O
483,9,you,O
484,9,are,O
485,9,5,B-tim
486,9,minutes,I-tim
487,9,away,O
488,9,from,O
489,9,some,O
490,9,of,O
491,9,the,O
492,9,best,O
493,9,Chinese,B-gpe
494,9,food,O
495,9,Had,O
496,9,an,O
497,9,amazing,O
498,9,time,O
499,9,in,O
500,9,Singapore,B-geo
501,9,",",O
502,9,and,O
503,9,staying,O
504,9,at,O
505,9,Alex,B-per
506,9,is,O
507,9,apartment,O
508,9,definitely,O
509,9,contributed,O
510,9,to,O
511,9,that,O
512,9,.,O
513,10,Quick,O
514,10,responses,O
515,10,",",O
516,10,very,O
517,10,nice,O
518,10,and,O
519,10,friendly,O
520,10,host,O
521,10,via,O
522,10,message,O
523,10,exchange,O
524,10,.,O
525,10,Apartment,O
526,10,is,O
527,10,clean,O
528,10,.,O
529,10,Easy,O
530,10,Check,O
531,10,in,O
532,10,with,O
533,10,the,O
534,10,apartment,O
535,10,unlocked,O
536,10,waiting,O
537,10,for,O
538,10,your,O
539,10,arrival,O
540,10,.,O
541,10,Space,O
542,10,is,O
543,10,spacious,O
544,10,and,O
545,10,large,O
546,10,enough,O
547,10,as,O
548,10,described,O
549,10,.,O
550,10,Location,O
551,10,is,O
552,10,right,O
553,10,in,O
554,10,the,O
555,10,heart,O
556,10,of,O
557,10,Chinatown,B-gpe
558,10,.,O
559,10,We,O
560,10,have,O
561,10,a,O
562,10,great,O
563,10,stay,O
564,10,Thank,O
565,10,you,O
566,10,very,O
567,10,much,O
568,10,.,O
569,11,The,O
570,11,place,O
571,11,has,O
572,11,a,O
573,11,great,O
574,11,location,O
575,11,",",O
576,11,close,O
577,11,to,O
578,11,Marina,B-geo
579,11,Bay,I-geo
580,11,by,O
581,11,train,O
582,11,and,O
583,11,to,O
584,11,shopping,O
585,11,malls,O
586,11,",",O
587,11,restaurants,O
588,11,and,O
589,11,supermarket,O
590,11,by,O
591,11,foot,O
592,11,.,O
593,11,Anna,B-per
594,11,is,O
595,11,very,O
596,11,friendly,O
597,11,and,O
598,11,gives,O
599,11,recommendations,O
600,11,about,O
601,11,what,O
602,11,to,O
603,11,do,O
604,11,",",O
605,11,to,O
606,11,visit,O
607,11,and,O
608,11,to,O
609,11,eat,O
610,11,in,O
611,11,Singapore,B-geo
612,11,.,O
613,11,The,O
614,11,place,O
615,11,is,O
616,11,convenient,O
617,11,if,O
618,11,your,O
619,11,plans,O
620,11,are,O
621,11,to,O
622,11,stay,O
623,11,outside,O
624,11,during,O
625,11,the,O
626,11,day,O
627,11,and,O
628,11,come,O
629,11,just,O
630,11,to,O
631,11,shower,O
632,11,",",O
633,11,sleep,O
634,11,and,O
635,11,have,O
636,11,breakfast,O
637,11,.,O
638,11,Anna,B-per
639,11,also,O
640,11,let,O
641,11,me,O
642,11,use,O
643,11,the,O
644,11,washing,O
645,11,machine,O
646,11,",",O
647,11,and,O
648,11,the,O
649,11,laundry,O
650,11,dries,O
651,11,the,O
652,11,same,O
653,11,day,O
654,11,thanks,O
655,11,to,O
656,11,the,O
657,11,Singaporean,B-gpe
658,11,weather,O
659,11,.,O
660,12,Good,O
661,12,16,O
662,12,bed,O
663,12,room,O
664,12,hostel,O
665,12,in,O
666,12,the,O
667,12,heart,O
668,12,of,O
669,12,Chinatown,B-gpe
670,12,downtown,O
671,12,.,O
672,12,Thanks,O
673,12,for,O
674,12,the,O
675,12,stay,O
676,12,.,O
677,13,Staying,O
678,13,at,O
679,13,Sue,B-per
680,13,is,O
681,13,was,O
682,13,great,O
683,13,.,O
684,13,The,O
685,13,house,O
686,13,is,O
687,13,located,O
688,13,nearby,O
689,13,Holland,B-geo
690,13,Village,I-geo
691,13,.,O
692,13,The,O
693,13,room,O
694,13,was,O
695,13,very,O
696,13,neat,O
697,13,",",O
698,13,quiet,O
699,13,",",O
700,13,and,O
701,13,very,O
702,13,hospitable,O
703,13,.,O
704,14,The,O
705,14,perfect,O
706,14,studio,O
707,14,for,O
708,14,two,O
709,14,people,O
710,14,wanting,O
711,14,a,O
712,14,central,O
713,14,space,O
714,14,to,O
715,14,stay,O
716,14,during,O
717,14,an,O
718,14,activity,O
719,14,packed,O
720,14,time,O
721,14,in,O
722,14,SG,B-geo
723,14,Easy,O
724,14,check,O
725,14,in,O
726,14,available,O
727,14,24,O
728,14,7,O
729,14,",",O
730,14,as,O
731,14,well,O
732,14,as,O
733,14,plenty,O
734,14,of,O
735,14,amenities,O
736,14,.,O
737,14,A,O
738,14,short,O
739,14,walk,O
740,14,to,O
741,14,Little,B-gpe
742,14,India,I-gpe
743,14,and,O
744,14,Dhoby,B-geo
745,14,Ghaut,I-geo
746,14,MRT,O
747,14,stations,O
748,14,.,O
749,14,Would,O
750,14,recommend,O
751,15,Hands,O
752,15,down,O
753,15,the,O
754,15,best,O
755,15,Airbnb,B-org
756,15,stay,O
757,15,I,O
758,15,have,O
759,15,had,O
760,15,so,O
761,15,far,O
762,15,.,O
763,15,The,O
764,15,apartment,O
765,15,was,O
766,15,clean,O
767,15,with,O
768,15,fresh,O
769,15,bedsheets,O
770,15,when,O
771,15,we,O
772,15,arrived,O
773,15,.,O
774,15,The,O
775,15,check,O
776,15,in,O
777,15,process,O
778,15,was,O
779,15,really,O
780,15,easy,O
781,15,and,O
782,15,hassle,O
783,15,free,O
784,15,using,O
785,15,a,O
786,15,digital,O
787,15,lock,O
788,15,.,O
789,15,It,O
790,15,is,O
791,15,located,O
792,15,in,O
793,15,a,O
794,15,good,O
795,15,area,O
796,15,where,O
797,15,we,O
798,15,can,O
799,15,easily,O
800,15,reach,O
801,15,Changi,B-org
802,15,airport,I-org
803,15,",",O
804,15,Orchard,B-geo
805,15,road,I-geo
806,15,and,O
807,15,other,O
808,15,touristy,O
809,15,places,O
810,15,.,O
811,15,Mr,O
812,15,.,O
813,15,J,O
814,15,was,O
815,15,also,O
816,15,very,O
817,15,thoughtful,O
818,15,",",O
819,15,there,O
820,15,were,O
821,15,extra,O
822,15,pillows,O
823,15,",",O
824,15,plenty,O
825,15,tissue,O
826,15,rolls,O
827,15,",",O
828,15,iron,O
829,15,",",O
830,15,hairdryer,O
831,15,",",O
832,15,cooking,O
833,15,and,O
834,15,eating,O
835,15,utensils,O
836,15,perfect,O
837,15,for,O
838,15,a,O
839,15,family,O
840,15,trip,O
841,15,Keep,O
842,15,up,O
843,15,the,O
844,15,good,O
845,15,work,O
846,16,We,O
847,16,liked,O
848,16,it,O
849,16,a,O
850,16,lot,O
851,16,to,O
852,16,stay,O
853,16,in,O
854,16,Stephanie,B-per
855,16,.,O
856,16,She,O
857,16,has,O
858,16,a,O
859,16,beautiful,O
860,16,apartment,O
861,16,in,O
862,16,a,O
863,16,well,O
864,16,located,O
865,16,place,O
866,16,of,O
867,16,Singapore,B-geo
868,16,.,O
869,16,Two,O
870,16,metro,O
871,16,stations,O
872,16,from,O
873,16,the,O
874,16,center,O
875,16,",",O
876,16,near,O
877,16,the,O
878,16,picturesque,O
879,16,neighborhood,O
880,16,of,O
881,16,Little,B-gpe
882,16,India,I-gpe
883,16,and,O
884,16,Arab,B-gpe
885,16,Street,I-gpe
886,16,.,O
887,16,Stephanie,B-per
888,16,is,O
889,16,lovely,O
890,16,and,O
891,16,was,O
892,16,present,O
893,16,for,O
894,16,everything,O
895,16,we,O
896,16,need,O
897,16,.,O
898,16,She,O
899,16,has,O
900,16,a,O
901,16,very,O
902,16,cheerful,O
903,16,puppy,O
904,16,",",O
905,16,Pippy,O
906,16,.,O
907,16,The,O
908,16,only,O
909,16,detail,O
910,16,is,O
911,16,that,O
912,16,there,O
913,16,was,O
914,16,no,O
915,16,WiFi,O
916,16,in,O
917,16,the,O
918,16,room,O
919,16,",",O
920,16,but,O
921,16,if,O
922,16,it,O
923,16,worked,O
924,16,in,O
925,16,the,O
926,16,living,O
927,16,room,O
928,16,.,O
929,16,Highly,O
930,16,recommended,O
931,17,Modern,O
932,17,",",O
933,17,clean,O
934,17,",",O
935,17,comfortable,O
936,17,apartment,O
937,17,.,O
938,17,Great,O
939,17,pool,O
940,17,.,O
941,17,Front,O
942,17,desk,O
943,17,was,O
944,17,very,O
945,17,helpful,O
946,17,",",O
947,17,with,O
948,17,questions,O
949,17,and,O
950,17,needs,O
951,17,.,O
952,17,Centrally,O
953,17,located,O
954,17,a,O
955,17,short,O
956,17,Grab,B-org
957,17,or,O
958,17,taxi,O
959,17,ride,O
960,17,to,O
961,17,many,O
962,17,attractions,O
963,17,CBD,O
964,17,",",O
965,17,Marina,B-geo
966,17,Bay,I-geo
967,17,",",O
968,17,Chinatown,B-gpe
969,17,",",O
970,17,Sentosa,B-geo
971,17,.,O
972,17,7,B-tim
973,17,minute,I-tim
974,17,walk,O
975,17,to,O
976,17,supermarket,O
977,17,.,O
978,17,20,B-tim
979,17,minutes,I-tim
980,17,to,O
981,17,Orchard,B-geo
982,17,Road,I-geo
983,17,.,O
984,17,Our,O
985,17,family,O
986,17,really,O
987,17,enjoyed,O
988,17,our,O
989,17,stay,O
990,17,.,O
991,17,Thank,O
992,17,you,O
993,18,Excellent,O
994,18,apartment,O
995,18,located,O
996,18,centrally,O
997,18,next,O
998,18,to,O
999,18,Chinatown,B-gpe
1000,18,",",O
1001,18,just,O
1002,18,above,O
1003,18,the,O
1004,18,MRT,O
1005,18,station,O
1006,18,.,O
1007,18,We,O
1008,18,were,O
1009,18,four,O
1010,18,staying,O
1011,18,which,O
1012,18,was,O
1013,18,great,O
1014,18,since,O
1015,18,we,O
1016,18,were,O
1017,18,only,O
1018,18,sleeping,O
1019,18,there,O
1020,18,",",O
1021,18,but,O
1022,18,if,O
1023,18,you,O
1024,18,plan,O
1025,18,to,O
1026,18,be,O
1027,18,four,O
1028,18,for,O
1029,18,longer,O
1030,18,periods,O
1031,18,it,O
1032,18,may,O
1033,18,feel,O
1034,18,a,O
1035,18,little,O
1036,18,bit,O
1037,18,packed,O
1038,18,.,O
1039,18,The,O
1040,18,pool,O
1041,18,is,O
1042,18,fantastic,O
1043,18,and,O
1044,18,gives,O
1045,18,an,O
1046,18,opportunity,O
1047,18,for,O
1048,18,refreshment,O
1049,18,in,O
1050,18,a,O
1051,18,very,O
1052,18,warm,O
1053,18,Singapore,B-geo
1054,18,.,O
1055,18,Kelvin,B-per
1056,18,was,O
1057,18,ready,O
1058,18,to,O
1059,18,answer,O
1060,18,very,O
1061,18,fast,O
1062,18,Thanks,O
1063,18,for,O
1064,18,that,O
1065,18,Would,O
1066,18,definitely,O
1067,18,stay,O
1068,18,here,O
1069,18,again,O
1070,19,Very,O
1071,19,convenient,O
1072,19,location,O
1073,19,.,O
1074,19,Chinatown,B-gpe
1075,19,station,O
1076,19,is,O
1077,19,right,O
1078,19,there,O
1079,19,",",O
1080,19,and,O
1081,19,we,O
1082,19,lived,O
1083,19,literally,O
1084,19,above,O
1085,19,great,O
1086,19,food,O
1087,19,options,O
1088,19,.,O
1089,19,apartment,O
1090,19,was,O
1091,19,well,O
1092,19,furnished,O
1093,19,and,O
1094,19,in,O
1095,19,good,O
1096,19,condition,O
1097,19,",",O
1098,19,very,O
1099,19,spacious,O
1100,19,for,O
1101,19,a,O
1102,19,Singaporean,B-gpe
1103,19,apartment,O
1104,19,and,O
1105,19,we,O
1106,19,were,O
1107,19,comfortable,O
1108,19,to,O
1109,19,stay,O
1110,19,there,O
1111,19,.,O
1112,19,Also,O
1113,19,walking,O
1114,19,distance,O
1115,19,from,O
1116,19,great,O
1117,19,Clark,B-geo
1118,19,Quay,I-geo
1119,19,area,O
1120,19,for,O
1121,19,good,O
1122,19,bars,O
1123,19,and,O
1124,19,restaurants,O
1125,19,.,O
1126,20,Very,O
1127,20,well,O
1128,20,equipped,O
1129,20,room,O
1130,20,Apple,B-org
1131,20,TV,O
1132,20,",",O
1133,20,toaster,O
1134,20,",",O
1135,20,plates,O
1136,20,",",O
1137,20,etc,O
1138,20,.,O
1139,20,.,O
1140,20,Comes,O
1141,20,with,O
1142,20,you,O
1143,20,own,O
1144,20,bathroom,O
1145,20,and,O
1146,20,washer,O
1147,20,dryers,O
1148,20,.,O
1149,20,Conveniently,O
1150,20,located,O
1151,20,a,O
1152,20,couple,O
1153,20,blocks,O
1154,20,away,O
1155,20,from,O
1156,20,Chinatown,B-gpe
1157,20,MRT,O
1158,20,.,O
1159,20,All,O
1160,20,in,O
1161,20,all,O
1162,20,a,O
1163,20,very,O
1164,20,nice,O
1165,20,place,O
1166,20,to,O
1167,20,spend,O
1168,20,sometime,O
1169,20,in,O
1170,20,Singapore,B-gpe
1171,20,",",O
1172,20,though,O
1173,20,the,O
1174,20,ventilation,O
1175,20,is,O
1176,20,not,O
1177,20,very,O
1178,20,well,O
1179,20,and,O
1180,20,some,O
1181,20,other,O
1182,20,guests,O
1183,20,were,O
1184,20,doing,O
1185,20,laundry,O
1186,20,until,O
1187,20,late,O
1188,20,",",O
1189,20,not,O
1190,20,the,O
1191,20,owner,O
1192,20,is,O
1193,20,fault,O
1194,20,per,O
1195,20,se,O
1196,20,.,O
1197,21,So,O
1198,21,close,O
1199,21,to,O
1200,21,the,O
1201,21,Kallang,B-geo
1202,21,MRT,O
1203,21,station,O
1204,21,",",O
1205,21,this,O
1206,21,place,O
1207,21,is,O
1208,21,incredibly,O
1209,21,clean,O
1210,21,and,O
1211,21,comfortable,O
1212,21,.,O
1213,22,Very,O
1214,22,central,O
1215,22,location,O
1216,22,",",O
1217,22,right,O
1218,22,in,O
1219,22,the,O
1220,22,middle,O
1221,22,of,O
1222,22,Chinatown,B-gpe
1223,22,restaurants,O
1224,22,",",O
1225,22,markets,O
1226,22,",",O
1227,22,stores,O
1228,22,",",O
1229,22,and,O
1230,22,lots,O
1231,22,of,O
1232,22,things,O
1233,22,to,O
1234,22,see,O
1235,22,around,O
1236,22,the,O
1237,22,area,O
1238,22,.,O
1239,22,Access,O
1240,22,to,O
1241,22,public,O
1242,22,transportation,O
1243,22,is,O
1244,22,a,O
1245,22,5,O
1246,22,minute,O
1247,22,walk,O
1248,22,.,O
1249,22,Highly,O
1250,22,recommend,O
1251,22,for,O
1252,22,backpack,O
1253,22,traveling,O
1254,23,Room,O
1255,23,is,O
1256,23,exactly,O
1257,23,as,O
1258,23,shown,O
1259,23,in,O
1260,23,the,O
1261,23,photos,O
1262,23,.,O
1263,23,Brilliant,O
1264,23,location,O
1265,23,in,O
1266,23,the,O
1267,23,heart,O
1268,23,of,O
1269,23,Orchard,B-geo
1270,23,only,O
1271,23,7,O
1272,23,mins,O
1273,23,walk,O
1274,23,to,O
1275,23,Somerset,B-geo
1276,23,mrt,O
1277,23,and,O
1278,23,Plaza,B-org
1279,23,Singapura,I-org
1280,23,.,O
1281,23,Lots,O
1282,23,of,O
1283,23,good,O
1284,23,quality,O
1285,23,local,O
1286,23,food,O
1287,23,options,O
1288,23,on,O
1289,23,Killenny,B-geo
1290,23,rd,I-geo
1291,23,nearby,O
1292,23,.,O
1293,23,Host,O
1294,23,Elaine,B-per
1295,23,is,O
1296,23,very,O
1297,23,friendly,O
1298,23,.,O
1299,23,Perfect,O
1300,23,budget,O
1301,23,accommodation,O
1302,23,in,O
1303,23,an,O
1304,23,expensive,O
1305,23,part,O
1306,23,of,O
1307,23,Singapore,B-geo
1308,23,.,O
1309,24,The,O
1310,24,room,O
1311,24,is,O
1312,24,very,O
1313,24,clean,O
1314,24,and,O
1315,24,nice,O
1316,24,",",O
1317,24,with,O
1318,24,good,O
1319,24,air,O
1320,24,condition,O
1321,24,and,O
1322,24,useful,O
1323,24,mirror,O
1324,24,.,O
1325,24,Cold,O
1326,24,water,O
1327,24,bottle,O
1328,24,is,O
1329,24,ready,O
1330,24,when,O
1331,24,I,O
1332,24,came,O
1333,24,.,O
1334,24,Mi,O
1335,24,s,O
1336,24,house,O
1337,24,is,O
1338,24,near,O
1339,24,the,O
1340,24,MRT,O
1341,24,Sengkang,B-geo
1342,24,.,O
1343,24,It,O
1344,24,s,O
1345,24,easy,O
1346,24,to,O
1347,24,get,O
1348,24,directly,O
1349,24,to,O
1350,24,famous,O
1351,24,palace,O
1352,24,in,O
1353,24,SIN,O
1354,24,such,O
1355,24,as,O
1356,24,Little,B-gpe
1357,24,India,I-gpe
1358,24,",",O
1359,24,China,B-gpe
1360,24,Town,I-gpe
1361,24,",",O
1362,24,Clarke,B-geo
1363,24,Quay,I-geo
1364,24,and,O
1365,24,HarbourFront,B-geo
1366,24,to,O
1367,24,transfer,O
1368,24,to,O
1369,24,Sentosa,B-geo
1370,24,Island,I-geo
1371,24,.,O
1372,24,Mi,O
1373,24,and,O
1374,24,her,O
1375,24,housekeeper,O
1376,24,is,O
1377,24,very,O
1378,24,friendly,O
1379,24,and,O
1380,24,nice,O
1381,24,",",O
1382,24,her,O
1383,24,children,O
1384,24,are,O
1385,24,very,O
1386,24,lovely,O
1387,24,.,O
1388,24,Highly,O
1389,24,recommend,O
1390,24,for,O
1391,24,great,O
1392,24,palace,O
1393,24,with,O
1394,24,reasonable,O
1395,24,price,O
1396,24,.,O
1397,25,The,O
1398,25,best,O
1399,25,choice,O
1400,25,for,O
1401,25,tourists,O
1402,25,Especially,O
1403,25,for,O
1404,25,people,O
1405,25,who,O
1406,25,want,O
1407,25,to,O
1408,25,look,O
1409,25,around,O
1410,25,the,O
1411,25,city,O
1412,25,on,O
1413,25,foot,O
1414,25,.,O
1415,25,Since,O
1416,25,it,O
1417,25,s,O
1418,25,located,O
1419,25,in,O
1420,25,the,O
1421,25,very,O
1422,25,center,O
1423,25,of,O
1424,25,the,O
1425,25,city,O
1426,25,just,O
1427,25,5,O
1428,25,10mins,O
1429,25,walk,O
1430,25,from,O
1431,25,MRT,O
1432,25,Bugis,B-geo
1433,25,station,O
1434,25,",",O
1435,25,I,O
1436,25,could,O
1437,25,get,O
1438,25,to,O
1439,25,almost,O
1440,25,all,O
1441,25,the,O
1442,25,scenic,O
1443,25,places,O
1444,25,within,O
1445,25,30mins,B-tim
1446,25,on,O
1447,25,foot,O
1448,25,.,O
1449,25,Of,O
1450,25,course,O
1451,25,you,O
1452,25,can,O
1453,25,get,O
1454,25,there,O
1455,25,much,O
1456,25,faster,O
1457,25,by,O
1458,25,MRT,O
1459,25,",",O
1460,25,though,O
1461,25,.,O
1462,25,The,O
1463,25,room,O
1464,25,was,O
1465,25,spacious,O
1466,25,",",O
1467,25,neat,O
1468,25,and,O
1469,25,clean,O
1470,25,.,O
1471,25,Basic,O
1472,25,kitchen,O
1473,25,and,O
1474,25,laundry,O
1475,25,facility,O
1476,25,are,O
1477,25,available,O
1478,25,.,O
1479,25,And,O
1480,25,importantly,O
1481,25,",",O
1482,25,the,O
1483,25,hosts,O
1484,25,were,O
1485,25,so,O
1486,25,kind,O
1487,25,and,O
1488,25,helpful,O
1489,25,.,O
1490,25,They,O
1491,25,re,O
1492,25,managing,O
1493,25,pretty,O
1494,25,well,O
1495,25,",",O
1496,25,I,O
1497,25,think,O
1498,25,.,O
1499,25,Thank,O
1500,25,you,O
1501,25,Hope,O
1502,25,to,O
1503,25,see,O
1504,25,you,O
1505,25,again,O
1506,25,",",O
1507,25,guys,O
1508,26,Everything,O
1509,26,is,O
1510,26,perfect,O
1511,26,.,O
1512,26,Location,O
1513,26,is,O
1514,26,accessible,O
1515,26,to,O
1516,26,nearby,O
1517,26,MRT,O
1518,26,stations,O
1519,26,such,O
1520,26,as,O
1521,26,Little,B-gpe
1522,26,India,I-gpe
1523,26,and,O
1524,26,Farrer,B-geo
1525,26,Park,I-geo
1526,26,.,O
1527,26,Kitchen,O
1528,26,area,O
1529,26,where,O
1530,26,breakfast,O
1531,26,is,O
1532,26,being,O
1533,26,served,O
1534,26,is,O
1535,26,a,O
1536,26,bit,O
1537,26,small,O
1538,26,that,O
1539,26,it,O
1540,26,can,O
1541,26,go,O
1542,26,crowded,O
1543,26,if,O
1544,26,guests,O
1545,26,will,O
1546,26,eat,O
1547,26,together,O
1548,26,but,O
1549,26,not,O
1550,26,really,O
1551,26,a,O
1552,26,biggie,O
1553,26,.,O
1554,26,I,O
1555,26,enjoyed,O
1556,26,my,O
1557,26,stay,O
1558,26,and,O
1559,26,will,O
1560,26,surely,O
1561,26,come,O
1562,26,back,O
1563,26,soon,O
1564,27,Host,O
1565,27,was,O
1566,27,very,O
1567,27,prompt,O
1568,27,and,O
1569,27,informative,O
1570,27,.,O
1571,27,Location,O
1572,27,is,O
1573,27,close,O
1574,27,by,O
1575,27,Rocher,B-geo
1576,27,MRT,O
1577,27,and,O
1578,27,also,O
1579,27,bus,O
1580,27,station,O
1581,27,Opp,O
1582,27,Nafa,B-org
1583,27,Campus,I-org
1584,27,.,O
1585,27,We,O
1586,27,were,O
1587,27,able,O
1588,27,to,O
1589,27,take,O
1590,27,bus,O
1591,27,to,O
1592,27,Merlion,B-gpe
1593,27,Park,I-gpe
1594,27,",",O
1595,27,Clarke,B-geo
1596,27,Quay,I-geo
1597,27,",",O
1598,27,and,O
1599,27,Orchard,B-geo
1600,27,.,O
1601,27,Lasalle,B-org
1602,27,College,I-org
1603,27,of,I-org
1604,27,the,I-org
1605,27,Arts,I-org
1606,27,with,O
1607,27,its,O
1608,27,unique,O
1609,27,architectural,O
1610,27,building,O
1611,27,is,O
1612,27,located,O
1613,27,very,O
1614,27,near,O
1615,27,the,O
1616,27,apartment,O
1617,27,.,O
1618,27,It,O
1619,27,is,O
1620,27,no,O
1621,27,wonder,O
1622,27,that,O
1623,27,the,O
1624,27,host,O
1625,27,had,O
1626,27,decorated,O
1627,27,the,O
1628,27,spacious,O
1629,27,living,O
1630,27,room,O
1631,27,with,O
1632,27,lots,O
1633,27,of,O
1634,27,Artworks,O
1635,27,.,O
1636,27,Early,O
1637,27,bag,O
1638,27,drop,O
1639,27,off,O
1640,27,and,O
1641,27,bag,O
1642,27,storage,O
1643,27,after,O
1644,27,check,O
1645,27,out,O
1646,27,hour,O
1647,27,was,O
1648,27,very,O
1649,27,convenient,O
1650,27,.,O
1651,27,Our,O
1652,27,stay,O
1653,27,was,O
1654,27,pleasant,O
1655,27,.,O
1656,28,Near,O
1657,28,Kallang,B-geo
1658,28,MRT,O
1659,28,Station,O
1660,28,",",O
1661,28,many,O
1662,28,restaurants,O
1663,28,in,O
1664,28,the,O
1665,28,area,O
1666,28,",",O
1667,28,and,O
1668,28,very,O
1669,28,hospitable,O
1670,28,people,O
1671,28,on,O
1672,28,the,O
1673,28,front,O
1674,28,desk,O
1675,28,.,O
1676,28,They,O
1677,28,also,O
1678,28,give,O
1679,28,you,O
1680,28,a,O
1681,28,very,O
1682,28,good,O
1683,28,information,O
1684,28,and,O
1685,28,tips,O
1686,28,within,O
1687,28,the,O
1688,28,area,O
1689,28,.,O
1690,29,Our,O
1691,29,comments,O
1692,29,on,O
1693,29,Joyce,B-per
1694,29,Home,O
1695,29,have,O
1696,29,only,O
1697,29,countless,O
1698,29,good,O
1699,29,.,O
1700,29,.,O
1701,29,.,O
1702,29,.,O
1703,29,.,O
1704,29,.,O
1705,29,.,O
1706,29,.,O
1707,29,.,O
1708,29,",",O
1709,29,remember,O
1710,29,that,O
1711,29,the,O
1712,29,first,O
1713,29,day,O
1714,29,to,O
1715,29,her,O
1716,29,home,O
1717,29,is,O
1718,29,7,O
1719,29,30,O
1720,29,in,O
1721,29,the,O
1722,29,morning,O
1723,29,",",O
1724,29,she,O
1725,29,is,O
1726,29,waiting,O
1727,29,at,O
1728,29,home,O
1729,29,",",O
1730,29,and,O
1731,29,allows,O
1732,29,us,O
1733,29,to,O
1734,29,stay,O
1735,29,early,O
1736,29,",",O
1737,29,I,O
1738,29,am,O
1739,29,so,O
1740,29,grateful,O
1741,29,to,O
1742,29,her,O
1743,29,",",O
1744,29,exemption,O
1745,29,With,O
1746,29,the,O
1747,29,practice,O
1748,29,",",O
1749,29,you,O
1750,29,can,O
1751,29,also,O
1752,29,take,O
1753,29,a,O
1754,29,little,O
1755,29,bit,O
1756,29,of,O
1757,29,rest,O
1758,29,.,O
1759,29,After,O
1760,29,you,O
1761,29,are,O
1762,29,taking,O
1763,29,it,O
1764,29,",",O
1765,29,you,O
1766,29,will,O
1767,29,be,O
1768,29,trained,O
1769,29,.,O
1770,29,The,O
1771,29,port,O
1772,29,is,O
1773,29,simple,O
1774,29,",",O
1775,29,and,O
1776,29,the,O
1777,29,room,O
1778,29,is,O
1779,29,simple,O
1780,29,",",O
1781,29,and,O
1782,29,there,O
1783,29,is,O
1784,29,an,O
1785,29,elevator,O
1786,29,.,O
1787,29,It,O
1788,29,is,O
1789,29,very,O
1790,29,intimate,O
1791,29,.,O
1792,29,Find,O
1793,29,food,O
1794,29,",",O
1795,29,just,O
1796,29,Your,O
1797,29,stomach,O
1798,29,is,O
1799,29,vacant,O
1800,29,",",O
1801,29,there,O
1802,29,is,O
1803,29,a,O
1804,29,good,O
1805,29,thing,O
1806,29,",",O
1807,29,chicken,O
1808,29,rice,O
1809,29,is,O
1810,29,a,O
1811,29,must,O
1812,29,eat,O
1813,29,lunch,O
1814,29,to,O
1815,29,queue,O
1816,29,up,O
1817,29,for,O
1818,29,20,O
1819,29,30,O
1820,29,minutes,O
1821,29,",",O
1822,29,Katong,B-geo
1823,29,Laksa,O
1824,29,",",O
1825,29,Toast,B-org
1826,29,Box,I-org
1827,29,",",O
1828,29,Cookes,O
1829,29,",",O
1830,29,Shu,O
1831,29,",",O
1832,29,Duck,O
1833,29,",",O
1834,29,Rojak,O
1835,29,.,O
1836,29,.,O
1837,29,.,O
1838,29,There,O
1839,29,should,O
1840,29,be,O
1841,29,",",O
1842,29,there,O
1843,29,is,O
1844,29,still,O
1845,29,a,O
1846,29,specialty,O
1847,29,pastry,O
1848,29,",",O
1849,29,non,O
1850,29,test,O
1851,29,cannot,O
1852,29,.,O
1853,29,Traffic,O
1854,29,is,O
1855,29,more,O
1856,29,four,O
1857,29,way,O
1858,29,",",O
1859,29,you,O
1860,29,can,O
1861,29,take,O
1862,29,a,O
1863,29,buse,O
1864,29,",",O
1865,29,there,O
1866,29,is,O
1867,29,direct,O
1868,29,bus,O
1869,29,to,O
1870,29,China,B-gpe
1871,29,Town,I-gpe
1872,29,",",O
1873,29,Clarke,B-org
1874,29,Quay,I-org
1875,29,Musalba,I-org
1876,29,Tea,I-org
1877,29,",",O
1878,29,City,B-gpe
1879,29,Hall,I-gpe
1880,29,",",O
1881,29,Sands,B-gpe
1882,29,Hotel,I-gpe
1883,29,",",O
1884,29,Garden,B-org
1885,29,By,I-org
1886,29,The,I-org
1887,29,Bay,I-org
1888,29,",",O
1889,29,Old,B-gpe
1890,29,Airport,I-gpe
1891,29,Road,I-gpe
1892,29,Food,I-gpe
1893,29,Center,I-gpe
1894,29,delicious,O
1895,29,food,O
1896,29,family,O
1897,29,",",O
1898,29,not,O
1899,29,ETC,O
1900,29,.,O
1901,29,.,O
1902,29,.,O
1903,29,next,O
1904,29,time,O
1905,29,to,O
1906,29,Singapore,B-geo
1907,29,",",O
1908,29,Joyce,B-per
1909,29,Home,O
1910,29,is,O
1911,29,a,O
1912,29,must,O
1913,29,choose,O
1914,29,.,O
1915,30,Stay,O
1916,30,at,O
1917,30,St,B-org
1918,30,Signature,I-org
1919,30,Chinatown,I-org
1920,30,is,O
1921,30,really,O
1922,30,a,O
1923,30,good,O
1924,30,stop,O
1925,30,to,O
1926,30,go,O
1927,30,around,O
1928,30,for,O
1929,30,a,O
1930,30,touristic,O
1931,30,or,O
1932,30,business,O
1933,30,trip,O
1934,30,around,O
1935,30,Singapore,B-geo
1936,30,.,O
1937,31,The,O
1938,31,apartment,O
1939,31,is,O
1940,31,located,O
1941,31,in,O
1942,31,a,O
1943,31,beautiful,O
1944,31,complex,O
1945,31,",",O
1946,31,there,O
1947,31,is,O
1948,31,also,O
1949,31,a,O
1950,31,private,O
1951,31,pool,O
1952,31,",",O
1953,31,and,O
1954,31,in,O
1955,31,a,O
1956,31,quiet,O
1957,31,area,O
1958,31,and,O
1959,31,well,O
1960,31,served,O
1961,31,by,O
1962,31,public,O
1963,31,transport,O
1964,31,Also,O
1965,31,on,O
1966,31,foot,O
1967,31,you,O
1968,31,get,O
1969,31,in,O
1970,31,half,O
1971,31,an,O
1972,31,hour,O
1973,31,in,O
1974,31,Clarke,B-geo
1975,31,Quay,I-geo
1976,31,.,O
1977,31,Cleaning,O
1978,31,is,O
1979,31,so,O
1980,31,thus,O
1981,31,",",O
1982,31,but,O
1983,31,everything,O
1984,31,is,O
1985,31,exceeded,O
1986,31,by,O
1987,31,the,O
1988,31,kindness,O
1989,31,and,O
1990,31,availability,O
1991,31,of,O
1992,31,Callie,B-per
1993,31,and,O
1994,31,Kel,O
1995,31,.,O
1996,31,If,O
1997,31,I,O
1998,31,go,O
1999,31,back,O
2000,31,to,O
2001,31,Singapore,B-geo
2002,31,I,O
2003,31,would,O
2004,31,definitely,O
2005,31,return,O
2006,31,.,O
2007,32,Unless,O
2008,32,you,O
2009,32,are,O
2010,32,really,O
2011,32,excited,O
2012,32,about,O
2013,32,living,O
2014,32,in,O
2015,32,an,O
2016,32,old,O
2017,32,shophouse,O
2018,32,in,O
2019,32,Chinatown,B-gpe
2020,32,",",O
2021,32,I,O
2022,32,would,O
2023,32,suggest,O
2024,32,you,O
2025,32,give,O
2026,32,this,O
2027,32,a,O
2028,32,pass,O
2029,32,.,O
2030,32,If,O
2031,32,you,O
2032,32,like,O
2033,32,the,O
2034,32,busy,O
2035,32,city,O
2036,32,",",O
2037,32,and,O
2038,32,consider,O
2039,32,this,O
2040,32,convenient,O
2041,32,to,O
2042,32,what,O
2043,32,you,O
2044,32,are,O
2045,32,doing,O
2046,32,",",O
2047,32,you,O
2048,32,may,O
2049,32,like,O
2050,32,it,O
2051,32,.,O
2052,32,This,O
2053,32,property,O
2054,32,needs,O
2055,32,upgrading,O
2056,32,.,O
2057,32,A,O
2058,32,bit,O
2059,32,too,O
2060,32,old,O
2061,32,and,O
2062,32,dark,O
2063,32,for,O
2064,32,me,O
2065,32,.,O
2066,32,The,O
2067,32,worst,O
2068,32,is,O
2069,32,that,O
2070,32,to,O
2071,32,catch,O
2072,32,a,O
2073,32,cab,O
2074,32,or,O
2075,32,Grab,B-org
2076,32,",",O
2077,32,they,O
2078,32,will,O
2079,32,not,O
2080,32,stop,O
2081,32,in,O
2082,32,the,O
2083,32,bus,O
2084,32,lane,O
2085,32,outside,O
2086,32,the,O
2087,32,shophouse,O
2088,32,during,O
2089,32,business,O
2090,32,hours,O
2091,32,.,O
2092,32,.,O
2093,32,.,O
2094,32,.just,O
2095,32,the,O
2096,32,time,O
2097,32,when,O
2098,32,you,O
2099,32,need,O
2100,32,them,O
2101,32,It,O
2102,32,is,O
2103,32,not,O
2104,32,permitted,O
2105,32,.,O
2106,32,It,O
2107,32,was,O
2108,32,just,O
2109,32,not,O
2110,32,easy,O
2111,32,to,O
2112,32,stay,O
2113,32,here,O
2114,32,.,O
2115,33,Great,O
2116,33,location,O
2117,33,its,O
2118,33,on,O
2119,33,a,O
2120,33,lovely,O
2121,33,part,O
2122,33,of,O
2123,33,Chinatown,B-gpe
2124,33,with,O
2125,33,lots,O
2126,33,of,O
2127,33,places,O
2128,33,to,O
2129,33,eat,O
2130,33,.,O
2131,33,The,O
2132,33,staff,O
2133,33,is,O
2134,33,friendly,O
2135,33,",",O
2136,33,and,O
2137,33,place,O
2138,33,is,O
2139,33,clean,O
2140,33,.,O
2141,33,High,O
2142,33,recommended,O
2143,33,for,O
2144,33,backpackers,O
2145,34,Good,O
2146,34,location,O
2147,34,near,O
2148,34,Kallang,B-geo
2149,34,MRT,O
2150,34,.,O
2151,34,A,O
2152,34,little,O
2153,34,noisy,O
2154,34,at,O
2155,34,night,O
2156,34,and,O
2157,34,people,O
2158,34,smoking,O
2159,34,right,O
2160,34,outside,O
2161,34,the,O
2162,34,building,O
2163,34,.,O
2164,34,Very,O
2165,34,comfortable,O
2166,34,and,O
2167,34,decently,O
2168,34,clean,O
2169,34,stay,O
2170,34,.,O
2171,35,Enjoyable,O
2172,35,Stay,O
2173,35,in,O
2174,35,Royal,B-org
2175,35,Hostel,I-org
2176,35,",",O
2177,35,Singapore,B-geo
2178,35,.,O
2179,35,The,O
2180,35,rooms,O
2181,35,were,O
2182,35,clean,O
2183,35,",",O
2184,35,spacious,O
2185,35,and,O
2186,35,have,O
2187,35,bunks,O
2188,35,",",O
2189,35,and,O
2190,35,a,O
2191,35,personal,O
2192,35,locker,O
2193,35,.,O
2194,35,a,O
2195,35,deposit,O
2196,35,of,O
2197,35,2,O
2198,35,dollars,O
2199,35,needed,O
2200,35,.,O
2201,35,Very,O
2202,35,close,O
2203,35,to,O
2204,35,the,O
2205,35,Chinatown,B-gpe
2206,35,metro,O
2207,35,station,O
2208,35,",",O
2209,35,walkable,O
2210,35,distance,O
2211,35,and,O
2212,35,then,O
2213,35,from,O
2214,35,the,O
2215,35,hostel,O
2216,35,you,O
2217,35,are,O
2218,35,at,O
2219,35,the,O
2220,35,central,O
2221,35,to,O
2222,35,everything,O
2223,35,you,O
2224,35,need,O
2225,35,to,O
2226,35,EAT,O
2227,35,in,O
2228,35,Singapore,B-geo
2229,35,.,O
2230,35,The,O
2231,35,staff,O
2232,35,was,O
2233,35,helpful,O
2234,35,.,O
2235,35,From,O
2236,35,help,O
2237,35,with,O
2238,35,locating,O
2239,35,the,O
2240,35,post,O
2241,35,office,O
2242,35,to,O
2243,35,advice,O
2244,35,on,O
2245,35,off,O
2246,35,the,O
2247,35,beaten,O
2248,35,path,O
2249,35,",",O
2250,35,to,O
2251,35,keeping,O
2252,35,guests,O
2253,35,fed,O
2254,35,with,O
2255,35,breakfast,O
2256,35,",",O
2257,35,to,O
2258,35,treating,O
2259,35,guests,O
2260,35,with,O
2261,35,cool,O
2262,35,beer,O
2263,35,in,O
2264,35,the,O
2265,35,late,O
2266,35,evening,O
2267,35,these,O
2268,35,people,O
2269,35,are,O
2270,35,awesome,O
2271,35,.,O
2272,35,Stayed,O
2273,35,April,B-tim
2274,35,2015,I-tim
2275,35,",",O
2276,35,traveled,O
2277,35,solo,O
2278,36,Great,O
2279,36,cosy,O
2280,36,studio,O
2281,36,nice,O
2282,36,and,O
2283,36,modern,O
2284,36,.,O
2285,36,Warm,O
2286,36,shower,O
2287,36,amazingly,O
2288,36,comfortable,O
2289,36,King,O
2290,36,size,O
2291,36,bed,O
2292,36,and,O
2293,36,quiet,O
2294,36,AC,O
2295,36,.,O
2296,36,Very,O
2297,36,handy,O
2298,36,location,O
2299,36,walkable,O
2300,36,to,O
2301,36,Arab,B-gpe
2302,36,St,I-gpe
2303,36,bars,O
2304,36,",",O
2305,36,Rochor,B-geo
2306,36,station,O
2307,36,",",O
2308,36,Bugis,B-gpe
2309,36,Junction,I-gpe
2310,36,and,O
2311,36,Little,B-gpe
2312,36,India,I-gpe
2313,36,.,O
2314,36,There,O
2315,36,is,O
2316,36,a,O
2317,36,shared,O
2318,36,kitchen,O
2319,36,but,O
2320,36,plenty,O
2321,36,of,O
2322,36,great,O
2323,36,local,O
2324,36,cuisine,O
2325,36,right,O
2326,36,outside,O
2327,36,too,O
2328,36,.,O
2329,37,Go,O
2330,37,for,O
2331,37,it,O
2332,37,",",O
2333,37,it,O
2334,37,is,O
2335,37,a,O
2336,37,great,O
2337,37,place,O
2338,37,Perfect,O
2339,37,location,O
2340,37,in,O
2341,37,the,O
2342,37,middle,O
2343,37,of,O
2344,37,Chinatown,B-gpe
2345,37,",",O
2346,37,just,O
2347,37,10,B-tim
2348,37,seconds,I-tim
2349,37,away,O
2350,37,from,O
2351,37,the,O
2352,37,mrt,O
2353,37,",",O
2354,37,you,O
2355,37,can,O
2356,37,also,O
2357,37,walk,O
2358,37,to,O
2359,37,the,O
2360,37,Buddha,B-org
2361,37,Tooth,I-org
2362,37,Relic,I-org
2363,37,Temple,I-org
2364,37,.,O
2365,37,The,O
2366,37,place,O
2367,37,was,O
2368,37,very,O
2369,37,clean,O
2370,37,",",O
2371,37,and,O
2372,37,A,O
2373,37,LOT,O
2374,37,of,O
2375,37,shampoos,O
2376,37,",",O
2377,37,soaps,O
2378,37,",",O
2379,37,etc,O
2380,37,were,O
2381,37,available,O
2382,37,for,O
2383,37,us,O
2384,37,.,O
2385,37,Our,O
2386,37,room,O
2387,37,had,O
2388,37,a,O
2389,37,great,O
2390,37,view,O
2391,37,over,O
2392,37,the,O
2393,37,city,O
2394,37,.,O
2395,37,There,O
2396,37,is,O
2397,37,a,O
2398,37,nice,O
2399,37,atmosphere,O
2400,37,both,O
2401,37,in,O
2402,37,the,O
2403,37,apartment,O
2404,37,and,O
2405,37,in,O
2406,37,the,O
2407,37,neighborhood,O
2408,37,.,O
2409,37,The,O
2410,37,host,O
2411,37,also,O
2412,37,sent,O
2413,37,us,O
2414,37,many,O
2415,37,pictures,O
2416,37,to,O
2417,37,smooth,O
2418,37,our,O
2419,37,arrival,O
2420,37,",",O
2421,37,making,O
2422,37,it,O
2423,37,very,O
2424,37,easy,O
2425,37,to,O
2426,37,find,O
2427,37,and,O
2428,37,stress,O
2429,37,free,O
2430,37,.,O
2431,37,Definitely,O
2432,37,recommend,O
2433,38,Great,O
2434,38,place,O
2435,38,to,O
2436,38,stay,O
2437,38,with,O
2438,38,nearby,O
2439,38,local,O
2440,38,restaurants,O
2441,38,and,O
2442,38,Bugis,B-geo
2443,38,center,O
2444,38,.,O
2445,38,I,O
2446,38,got,O
2447,38,there,O
2448,38,earlier,O
2449,38,but,O
2450,38,the,O
2451,38,host,O
2452,38,allowed,O
2453,38,me,O
2454,38,to,O
2455,38,check,O
2456,38,in,O
2457,38,so,O
2458,38,that,O
2459,38,was,O
2460,38,really,O
2461,38,nice,O
2462,38,.,O
2463,39,Overall,O
2464,39,",",O
2465,39,a,O
2466,39,great,O
2467,39,place,O
2468,39,to,O
2469,39,stay,O
2470,39,convenient,O
2471,39,location,O
2472,39,walkable,O
2473,39,to,O
2474,39,Orchard,B-geo
2475,39,",",O
2476,39,Robertson,B-geo
2477,39,Quay,I-geo
2478,39,",",O
2479,39,Clarke,B-geo
2480,39,Quay,I-geo
2481,39,",",O
2482,39,MRT,O
2483,39,stations,O
2484,39,",",O
2485,39,etc,O
2486,39,and,O
2487,39,decent,O
2488,39,value,O
2489,39,for,O
2490,39,area,O
2491,39,.,O
2492,39,In,O
2493,39,a,O
2494,39,residential,O
2495,39,area,O
2496,39,so,O
2497,39,nice,O
2498,39,and,O
2499,39,quiet,O
2500,39,in,O
2501,39,the,O
2502,39,evenings,O
2503,39,and,O
2504,39,family,O
2505,39,oriented,O
2506,39,.,O
2507,39,Good,O
2508,39,for,O
2509,39,short,O
2510,39,and,O
2511,39,long,O
2512,39,term,O
2513,39,stay,O
2514,39,as,O
2515,39,place,O
2516,39,includes,O
2517,39,washer,O
2518,39,dryer,O
2519,39,.,O
2520,39,Apartment,O
2521,39,is,O
2522,39,not,O
2523,39,brand,O
2524,39,new,O
2525,39,but,O
2526,39,well,O
2527,39,kept,O
2528,39,.,O
2529,39,Kitchenette,O
2530,39,could,O
2531,39,equip,O
2532,39,scissors,O
2533,39,and,O
2534,39,strainer,O
2535,39,colander,O
2536,39,.,O
2537,39,Note,O
2538,39,that,O
2539,39,kitchenette,O
2540,39,is,O
2541,39,basic,O
2542,39,only,O
2543,39,table,O
2544,39,top,O
2545,39,induction,O
2546,39,cooker,O
2547,39,so,O
2548,39,only,O
2549,39,light,O
2550,39,cooking,O
2551,39,in,O
2552,39,the,O
2553,39,apartment,O
2554,39,.,O
2555,40,The,O
2556,40,pods,O
2557,40,are,O
2558,40,clean,O
2559,40,and,O
2560,40,comfy,O
2561,40,.,O
2562,40,It,O
2563,40,s,O
2564,40,a,O
2565,40,quiet,O
2566,40,place,O
2567,40,and,O
2568,40,you,O
2569,40,ll,O
2570,40,get,O
2571,40,enough,O
2572,40,privacy,O
2573,40,in,O
2574,40,your,O
2575,40,Pod,O
2576,40,.,O
2577,40,It,O
2578,40,s,O
2579,40,located,O
2580,40,super,O
2581,40,close,O
2582,40,to,O
2583,40,China,B-gpe
2584,40,town,I-gpe
2585,40,and,O
2586,40,is,O
2587,40,well,O
2588,40,connected,O
2589,40,by,O
2590,40,bus,O
2591,40,and,O
2592,40,MRT,O
2593,40,.,O
2594,40,Lot,O
2595,40,of,O
2596,40,restaurants,O
2597,40,and,O
2598,40,hawkers,O
2599,40,nearby,O
2600,40,",",O
2601,40,enough,O
2602,40,and,O
2603,40,more,O
2604,40,options,O
2605,40,to,O
2606,40,eat,O
2607,40,out,O
2608,40,.,O
2609,40,It,O
2610,40,s,O
2611,40,walkable,O
2612,40,to,O
2613,40,Boat,B-geo
2614,40,Quay,I-geo
2615,40,and,O
2616,40,Clarke,B-geo
2617,40,Quay,I-geo
2618,40,.,O
2619,40,It,O
2620,40,s,O
2621,40,a,O
2622,40,quiet,O
2623,40,place,O
2624,40,which,O
2625,40,gives,O
2626,40,you,O
2627,40,a,O
2628,40,professional,O
2629,40,vibe,O
2630,40,.,O
2631,40,I,O
2632,40,ve,O
2633,40,heard,O
2634,40,that,O
2635,40,most,O
2636,40,hostels,O
2637,40,in,O
2638,40,Singapore,O
2639,40,are,O
2640,40,like,O
2641,40,that,O
2642,40,.,O
2643,41,Located,O
2644,41,in,O
2645,41,the,O
2646,41,Little,B-gpe
2647,41,India,I-gpe
2648,41,area,O
2649,41,",",O
2650,41,the,O
2651,41,apartment,O
2652,41,is,O
2653,41,very,O
2654,41,close,O
2655,41,to,O
2656,41,the,O
2657,41,small,O
2658,41,Indian,B-gpe
2659,41,subway,O
2660,41,station,O
2661,41,.,O
2662,41,You,O
2663,41,can,O
2664,41,reach,O
2665,41,the,O
2666,41,shopping,O
2667,41,center,O
2668,41,or,O
2669,41,attraction,O
2670,41,you,O
2671,41,want,O
2672,41,to,O
2673,41,go,O
2674,41,by,O
2675,41,1,O
2676,41,3,O
2677,41,.,O
2678,41,The,O
2679,41,landlord,O
2680,41,",",O
2681,41,very,O
2682,41,clean,O
2683,41,room,O
2684,41,",",O
2685,41,very,O
2686,41,clean,O
2687,41,room,O
2688,41,",",O
2689,41,very,O
2690,41,convenient,O
2691,41,Check,O
2692,41,in,O
2693,41,There,O
2694,41,are,O
2695,41,also,O
2696,41,milk,O
2697,41,",",O
2698,41,pure,O
2699,41,water,O
2700,41,",",O
2701,41,bread,O
2702,41,",",O
2703,41,apartment,O
2704,41,in,O
2705,41,the,O
2706,41,room,O
2707,41,",",O
2708,41,in,O
2709,41,addition,O
2710,41,to,O
2711,41,toothbrushes,O
2712,41,",",O
2713,41,toothpaste,O
2714,41,requires,O
2715,41,self,O
2716,41,contained,O
2717,41,",",O
2718,41,other,O
2719,41,necessities,O
2720,41,can,O
2721,41,be,O
2722,41,obtained,O
2723,41,in,O
2724,41,the,O
2725,41,apartment,O
2726,41,.,O
2727,41,During,O
2728,41,the,O
2729,41,stay,O
2730,41,",",O
2731,41,the,O
2732,41,passport,O
2733,41,lock,O
2734,41,in,O
2735,41,the,O
2736,41,safe,O
2737,41,",",O
2738,41,the,O
2739,41,landlord,O
2740,41,also,O
2741,41,To,O
2742,41,open,O
2743,41,the,O
2744,41,safe,O
2745,41,",",O
2746,41,although,O
2747,41,there,O
2748,41,is,O
2749,41,no,O
2750,41,friend,O
2751,41,of,O
2752,41,your,O
2753,41,own,O
2754,41,eyes,O
2755,41,",",O
2756,41,you,O
2757,41,can,O
2758,41,know,O
2759,41,the,O
2760,41,landlord,O
2761,41,is,O
2762,41,a,O
2763,41,very,O
2764,41,good,O
2765,41,person,O
2766,41,.,O
2767,41,There,O
2768,41,is,O
2769,41,a,O
2770,41,cinema,O
2771,41,that,O
2772,41,releases,O
2773,41,the,O
2774,41,Indian,B-gpe
2775,41,movie,O
2776,41,",",O
2777,41,you,O
2778,41,can,O
2779,41,go,O
2780,41,see,O
2781,41,",",O
2782,41,hahaha,O
2783,41,.,O
2784,41,Other,O
2785,41,words,O
2786,41,",",O
2787,41,the,O
2788,41,movie,O
2789,41,theater,O
2790,41,There,O
2791,41,are,O
2792,41,a,O
2793,41,few,O
2794,41,traditional,O
2795,41,Indian,O
2796,41,restaurants,O
2797,41,",",O
2798,41,the,O
2799,41,taste,O
2800,41,is,O
2801,41,very,O
2802,41,good,O
2803,41,The,O
2804,41,apartment,O
2805,41,can,O
2806,41,go,O
2807,41,to,O
2808,41,the,O
2809,41,surrounding,O
2810,41,shopping,O
2811,41,center,O
2812,41,.,O
2813,41,The,O
2814,41,subway,O
2815,41,can,O
2816,41,be,O
2817,41,easily,O
2818,41,arrived,O
2819,41,.,O
2820,41,But,O
2821,41,the,O
2822,41,zoo,O
2823,41,",",O
2824,41,etc,O
2825,41,.,O
2826,41,",",O
2827,41,suggestions,O
2828,41,or,O
2829,41,arrive,O
2830,41,at,O
2831,41,the,O
2832,41,GRAB,B-org
2833,41,",",O
2834,41,this,O
2835,41,will,O
2836,41,not,O
2837,41,spend,O
2838,41,too,O
2839,41,much,O
2840,41,time,O
2841,41,on,O
2842,41,the,O
2843,41,road,O
2844,41,.,O
2845,41,Don,O
2846,41,t,O
2847,41,worry,O
2848,41,More,O
2849,41,Indian,B-gpe
2850,41,people,O
2851,41,nearby,O
2852,41,",",O
2853,41,because,O
2854,41,they,O
2855,41,stayed,O
2856,41,for,O
2857,41,a,O
2858,41,few,O
2859,41,days,O
2860,41,",",O
2861,41,you,O
2862,41,will,O
2863,41,find,O
2864,41,that,O
2865,41,you,O
2866,41,will,O
2867,41,like,O
2868,41,to,O
2869,41,live,O
2870,41,in,O
2871,41,this,O
2872,41,place,O
2873,41,",",O
2874,41,like,O
2875,41,staying,O
2876,41,in,O
2877,41,Singapore,B-geo
2878,41,is,O
2879,41,pleasant,O
2880,41,",",O
2881,41,clean,O
2882,41,and,O
2883,41,livable,O
2884,41,country,O
2885,42,It,O
2886,42,is,O
2887,42,extremely,O
2888,42,well,O
2889,42,located,O
2890,42,though,O
2891,42,this,O
2892,42,may,O
2893,42,not,O
2894,42,appear,O
2895,42,so,O
2896,42,from,O
2897,42,maps,O
2898,42,because,O
2899,42,a,O
2900,42,it,O
2901,42,is,O
2902,42,within,O
2903,42,easy,O
2904,42,walking,O
2905,42,distance,O
2906,42,to,O
2907,42,the,O
2908,42,Tan,B-gpe
2909,42,Kah,I-gpe
2910,42,Kee,I-gpe
2911,42,MRT,O
2912,42,station,O
2913,42,which,O
2914,42,opens,O
2915,42,all,O
2916,42,of,O
2917,42,Orchard,B-geo
2918,42,Road,I-geo
2919,42,",",O
2920,42,downtown,O
2921,42,and,O
2922,42,Maria,B-per
2923,42,",",O
2924,42,b,O
2925,42,it,O
2926,42,is,O
2927,42,just,O
2928,42,around,O
2929,42,the,O
2930,42,corner,O
2931,42,from,O
2932,42,the,O
2933,42,Hillcrest,B-geo
2934,42,Road,I-geo
2935,42,shophouses,O
2936,42,which,O
2937,42,have,O
2938,42,become,O
2939,42,a,O
2940,42,special,O
2941,42,upmarket,O
2942,42,area,O
2943,42,for,O
2944,42,in,O
2945,42,the,O
2946,42,know,O
2947,42,locals,O
2948,42,",",O
2949,42,c,O
2950,42,key,O
2951,42,upmarket,O
2952,42,local,O
2953,42,areas,O
2954,42,like,O
2955,42,Holland,B-geo
2956,42,Village,I-geo
2957,42,and,O
2958,42,the,O
2959,42,hawker,O
2960,42,stalls,O
2961,42,across,O
2962,42,Beauty,B-geo
2963,42,World,I-geo
2964,42,are,O
2965,42,close,O
2966,42,by,O
2967,42,via,O
2968,42,MRT,O
2969,42,",",O
2970,42,and,O
2971,42,d,O
2972,42,Tryston,B-per
2973,42,is,O
2974,42,a,O
2975,42,wonderfully,O
2976,42,friendly,O
2977,42,host,O
2978,42,.,O
2979,43,Location,O
2980,43,This,O
2981,43,studio,O
2982,43,is,O
2983,43,right,O
2984,43,in,O
2985,43,the,O
2986,43,heart,O
2987,43,of,O
2988,43,Little,B-gpe
2989,43,India,I-gpe
2990,43,.,O
2991,43,The,O
2992,43,Farrer,B-geo
2993,43,Station,O
2994,43,is,O
2995,43,about,O
2996,43,2,B-tim
2997,43,minutes,I-tim
2998,43,away,O
2999,43,",",O
3000,43,very,O
3001,43,handy,O
3002,43,.,O
3003,43,You,O
3004,43,get,O
3005,43,what,O
3006,43,you,O
3007,43,pay,O
3008,43,for,O
3009,43,in,O
3010,43,terms,O
3011,43,of,O
3012,43,the,O
3013,43,facilities,O
3014,43,",",O
3015,43,but,O
3016,43,best,O
3017,43,value,O
3018,43,in,O
3019,43,Singapore,B-geo
3020,43,for,O
3021,43,accommodation,O
3022,43,.,O
3023,44,Wink,B-org
3024,44,Hostel,I-org
3025,44,is,O
3026,44,in,O
3027,44,the,O
3028,44,perfect,O
3029,44,location,O
3030,44,to,O
3031,44,explore,O
3032,44,Singapore,B-geo
3033,44,",",O
3034,44,right,O
3035,44,in,O
3036,44,the,O
3037,44,heart,O
3038,44,of,O
3039,44,Chinatown,B-gpe
3040,44,and,O
3041,44,close,O
3042,44,to,O
3043,44,the,O
3044,44,train,O
3045,44,.,O
3046,44,They,O
3047,44,were,O
3048,44,great,O
3049,44,hosts,O
3050,44,",",O
3051,44,I,O
3052,44,arrived,O
3053,44,at,O
3054,44,4am,O
3055,44,and,O
3056,44,it,O
3057,44,was,O
3058,44,so,O
3059,44,easy,O
3060,44,to,O
3061,44,check,O
3062,44,in,O
3063,44,",",O
3064,44,and,O
3065,44,any,O
3066,44,time,O
3067,44,I,O
3068,44,needed,O
3069,44,assistance,O
3070,44,they,O
3071,44,were,O
3072,44,very,O
3073,44,helpful,O
3074,44,.,O
3075,44,The,O
3076,44,room,O
3077,44,was,O
3078,44,nice,O
3079,44,and,O
3080,44,clean,O
3081,44,with,O
3082,44,a,O
3083,44,good,O
3084,44,amount,O
3085,44,of,O
3086,44,space,O
3087,44,",",O
3088,44,the,O
3089,44,beds,O
3090,44,are,O
3091,44,great,O
3092,44,and,O
3093,44,private,O
3094,44,",",O
3095,44,and,O
3096,44,the,O
3097,44,aircon,O
3098,44,in,O
3099,44,the,O
3100,44,room,O
3101,44,was,O
3102,44,a,O
3103,44,blessing,O
3104,44,.,O
3105,44,Breakfast,O
3106,44,was,O
3107,44,simple,O
3108,44,.,O
3109,44,Definitely,O
3110,44,a,O
3111,44,good,O
3112,44,place,O
3113,44,to,O
3114,44,stay,O
3115,44,.,O
3116,45,This,O
3117,45,review,O
3118,45,is,O
3119,45,for,O
3120,45,a,O
3121,45,similar,O
3122,45,space,O
3123,45,",",O
3124,45,as,O
3125,45,I,O
3126,45,saw,O
3127,45,from,O
3128,45,another,O
3129,45,review,O
3130,45,that,O
3131,45,there,O
3132,45,were,O
3133,45,no,O
3134,45,windows,O
3135,45,in,O
3136,45,this,O
3137,45,one,O
3138,45,",",O
3139,45,but,O
3140,45,the,O
3141,45,minor,O
3142,45,upgrade,O
3143,45,was,O
3144,45,fine,O
3145,45,.,O
3146,45,It,O
3147,45,was,O
3148,45,service,O
3149,45,apartments,O
3150,45,in,O
3151,45,Chinatown,B-gpe
3152,45,on,O
3153,45,a,O
3154,45,very,O
3155,45,popular,O
3156,45,street,O
3157,45,",",O
3158,45,but,O
3159,45,it,O
3160,45,is,O
3161,45,actually,O
3162,45,as,O
3163,45,quiet,O
3164,45,as,O
3165,45,possible,O
3166,45,.,O
3167,45,I,O
3168,45,do,O
3169,45,not,O
3170,45,mind,O
3171,45,it,O
3172,45,",",O
3173,45,but,O
3174,45,I,O
3175,45,would,O
3176,45,suggest,O
3177,45,very,O
3178,45,light,O
3179,45,sleepers,O
3180,45,should,O
3181,45,look,O
3182,45,elsewhere,O
3183,45,.,O
3184,45,Overall,O
3185,45,the,O
3186,45,space,O
3187,45,was,O
3188,45,comfortable,O
3189,45,",",O
3190,45,clean,O
3191,45,",",O
3192,45,and,O
3193,45,very,O
3194,45,well,O
3195,45,managed,O
3196,45,.,O
3197,45,The,O
3198,45,hosts,O
3199,45,are,O
3200,45,quite,O
3201,45,responsive,O
3202,45,and,O
3203,45,very,O
3204,45,communicative,O
3205,45,if,O
3206,45,there,O
3207,45,is,O
3208,45,ever,O
3209,45,any,O
3210,45,problem,O
3211,45,.,O
3212,45,I,O
3213,45,would,O
3214,45,certainly,O
3215,45,consider,O
3216,45,Heritage,O
3217,45,when,O
3218,45,I,O
3219,45,return,O
3220,45,to,O
3221,45,Singapore,B-geo
3222,45,.,O
3223,46,Chrisa,B-per
3224,46,was,O
3225,46,right,O
3226,46,on,O
3227,46,the,O
3228,46,spot,O
3229,46,letting,O
3230,46,me,O
3231,46,in,O
3232,46,and,O
3233,46,helping,O
3234,46,me,O
3235,46,get,O
3236,46,my,O
3237,46,stuff,O
3238,46,up,O
3239,46,the,O
3240,46,stairs,O
3241,46,.,O
3242,46,Listing,O
3243,46,description,O
3244,46,was,O
3245,46,good,O
3246,46,.,O
3247,46,.,O
3248,46,.S2,O
3249,46,is,O
3250,46,a,O
3251,46,smart,O
3252,46,little,O
3253,46,room,O
3254,46,.,O
3255,46,.,O
3256,46,.bright,O
3257,46,",",O
3258,46,clean,O
3259,46,",",O
3260,46,high,O
3261,46,ceilings,O
3262,46,",",O
3263,46,modern,O
3264,46,fixtures,O
3265,46,.,O
3266,46,She,O
3267,46,had,O
3268,46,noise,O
3269,46,insulation,O
3270,46,blanket,O
3271,46,installed,O
3272,46,over,O
3273,46,window,O
3274,46,to,O
3275,46,help,O
3276,46,cut,O
3277,46,down,O
3278,46,on,O
3279,46,outside,O
3280,46,MRT,O
3281,46,station,O
3282,46,construction,O
3283,46,noise,O
3284,46,which,O
3285,46,helped,O
3286,46,.,O
3287,46,Bed,O
3288,46,was,O
3289,46,comfy,O
3290,46,",",O
3291,46,hard,O
3292,46,mattress,O
3293,46,.,O
3294,46,Being,O
3295,46,right,O
3296,46,on,O
3297,46,the,O
3298,46,edge,O
3299,46,of,O
3300,46,Little,B-gpe
3301,46,India,I-gpe
3302,46,and,O
3303,46,a,O
3304,46,few,O
3305,46,blocks,O
3306,46,from,O
3307,46,Arab,B-gpe
3308,46,Street,I-gpe
3309,46,was,O
3310,46,fantastic,O
3311,46,.,O
3312,46,A,O
3313,46,few,O
3314,46,minutes,O
3315,46,from,O
3316,46,Sim,B-org
3317,46,Lim,I-org
3318,46,Square,I-org
3319,46,and,O
3320,46,Bugis,B-geo
3321,46,area,O
3322,46,also,O
3323,46,made,O
3324,46,for,O
3325,46,good,O
3326,46,location,O
3327,46,.,O
3328,47,Great,O
3329,47,location,O
3330,47,.,O
3331,47,Close,O
3332,47,to,O
3333,47,Bugis,B-org
3334,47,Junction,I-org
3335,47,food,O
3336,47,and,O
3337,47,shops,O
3338,47,.,O
3339,47,Excellent,O
3340,47,front,O
3341,47,desk,O
3342,47,service,O
3343,47,.,O
3344,47,See,O
3345,47,you,O
3346,47,next,O
3347,47,year,O
3348,48,This,O
3349,48,is,O
3350,48,a,O
3351,48,very,O
3352,48,nice,O
3353,48,place,O
3354,48,to,O
3355,48,stay,O
3356,48,for,O
3357,48,a,O
3358,48,short,O
3359,48,visit,O
3360,48,",",O
3361,48,and,O
3362,48,for,O
3363,48,me,O
3364,48,",",O
3365,48,a,O
3366,48,good,O
3367,48,place,O
3368,48,of,O
3369,48,transition,O
3370,48,and,O
3371,48,work,O
3372,48,from,O
3373,48,home,O
3374,48,.,O
3375,48,Folks,O
3376,48,are,O
3377,48,very,O
3378,48,nice,O
3379,48,.,O
3380,48,Location,O
3381,48,is,O
3382,48,great,O
3383,48,for,O
3384,48,access,O
3385,48,to,O
3386,48,Orchard,B-geo
3387,48,road,I-geo
3388,48,",",O
3389,48,Bugis,B-geo
3390,48,",",O
3391,48,and,O
3392,48,CBD,O
3393,48,.,O
3394,49,The,O
3395,49,landlord,O
3396,49,Angelina,B-per
3397,49,is,O
3398,49,very,O
3399,49,enthusiastic,O
3400,49,",",O
3401,49,the,O
3402,49,flight,O
3403,49,is,O
3404,49,late,O
3405,49,to,O
3406,49,2,O
3407,49,0,O
3408,49,in,O
3409,49,the,O
3410,49,morning,O
3411,49,",",O
3412,49,she,O
3413,49,is,O
3414,49,also,O
3415,49,waiting,O
3416,49,for,O
3417,49,us,O
3418,49,in,O
3419,49,the,O
3420,49,apartment,O
3421,49,building,O
3422,49,.,O
3423,49,The,O
3424,49,room,O
3425,49,is,O
3426,49,located,O
3427,49,on,O
3428,49,the,O
3429,49,26th,O
3430,49,floor,O
3431,49,of,O
3432,49,the,O
3433,49,building,O
3434,49,",",O
3435,49,the,O
3436,49,living,O
3437,49,room,O
3438,49,and,O
3439,49,the,O
3440,49,bedroom,O
3441,49,window,O
3442,49,can,O
3443,49,see,O
3444,49,the,O
3445,49,beautiful,O
3446,49,scenery,O
3447,49,",",O
3448,49,and,O
3449,49,6,O
3450,49,58,O
3451,49,AM,O
3452,49,can,O
3453,49,watch,O
3454,49,Singapore,B-geo
3455,49,Sunrise,O
3456,49,on,O
3457,49,time,O
3458,49,.,O
3459,49,Very,O
3460,49,beautiful,O
3461,49,.,O
3462,49,Just,O
3463,49,Singapore,B-geo
3464,49,weather,O
3465,49,is,O
3466,49,hot,O
3467,49,",",O
3468,49,if,O
3469,49,there,O
3470,49,is,O
3471,49,a,O
3472,49,meal,O
3473,49,on,O
3474,49,the,O
3475,49,kitchen,O
3476,49,countertop,O
3477,49,",",O
3478,49,there,O
3479,49,will,O
3480,49,be,O
3481,49,some,O
3482,49,kitchen,O
3483,49,countertops,O
3484,49,in,O
3485,49,the,O
3486,49,middle,O
3487,49,of,O
3488,49,the,O
3489,49,kitchen,O
3490,49,countertop,O
3491,49,",",O
3492,49,Ahahaha,O
3493,49,",",O
3494,49,very,O
3495,49,original,O
3496,49,ecology,O
3497,49,.,O
3498,49,.,O
3499,49,.,O
3500,49,.,O
3501,49,.,O
3502,49,.,O
3503,49,.,O
3504,49,.,O
3505,49,There,O
3506,49,is,O
3507,49,a,O
3508,49,journey,O
3509,49,during,O
3510,49,the,O
3511,49,stay,O
3512,49,",",O
3513,49,the,O
3514,49,landlord,O
3515,49,will,O
3516,49,be,O
3517,49,very,O
3518,49,careful,O
3519,49,.,O
3520,49,The,O
3521,49,opposite,O
3522,49,is,O
3523,49,the,O
3524,49,Harborne,B-geo
3525,49,and,O
3526,49,Arab,B-gpe
3527,49,Street,I-gpe
3528,49,.,O
3529,49,It,O
3530,49,is,O
3531,49,recommended,O
3532,49,that,O
3533,49,the,O
3534,49,Landmark,O
3535,49,buffet,O
3536,49,nearby,O
3537,49,",",O
3538,49,the,O
3539,49,network,O
3540,49,is,O
3541,49,available,O
3542,49,for,O
3543,49,20,O
3544,49,discount,O
3545,49,.,O
3546,49,In,O
3547,49,short,O
3548,49,",",O
3549,49,it,O
3550,49,is,O
3551,49,recommended,O
3552,49,.,O
3553,49,Thank,O
3554,49,you,O
3555,49,.,O
3556,50,We,O
3557,50,had,O
3558,50,a,O
3559,50,great,O
3560,50,time,O
3561,50,at,O
3562,50,Diane,B-per
3563,50,is,O
3564,50,place,O
3565,50,Her,O
3566,50,assistant,O
3567,50,checked,O
3568,50,us,O
3569,50,in,O
3570,50,and,O
3571,50,she,O
3572,50,was,O
3573,50,very,O
3574,50,polite,O
3575,50,.,O
3576,50,The,O
3577,50,location,O
3578,50,of,O
3579,50,this,O
3580,50,place,O
3581,50,in,O
3582,50,Tiong,B-geo
3583,50,Bahru,I-geo
3584,50,is,O
3585,50,great,O
3586,50,and,O
3587,50,near,O
3588,50,many,O
3589,50,popular,O
3590,50,eating,O
3591,50,spots,O
3592,50,.,O
3593,50,The,O
3594,50,place,O
3595,50,was,O
3596,50,clean,O
3597,50,",",O
3598,50,spacious,O
3599,50,",",O
3600,50,comfortable,O
3601,50,and,O
3602,50,well,O
3603,50,stocked,O
3604,50,with,O
3605,50,equipment,O
3606,50,for,O
3607,50,cooking,O
3608,50,.,O
3609,50,Would,O
3610,50,definitely,O
3611,50,book,O
3612,50,again,O
3613,50,.,O
3614,51,Great,O
3615,51,location,O
3616,51,",",O
3617,51,just,O
3618,51,upstairs,O
3619,51,of,O
3620,51,Chinatown,B-gpe
3621,51,station,O
3622,51,",",O
3623,51,very,O
3624,51,convenient,O
3625,51,.,O
3626,51,The,O
3627,51,room,O
3628,51,and,O
3629,51,bathroom,O
3630,51,toilet,O
3631,51,are,O
3632,51,old,O
3633,51,and,O
3634,51,not,O
3635,51,so,O
3636,51,clean,O
3637,51,.,O
3638,51,.,O
3639,51,cost,O
3640,51,is,O
3641,51,fair,O
3642,51,.,O
3643,52,Cozy,O
3644,52,nice,O
3645,52,little,O
3646,52,room,O
3647,52,next,O
3648,52,to,O
3649,52,a,O
3650,52,mrt,O
3651,52,and,O
3652,52,walking,O
3653,52,distance,O
3654,52,to,O
3655,52,Little,B-gpe
3656,52,India,I-gpe
3657,52,",",O
3658,52,Arab,B-gpe
3659,52,street,I-gpe
3660,52,and,O
3661,52,a,O
3662,52,couple,O
3663,52,of,O
3664,52,good,O
3665,52,and,O
3666,52,nice,O
3667,52,bars,O
3668,52,.,O
3669,52,It,O
3670,52,is,O
3671,52,a,O
3672,52,small,O
3673,52,room,O
3674,52,which,O
3675,52,has,O
3676,52,everything,O
3677,52,you,O
3678,52,need,O
3679,52,.,O
3680,52,There,O
3681,52,is,O
3682,52,a,O
3683,52,nice,O
3684,52,and,O
3685,52,cozy,O
3686,52,area,O
3687,52,with,O
3688,52,kitchen,O
3689,52,and,O
3690,52,some,O
3691,52,tables,O
3692,52,.,O
3693,52,It,O
3694,52,is,O
3695,52,the,O
3696,52,perfect,O
3697,52,location,O
3698,52,to,O
3699,52,explore,O
3700,52,the,O
3701,52,amazing,O
3702,52,city,O
3703,52,.,O
3704,52,Defently,O
3705,52,would,O
3706,52,come,O
3707,52,back,O
3708,53,The,O
3709,53,location,O
3710,53,was,O
3711,53,great,O
3712,53,The,O
3713,53,apartment,O
3714,53,is,O
3715,53,placed,O
3716,53,right,O
3717,53,across,O
3718,53,the,O
3719,53,street,O
3720,53,from,O
3721,53,the,O
3722,53,Chinatown,B-gpe
3723,53,MRT,O
3724,53,station,O
3725,53,.,O
3726,53,There,O
3727,53,was,O
3728,53,so,O
3729,53,much,O
3730,53,to,O
3731,53,do,O
3732,53,in,O
3733,53,the,O
3734,53,immediate,O
3735,53,location,O
3736,53,in,O
3737,53,terms,O
3738,53,of,O
3739,53,restaurants,O
3740,53,",",O
3741,53,bars,O
3742,53,",",O
3743,53,and,O
3744,53,markets,O
3745,53,.,O
3746,53,It,O
3747,53,was,O
3748,53,also,O
3749,53,about,O
3750,53,a,O
3751,53,12,B-tim
3752,53,minute,I-tim
3753,53,walk,O
3754,53,or,O
3755,53,1,O
3756,53,2,O
3757,53,subway,O
3758,53,stops,O
3759,53,to,O
3760,53,Clarke,B-geo
3761,53,Quay,I-geo
3762,53,and,O
3763,53,about,O
3764,53,a,O
3765,53,20,B-tim
3766,53,minute,I-tim
3767,53,walk,O
3768,53,or,O
3769,53,2,O
3770,53,3,O
3771,53,subway,O
3772,53,stops,O
3773,53,to,O
3774,53,Marina,B-geo
3775,53,Bay,I-geo
3776,53,.,O
3777,53,The,O
3778,53,place,O
3779,53,itself,O
3780,53,was,O
3781,53,very,O
3782,53,spacious,O
3783,53,and,O
3784,53,clean,O
3785,53,",",O
3786,53,with,O
3787,53,a,O
3788,53,housekeeper,O
3789,53,coming,O
3790,53,by,O
3791,53,once,O
3792,53,during,O
3793,53,our,O
3794,53,week,O
3795,53,long,O
3796,53,stay,O
3797,53,to,O
3798,53,clean,O
3799,53,and,O
3800,53,replace,O
3801,53,our,O
3802,53,towels,O
3803,53,.,O
3804,53,Would,O
3805,53,highly,O
3806,53,recommend,O
3807,54,Great,O
3808,54,place,O
3809,54,to,O
3810,54,be,O
3811,54,if,O
3812,54,you,O
3813,54,want,O
3814,54,to,O
3815,54,be,O
3816,54,in,O
3817,54,the,O
3818,54,middle,O
3819,54,of,O
3820,54,various,O
3821,54,places,O
3822,54,in,O
3823,54,town,O
3824,54,like,O
3825,54,Clarke,B-geo
3826,54,Quay,I-geo
3827,54,",",O
3828,54,Bugis,B-geo
3829,54,",",O
3830,54,Orchard,B-geo
3831,54,by,O
3832,54,bus,O
3833,54,and,O
3834,54,Somerset,B-geo
3835,54,10,O
3836,54,15,B-tim
3837,54,minutes,I-tim
3838,54,walk,O
3839,54,.,O
3840,54,Had,O
3841,54,a,O
3842,54,comfortable,O
3843,54,stay,O
3844,54,otherwise,O
3845,55,Love,O
3846,55,the,O
3847,55,great,O
3848,55,location,O
3849,55,to,O
3850,55,all,O
3851,55,the,O
3852,55,convenience,O
3853,55,the,O
3854,55,surroundings,O
3855,55,had,O
3856,55,to,O
3857,55,offer,O
3858,55,.,O
3859,55,The,O
3860,55,nearby,O
3861,55,Lavender,B-geo
3862,55,MRT,O
3863,55,station,O
3864,55,and,O
3865,55,the,O
3866,55,great,O
3867,55,fun,O
3868,55,of,O
3869,55,Arab,B-gpe
3870,55,Street,I-gpe
3871,55,and,O
3872,55,Kampung,B-gpe
3873,55,Glam,I-gpe
3874,55,.,O
3875,55,Will,O
3876,55,sure,O
3877,55,think,O
3878,55,of,O
3879,55,SK,O
3880,55,is,O
3881,55,place,O
3882,55,when,O
3883,55,I,O
3884,55,am,O
3885,55,planning,O
3886,55,another,O
3887,55,trip,O
3888,55,to,O
3889,55,S,O
3890,55,pore,O
3891,55,.,O
3892,55,Thank,O
3893,55,you,O
3894,56,Perfect,O
3895,56,apartment,O
3896,56,for,O
3897,56,two,O
3898,56,people,O
3899,56,.,O
3900,56,Great,O
3901,56,location,O
3902,56,with,O
3903,56,Robertson,B-geo
3904,56,and,O
3905,56,Clarke,B-geo
3906,56,Quay,I-geo
3907,56,as,O
3908,56,well,O
3909,56,of,O
3910,56,Somerset,B-geo
3911,56,Metro,O
3912,56,Station,O
3913,56,only,O
3914,56,a,O
3915,56,short,O
3916,56,walk,O
3917,56,away,O
3918,56,.,O
3919,56,Would,O
3920,56,stay,O
3921,56,there,O
3922,56,again,O
3923,57,I,O
3924,57,love,O
3925,57,the,O
3926,57,place,O
3927,57,.,O
3928,57,Clean,O
3929,57,",",O
3930,57,quiet,O
3931,57,and,O
3932,57,the,O
3933,57,location,O
3934,57,is,O
3935,57,perfect,O
3936,57,.,O
3937,57,It,O
3938,57,just,O
3939,57,be,O
3940,57,a,O
3941,57,few,O
3942,57,stops,O
3943,57,to,O
3944,57,visit,O
3945,57,Little,B-gpe
3946,57,India,I-gpe
3947,57,",",O
3948,57,Santosa,B-geo
3949,57,",",O
3950,57,Clark,B-geo
3951,57,Quay,I-geo
3952,57,",",O
3953,57,etc,O
3954,57,.,O
3955,57,And,O
3956,57,the,O
3957,57,staff,O
3958,57,are,O
3959,57,really,O
3960,57,nice,O
3961,57,.,O
3962,57,Definitely,O
3963,57,I,O
3964,57,will,O
3965,57,come,O
3966,57,again,O
3967,57,.,O
3968,58,I,O
3969,58,was,O
3970,58,convenient,O
3971,58,for,O
3972,58,MRT,O
3973,58,station,O
3974,58,",",O
3975,58,so,O
3976,58,it,O
3977,58,was,O
3978,58,convenient,O
3979,58,for,O
3980,58,the,O
3981,58,mirror,O
3982,58,",",O
3983,58,than,O
3984,58,anything,O
3985,58,about,O
3986,58,the,O
3987,58,staff,O
3988,58,.,O
3989,58,I,O
3990,58,really,O
3991,58,liked,O
3992,58,it,O
3993,58,when,O
3994,58,I,O
3995,58,was,O
3996,58,smiling,O
3997,58,when,O
3998,58,communication,O
3999,58,is,O
4000,58,not,O
4001,58,smooth,O
4002,58,If,O
4003,58,the,O
4004,58,bed,O
4005,58,matrix,O
4006,58,was,O
4007,58,hard,O
4008,58,",",O
4009,58,he,O
4010,58,was,O
4011,58,worried,O
4012,58,about,O
4013,58,it,O
4014,58,",",O
4015,58,but,O
4016,58,it,O
4017,58,was,O
4018,58,really,O
4019,58,done,O
4020,58,every,O
4021,58,day,O
4022,58,.,O
4023,58,It,O
4024,58,was,O
4025,58,really,O
4026,58,good,O
4027,58,There,O
4028,58,is,O
4029,58,a,O
4030,58,lot,O
4031,58,of,O
4032,58,things,O
4033,58,that,O
4034,58,I,O
4035,58,have,O
4036,58,a,O
4037,58,great,O
4038,58,towel,O
4039,58,in,O
4040,58,the,O
4041,58,room,O
4042,58,",",O
4043,58,but,O
4044,58,I,O
4045,58,have,O
4046,58,to,O
4047,58,tell,O
4048,58,you,O
4049,58,when,O
4050,58,I,O
4051,58,replace,O
4052,58,it,O
4053,58,.,O
4054,58,I,O
4055,58,hope,O
4056,58,you,O
4057,58,will,O
4058,58,see,O
4059,58,the,O
4060,58,travel,O
4061,58,route,O
4062,58,on,O
4063,58,the,O
4064,58,center,O
4065,58,of,O
4066,58,Chinatown,B-gpe
4067,58,.,O
4068,58,Next,O
4069,58,",",O
4070,58,if,O
4071,58,you,O
4072,58,are,O
4073,58,in,O
4074,58,Singapore,B-geo
4075,58,",",O
4076,58,you,O
4077,58,will,O
4078,58,stay,O
4079,58,again,O
4080,59,I,O
4081,59,would,O
4082,59,like,O
4083,59,to,O
4084,59,recommend,O
4085,59,everyone,O
4086,59,to,O
4087,59,stay,O
4088,59,in,O
4089,59,Wu,O
4090,59,Daxia,O
4091,59,is,O
4092,59,house,O
4093,59,and,O
4094,59,thank,O
4095,59,you,O
4096,59,Thank,O
4097,59,you,O
4098,59,for,O
4099,59,your,O
4100,59,convenience,O
4101,59,of,O
4102,59,traveling,O
4103,59,us,O
4104,59,.,O
4105,59,Although,O
4106,59,the,O
4107,59,location,O
4108,59,of,O
4109,59,the,O
4110,59,house,O
4111,59,is,O
4112,59,not,O
4113,59,close,O
4114,59,to,O
4115,59,the,O
4116,59,subway,O
4117,59,",",O
4118,59,the,O
4119,59,bus,O
4120,59,around,O
4121,59,the,O
4122,59,truth,O
4123,59,is,O
4124,59,convenient,O
4125,59,",",O
4126,59,basically,O
4127,59,can,O
4128,59,be,O
4129,59,covered,O
4130,59,to,O
4131,59,all,O
4132,59,",",O
4133,59,and,O
4134,59,we,O
4135,59,will,O
4136,59,basically,O
4137,59,rely,O
4138,59,on,O
4139,59,the,O
4140,59,bus,O
4141,59,.,O
4142,59,Also,O
4143,59,thank,O
4144,59,the,O
4145,59,Heroes,O
4146,59,to,O
4147,59,provide,O
4148,59,the,O
4149,59,traffic,O
4150,59,card,O
4151,59,",",O
4152,59,just,O
4153,59,make,O
4154,59,the,O
4155,59,balance,O
4156,59,of,O
4157,59,the,O
4158,59,balance,O
4159,59,as,O
4160,59,long,O
4161,59,as,O
4162,59,it,O
4163,59,go,O
4164,59,back,O
4165,59,.,O
4166,59,The,O
4167,59,first,O
4168,59,two,O
4169,59,days,O
4170,59,of,O
4171,59,travel,O
4172,59,selection,O
4173,59,to,O
4174,59,Sentosa,B-geo
4175,59,",",O
4176,59,downstairs,O
4177,59,bus,O
4178,59,direct,O
4179,59,Vivocity,O
4180,59,and,O
4181,59,walk,O
4182,59,the,O
4183,59,cross,O
4184,59,sea,O
4185,59,trail,O
4186,59,can,O
4187,59,enter,O
4188,59,the,O
4189,59,island,O
4190,59,.,O
4191,59,After,O
4192,59,three,O
4193,59,days,O
4194,59,",",O
4195,59,we,O
4196,59,went,O
4197,59,to,O
4198,59,the,O
4199,59,bull,O
4200,59,is,O
4201,59,water,O
4202,59,small,O
4203,59,India,B-gpe
4204,59,Arab,B-gpe
4205,59,Street,I-gpe
4206,59,and,O
4207,59,other,O
4208,59,places,O
4209,59,Finally,O
4210,59,",",O
4211,59,I,O
4212,59,also,O
4213,59,prepared,O
4214,59,a,O
4215,59,big,O
4216,59,breakfast,O
4217,59,for,O
4218,59,us,O
4219,59,on,O
4220,59,that,O
4221,59,day,O
4222,59,Thank,O
4223,59,you,O
4224,59,for,O
4225,59,your,O
4226,59,help,O
4227,59,",",O
4228,59,you,O
4229,59,also,O
4230,59,welcome,O
4231,59,your,O
4232,59,own,O
4233,59,opportunity,O
4234,59,to,O
4235,59,come,O
4236,59,to,O
4237,59,Beijing,B-geo
4238,59,.,O
4239,60,Great,O
4240,60,host,O
4241,60,with,O
4242,60,a,O
4243,60,great,O
4244,60,flat,O
4245,60,and,O
4246,60,in,O
4247,60,an,O
4248,60,amazing,O
4249,60,location,O
4250,60,.,O
4251,60,Would,O
4252,60,recommend,O
4253,60,going,O
4254,60,to,O
4255,60,Tiong,B-geo
4256,60,Bahru,I-geo
4257,60,market,O
4258,60,for,O
4259,60,food,O
4260,60,.,O
4261,60,Would,O
4262,60,definitely,O
4263,60,recommend,O
4264,60,staying,O
4265,60,here,O
4266,61,Located,O
4267,61,30,B-tim
4268,61,minutes,I-tim
4269,61,from,O
4270,61,the,O
4271,61,airport,O
4272,61,and,O
4273,61,25,B-tim
4274,61,minutes,I-tim
4275,61,from,O
4276,61,Raffles,B-geo
4277,61,Place,I-geo
4278,61,transportation,O
4279,61,",",O
4280,61,this,O
4281,61,room,O
4282,61,is,O
4283,61,ideal,O
4284,61,for,O
4285,61,a,O
4286,61,trip,O
4287,61,to,O
4288,61,the,O
4289,61,heart,O
4290,61,of,O
4291,61,the,O
4292,61,city,O
4293,61,for,O
4294,61,a,O
4295,61,price,O
4296,61,more,O
4297,61,than,O
4298,61,reasonable,O
4299,62,Great,O
4300,62,location,O
4301,62,apart,O
4302,62,from,O
4303,62,building,O
4304,62,works,O
4305,62,all,O
4306,62,around,O
4307,62,",",O
4308,62,short,O
4309,62,walks,O
4310,62,to,O
4311,62,Downtown,O
4312,62,",",O
4313,62,Little,B-gpe
4314,62,Arabia,I-gpe
4315,62,",",O
4316,62,Little,B-gpe
4317,62,India,I-gpe
4318,62,and,O
4319,62,MRT,O
4320,62,Bugis,B-geo
4321,62,.,O
4322,62,Apartment,O
4323,62,is,O
4324,62,pretty,O
4325,62,standard,O
4326,62,especially,O
4327,62,compared,O
4328,62,to,O
4329,62,the,O
4330,62,fancy,O
4331,62,photo,O
4332,62,is,O
4333,62,",",O
4334,62,but,O
4335,62,facilities,O
4336,62,are,O
4337,62,good,O
4338,62,it,O
4339,62,even,O
4340,62,includes,O
4341,62,a,O
4342,62,massage,O
4343,62,chair,O
4344,62,Shared,O
4345,62,bathroom,O
4346,62,with,O
4347,62,multiple,O
4348,62,rooms,O
4349,62,is,O
4350,62,a,O
4351,62,bit,O
4352,62,of,O
4353,62,a,O
4354,62,hassle,O
4355,62,.,O
4356,62,Recommended,O
4357,63,This,O
4358,63,is,O
4359,63,my,O
4360,63,2nd,O
4361,63,time,O
4362,63,at,O
4363,63,Alex,B-per
4364,63,is,O
4365,63,unit,O
4366,63,.,O
4367,63,Great,O
4368,63,location,O
4369,63,fantastic,O
4370,63,value,O
4371,63,for,O
4372,63,money,O
4373,63,.,O
4374,63,Very,O
4375,63,clean,O
4376,63,short,O
4377,63,walk,O
4378,63,to,O
4379,63,Orchard,B-org
4380,63,Central,I-org
4381,63,.,O
4382,63,Thank,O
4383,63,you,O
4384,64,If,O
4385,64,you,O
4386,64,are,O
4387,64,lucky,O
4388,64,enough,O
4389,64,to,O
4390,64,get,O
4391,64,a,O
4392,64,room,O
4393,64,at,O
4394,64,this,O
4395,64,location,O
4396,64,you,O
4397,64,will,O
4398,64,have,O
4399,64,a,O
4400,64,great,O
4401,64,stay,O
4402,64,in,O
4403,64,Singapore,B-geo
4404,64,.,O
4405,64,The,O
4406,64,lofts,O
4407,64,are,O
4408,64,incredible,O
4409,64,really,O
4410,64,makes,O
4411,64,you,O
4412,64,feel,O
4413,64,like,O
4414,64,you,O
4415,64,are,O
4416,64,in,O
4417,64,Singapore,B-geo
4418,64,is,O
4419,64,Chinatown,B-gpe
4420,64,.,O
4421,64,Not,O
4422,64,only,O
4423,64,would,O
4424,64,I,O
4425,64,say,O
4426,64,here,O
4427,64,again,O
4428,64,",",O
4429,64,I,O
4430,64,have,O
4431,64,already,O
4432,64,booked,O
4433,64,for,O
4434,64,my,O
4435,64,next,O
4436,64,trip,O
4437,64,.,O
4438,64,Absolutely,O
4439,64,excellent,O
4440,64,.,O
4441,65,The,O
4442,65,flat,O
4443,65,is,O
4444,65,spacious,O
4445,65,regarding,O
4446,65,Singspore,O
4447,65,standard,O
4448,65,and,O
4449,65,especially,O
4450,65,compared,O
4451,65,to,O
4452,65,standard,O
4453,65,hotel,O
4454,65,rooms,O
4455,65,with,O
4456,65,a,O
4457,65,separate,O
4458,65,bathroom,O
4459,65,for,O
4460,65,each,O
4461,65,bedroom,O
4462,65,.,O
4463,65,The,O
4464,65,flat,O
4465,65,is,O
4466,65,very,O
4467,65,quiet,O
4468,65,and,O
4469,65,closely,O
4470,65,located,O
4471,65,to,O
4472,65,the,O
4473,65,MRT,O
4474,65,station,O
4475,65,Farrer,B-geo
4476,65,Park,I-geo
4477,65,3,O
4478,65,min,O
4479,65,.,O
4480,65,walking,O
4481,65,distance,O
4482,65,and,O
4483,65,therefore,O
4484,65,you,O
4485,65,can,O
4486,65,get,O
4487,65,to,O
4488,65,the,O
4489,65,down,O
4490,65,town,O
4491,65,area,O
4492,65,quickly,O
4493,65,.,O
4494,65,Lulu,O
4495,65,handed,O
4496,65,over,O
4497,65,the,O
4498,65,keys,O
4499,65,personally,O
4500,65,and,O
4501,65,responded,O
4502,65,instantly,O
4503,65,in,O
4504,65,case,O
4505,65,of,O
4506,65,questions,O
4507,65,via,O
4508,65,Hidden,O
4509,65,by,O
4510,65,Airbnb,B-org
4511,65,.,O
4512,65,Just,O
4513,65,around,O
4514,65,the,O
4515,65,corner,O
4516,65,we,O
4517,65,found,O
4518,65,several,O
4519,65,nice,O
4520,65,cafes,O
4521,65,for,O
4522,65,breakfast,O
4523,65,",",O
4524,65,e,O
4525,65,.g,O
4526,65,.,O
4527,65,brunches,O
4528,65,.,O
4529,66,Darrick,B-per
4530,66,s,O
4531,66,place,O
4532,66,is,O
4533,66,exactly,O
4534,66,as,O
4535,66,advertised,O
4536,66,.,O
4537,66,Great,O
4538,66,location,O
4539,66,only,O
4540,66,20min,O
4541,66,walk,O
4542,66,to,O
4543,66,Orchard,B-geo
4544,66,and,O
4545,66,also,O
4546,66,close,O
4547,66,with,O
4548,66,other,O
4549,66,tourist,O
4550,66,spots,O
4551,66,in,O
4552,66,the,O
4553,66,city,O
4554,66,",",O
4555,66,great,O
4556,66,amenities,O
4557,66,",",O
4558,66,and,O
4559,66,most,O
4560,66,importantly,O
4561,66,the,O
4562,66,space,O
4563,66,is,O
4564,66,really,O
4565,66,clean,O
4566,66,and,O
4567,66,comfortable,O
4568,66,for,O
4569,66,resting,O
4570,66,after,O
4571,66,long,O
4572,66,day,O
4573,66,of,O
4574,66,travel,O
4575,66,.,O
4576,66,Will,O
4577,66,definitely,O
4578,66,book,O
4579,66,the,O
4580,66,place,O
4581,66,for,O
4582,66,our,O
4583,66,next,O
4584,66,visit,O
4585,67,Great,O
4586,67,place,O
4587,67,to,O
4588,67,stay,O
4589,67,overall,O
4590,67,.,O
4591,67,There,O
4592,67,is,O
4593,67,an,O
4594,67,entire,O
4595,67,shopping,O
4596,67,centre,O
4597,67,downstairs,O
4598,67,.,O
4599,67,The,O
4600,67,MRT,O
4601,67,is,O
4602,67,literally,O
4603,67,20m,O
4604,67,away,O
4605,67,",",O
4606,67,buses,O
4607,67,stop,O
4608,67,outside,O
4609,67,",",O
4610,67,and,O
4611,67,there,O
4612,67,is,O
4613,67,several,O
4614,67,ATMs,O
4615,67,right,O
4616,67,outside,O
4617,67,the,O
4618,67,front,O
4619,67,door,O
4620,67,.,O
4621,67,I,O
4622,67,would,O
4623,67,often,O
4624,67,walk,O
4625,67,into,O
4626,67,town,O
4627,67,because,O
4628,67,everything,O
4629,67,was,O
4630,67,relatively,O
4631,67,close,O
4632,67,.,O
4633,67,There,O
4634,67,are,O
4635,67,not,O
4636,67,many,O
4637,67,halal,O
4638,67,food,O
4639,67,options,O
4640,67,in,O
4641,67,Chinatown,B-gpe
4642,67,",",O
4643,67,but,O
4644,67,good,O
4645,67,halal,O
4646,67,food,O
4647,67,is,O
4648,67,just,O
4649,67,1km,O
4650,67,away,O
4651,67,",",O
4652,67,and,O
4653,67,with,O
4654,67,the,O
4655,67,MRT,O
4656,67,being,O
4657,67,so,O
4658,67,close,O
4659,67,",",O
4660,67,everything,O
4661,67,was,O
4662,67,very,O
4663,67,easily,O
4664,67,accessible,O
4665,67,.,O
4666,68,The,O
4667,68,Han,O
4668,68,apartment,O
4669,68,is,O
4670,68,an,O
4671,68,ideal,O
4672,68,starting,O
4673,68,point,O
4674,68,to,O
4675,68,Chinatown,B-gpe
4676,68,and,O
4677,68,is,O
4678,68,within,O
4679,68,walking,O
4680,68,distance,O
4681,68,to,O
4682,68,the,O
4683,68,nearest,O
4684,68,metro,O
4685,68,station,O
4686,68,10,O
4687,68,15min,O
4688,68,.,O
4689,68,There,O
4690,68,was,O
4691,68,also,O
4692,68,the,O
4693,68,possibility,O
4694,68,to,O
4695,68,park,O
4696,68,the,O
4697,68,luggage,O
4698,68,after,O
4699,68,registration,O
4700,68,on,O
4701,68,the,O
4702,68,day,O
4703,68,of,O
4704,68,arrival,O
4705,68,or,O
4706,68,before,O
4707,68,departure,O
4708,68,at,O
4709,68,Han,O
4710,68,.,O
4711,68,Chic,O
4712,68,apartment,O
4713,68,",",O
4714,68,slightly,O
4715,68,small,O
4716,68,but,O
4717,68,sufficient,O
4718,68,enough,O
4719,68,for,O
4720,68,2,O
4721,68,persons,O
4722,68,.,O
4723,68,Gladly,O
4724,68,again,O
4725,68,in,O
4726,68,Singapore,B-geo
4727,69,Thank,O
4728,69,u,O
4729,69,Ben,O
4730,69,we,O
4731,69,have,O
4732,69,a,O
4733,69,great,O
4734,69,week,O
4735,69,in,O
4736,69,Singapore,B-geo
4737,69,.,O
4738,69,The,O
4739,69,whole,O
4740,69,place,O
4741,69,is,O
4742,69,clean,O
4743,69,n,O
4744,69,cozy,O
4745,69,.,O
4746,69,MRT,O
4747,69,just,O
4748,69,10,O
4749,69,mins,O
4750,69,walking,O
4751,69,from,O
4752,69,the,O
4753,69,place,O
4754,69,and,O
4755,69,we,O
4756,69,could,O
4757,69,have,O
4758,69,meal,O
4759,69,in,O
4760,69,Clark,B-geo
4761,69,Quay,I-geo
4762,69,.,O
4763,69,You,O
4764,69,can,O
4765,69,even,O
4766,69,walk,O
4767,69,to,O
4768,69,Orchard,B-geo
4769,69,.,O
4770,69,There,O
4771,69,is,O
4772,69,a,O
4773,69,very,O
4774,69,nice,O
4775,69,playground,O
4776,69,near,O
4777,69,the,O
4778,69,place,O
4779,69,",",O
4780,69,let,O
4781,69,us,O
4782,69,find,O
4783,69,out,O
4784,69,.,O
4785,70,Interesting,O
4786,70,concept,O
4787,70,of,O
4788,70,living,O
4789,70,room,O
4790,70,and,O
4791,70,bedroom,O
4792,70,here,O
4793,70,.,O
4794,70,Clean,O
4795,70,room,O
4796,70,and,O
4797,70,good,O
4798,70,aircon,O
4799,70,.,O
4800,70,On,O
4801,70,the,O
4802,70,highest,O
4803,70,floor,O
4804,70,of,O
4805,70,Chinatown,B-gpe
4806,70,apartment,O
4807,70,here,O
4808,70,right,O
4809,70,above,O
4810,70,Chinatown,B-gpe
4811,70,MRT,O
4812,70,means,O
4813,70,great,O
4814,70,convenience,O
4815,70,and,O
4816,70,well,O
4817,70,connected,O
4818,70,to,O
4819,70,any,O
4820,70,part,O
4821,70,of,O
4822,70,Singapore,B-geo
4823,70,.,O
4824,70,Security,O
4825,70,on,O
4826,70,the,O
4827,70,ground,O
4828,70,floor,O
4829,70,offers,O
4830,70,some,O
4831,70,friendly,O
4832,70,security,O
4833,70,.,O
4834,70,Plenty,O
4835,70,of,O
4836,70,budget,O
4837,70,friendly,O
4838,70,food,O
4839,70,24hrs,O
4840,70,nearby,O
4841,70,here,O
4842,70,works,O
4843,70,for,O
4844,70,us,O
4845,70,or,O
4846,70,anyone,O
4847,70,.,O
4848,70,check,O
4849,70,in,O
4850,70,was,O
4851,70,self,O
4852,70,DIY,O
4853,70,and,O
4854,70,works,O
4855,70,well,O
4856,70,.,O
4857,70,communications,O
4858,70,mainly,O
4859,70,via,O
4860,70,messaging,O
4861,70,to,O
4862,70,host,O
4863,70,and,O
4864,70,works,O
4865,70,pretty,O
4866,70,well,O
4867,71,Great,O
4868,71,place,O
4869,71,.,O
4870,71,Near,O
4871,71,to,O
4872,71,Chinatown,B-gpe
4873,71,MRT,O
4874,71,",",O
4875,71,lots,O
4876,71,of,O
4877,71,good,O
4878,71,food,O
4879,71,nearby,O
4880,71,as,O
4881,71,well,O
4882,71,.,O
4883,71,Perfect,O
4884,71,for,O
4885,71,backpacking,O
4886,71,travellers,O
4887,71,.,O
4888,72,Good,O
4889,72,base,O
4890,72,for,O
4891,72,exploring,O
4892,72,Singapore,B-geo
4893,72,for,O
4894,72,a,O
4895,72,few,O
4896,72,days,O
4897,72,.,O
4898,72,Walking,O
4899,72,distance,O
4900,72,to,O
4901,72,the,O
4902,72,MRT,O
4903,72,and,O
4904,72,you,O
4905,72,can,O
4906,72,rent,O
4907,72,bikes,O
4908,72,nearby,O
4909,72,to,O
4910,72,cycle,O
4911,72,down,O
4912,72,to,O
4913,72,East,B-geo
4914,72,Coast,I-geo
4915,72,Park,I-geo
4916,72,.,O
4917,72,The,O
4918,72,apartment,O
4919,72,is,O
4920,72,very,O
4921,72,small,O
4922,72,and,O
4923,72,basic,O
4924,72,but,O
4925,72,with,O
4926,72,great,O
4927,72,infinity,O
4928,72,pool,O
4929,72,on,O
4930,72,the,O
4931,72,roof,O
4932,72,with,O
4933,72,views,O
4934,72,of,O
4935,72,the,O
4936,72,city,O
4937,72,.,O
4938,72,The,O
4939,72,gym,O
4940,72,is,O
4941,72,a,O
4942,72,box,O
4943,72,and,O
4944,72,not,O
4945,72,really,O
4946,72,usable,O
4947,72,.,O
4948,72,I,O
4949,72,would,O
4950,72,stay,O
4951,72,here,O
4952,72,again,O
4953,72,though,O
4954,72,.,O
4955,73,Ben,O
4956,73,is,O
4957,73,a,O
4958,73,considerate,O
4959,73,and,O
4960,73,accommodating,O
4961,73,young,O
4962,73,host,O
4963,73,his,O
4964,73,place,O
4965,73,is,O
4966,73,almost,O
4967,73,ideal,O
4968,73,because,O
4969,73,it,O
4970,73,is,O
4971,73,only,O
4972,73,a,O
4973,73,3,B-tim
4974,73,min,I-tim
4975,73,walk,O
4976,73,from,O
4977,73,the,O
4978,73,place,O
4979,73,I,O
4980,73,have,O
4981,73,to,O
4982,73,be,O
4983,73,everyday,O
4984,73,for,O
4985,73,a,O
4986,73,week,O
4987,73,He,O
4988,73,is,O
4989,73,indeed,O
4990,73,very,O
4991,73,thoughtful,O
4992,73,in,O
4993,73,his,O
4994,73,own,O
4995,73,ways,O
4996,73,and,O
4997,73,I,O
4998,73,am,O
4999,73,very,O
5000,73,thankful,O
5001,73,",",O
5002,73,indeed,O
5003,73,Even,O
5004,73,though,O
5005,73,the,O
5006,73,room,O
5007,73,and,O
5008,73,bathroom,O
5009,73,is,O
5010,73,small,O
5011,73,",",O
5012,73,it,O
5013,73,is,O
5014,73,clean,O
5015,73,and,O
5016,73,comfortable,O
5017,73,enough,O
5018,73,and,O
5019,73,the,O
5020,73,hot,O
5021,73,water,O
5022,73,shower,O
5023,73,works,O
5024,73,Even,O
5025,73,though,O
5026,73,I,O
5027,73,am,O
5028,73,not,O
5029,73,there,O
5030,73,for,O
5031,73,any,O
5032,73,sightseeing,O
5033,73,or,O
5034,73,shopping,O
5035,73,spots,O
5036,73,but,O
5037,73,the,O
5038,73,location,O
5039,73,looks,O
5040,73,really,O
5041,73,close,O
5042,73,to,O
5043,73,Clarke,B-geo
5044,73,Quay,I-geo
5045,73,and,O
5046,73,Orchard,B-geo
5047,73,with,O
5048,73,walking,O
5049,73,distance,O
5050,73,bus,O
5051,73,stops,O
5052,73,and,O
5053,73,MRT,O
5054,73,station,O
5055,73,.,O
5056,74,Great,O
5057,74,amenities,O
5058,74,.,O
5059,74,Quiet,O
5060,74,neighbourhood,O
5061,74,",",O
5062,74,yet,O
5063,74,still,O
5064,74,a,O
5065,74,lot,O
5066,74,of,O
5067,74,happenings,O
5068,74,nearby,O
5069,74,.,O
5070,74,The,O
5071,74,Studio,O
5072,74,is,O
5073,74,within,O
5074,74,10,B-tim
5075,74,minutes,I-tim
5076,74,walk,O
5077,74,of,O
5078,74,the,O
5079,74,MRT,O
5080,74,",",O
5081,74,and,O
5082,74,Supermarkets,O
5083,74,.,O
5084,74,Tiong,B-geo
5085,74,Bahru,I-geo
5086,74,Hawker,O
5087,74,is,O
5088,74,closer,O
5089,74,still,O
5090,74,.,O
5091,74,Recently,O
5092,74,renovated,O
5093,74,",",O
5094,74,modern,O
5095,74,decor,O
5096,74,.,O
5097,74,Nothing,O
5098,74,to,O
5099,74,worry,O
5100,74,about,O
5101,74,staying,O
5102,74,here,O
5103,74,.,O
5104,75,Very,O
5105,75,kind,O
5106,75,host,O
5107,75,",",O
5108,75,Lucinda,B-per
5109,75,was,O
5110,75,very,O
5111,75,fast,O
5112,75,responding,O
5113,75,and,O
5114,75,accommodating,O
5115,75,.,O
5116,75,The,O
5117,75,space,O
5118,75,was,O
5119,75,clean,O
5120,75,",",O
5121,75,the,O
5122,75,beds,O
5123,75,were,O
5124,75,comfortable,O
5125,75,and,O
5126,75,we,O
5127,75,had,O
5128,75,a,O
5129,75,great,O
5130,75,stay,O
5131,75,.,O
5132,75,The,O
5133,75,location,O
5134,75,is,O
5135,75,perfect,O
5136,75,walking,O
5137,75,distance,O
5138,75,from,O
5139,75,the,O
5140,75,Marina,B-geo
5141,75,Bay,I-geo
5142,75,area,O
5143,75,",",O
5144,75,the,O
5145,75,Bugis,B-geo
5146,75,Market,O
5147,75,and,O
5148,75,many,O
5149,75,great,O
5150,75,restaurants,O
5151,75,and,O
5152,75,hawker,O
5153,75,centers,O
5154,75,.,O
5155,75,Will,O
5156,75,recommend,O
5157,75,to,O
5158,75,anyone,O
5159,76,Super,O
5160,76,affordable,O
5161,76,and,O
5162,76,in,O
5163,76,a,O
5164,76,great,O
5165,76,part,O
5166,76,of,O
5167,76,town,O
5168,76,",",O
5169,76,Arab,B-gpe
5170,76,Street,I-gpe
5171,76,is,O
5172,76,a,O
5173,76,personal,O
5174,76,fave,O
5175,76,of,O
5176,76,mine,O
5177,76,for,O
5178,76,food,O
5179,76,and,O
5180,76,Bugis,B-geo
5181,76,MRT,O
5182,76,is,O
5183,76,a,O
5184,76,5,B-tim
5185,76,minute,I-tim
5186,76,walk,O
5187,76,away,O
5188,76,.,O
5189,77,I,O
5190,77,love,O
5191,77,the,O
5192,77,room,O
5193,77,",",O
5194,77,it,O
5195,77,is,O
5196,77,spacious,O
5197,77,",",O
5198,77,clean,O
5199,77,",",O
5200,77,and,O
5201,77,has,O
5202,77,excellent,O
5203,77,private,O
5204,77,green,O
5205,77,views,O
5206,77,.,O
5207,77,The,O
5208,77,location,O
5209,77,cannot,O
5210,77,be,O
5211,77,better,O
5212,77,",",O
5213,77,just,O
5214,77,walking,O
5215,77,distance,O
5216,77,to,O
5217,77,Sommerset,B-geo
5218,77,and,O
5219,77,Orchard,B-geo
5220,77,Road,I-geo
5221,77,.,O
5222,77,Travelling,O
5223,77,from,O
5224,77,the,O
5225,77,airport,O
5226,77,is,O
5227,77,easy,O
5228,77,",",O
5229,77,I,O
5230,77,took,O
5231,77,the,O
5232,77,Downtown,O
5233,77,Line,O
5234,77,to,O
5235,77,Fort,B-geo
5236,77,Canning,I-geo
5237,77,Park,I-geo
5238,77,and,O
5239,77,walk,O
5240,77,about,O
5241,77,10,B-tim
5242,77,minutes,I-tim
5243,77,to,O
5244,77,reach,O
5245,77,the,O
5246,77,house,O
5247,77,.,O
5248,77,The,O
5249,77,whole,O
5250,77,journey,O
5251,77,took,O
5252,77,only,O
5253,77,about,O
5254,77,45,B-tim
5255,77,minutes,I-tim
5256,77,and,O
5257,77,around,O
5258,77,2,O
5259,77,dollars,O
5260,77,.,O
5261,77,The,O
5262,77,hosts,O
5263,77,were,O
5264,77,very,O
5265,77,friendly,O
5266,77,and,O
5267,77,also,O
5268,77,respect,O
5269,77,guest,O
5270,77,is,O
5271,77,privacy,O
5272,77,.,O
5273,77,Highly,O
5274,77,recommend,O
5275,77,this,O
5276,77,place,O
5277,77,.,O
5278,78,In,O
5279,78,STUDIOS,O
5280,78,",",O
5281,78,I,O
5282,78,lived,O
5283,78,for,O
5284,78,6,O
5285,78,nights,O
5286,78,.,O
5287,78,I,O
5288,78,saw,O
5289,78,comments,O
5290,78,before,O
5291,78,I,O
5292,78,came,O
5293,78,to,O
5294,78,the,O
5295,78,house,O
5296,78,.,O
5297,78,I,O
5298,78,said,O
5299,78,that,O
5300,78,I,O
5301,78,was,O
5302,78,very,O
5303,78,close,O
5304,78,to,O
5305,78,the,O
5306,78,subway,O
5307,78,station,O
5308,78,.,O
5309,78,The,O
5310,78,small,O
5311,78,house,O
5312,78,was,O
5313,78,surprised,O
5314,78,.,O
5315,78,It,O
5316,78,is,O
5317,78,TRUE,O
5318,78,.,O
5319,78,It,O
5320,78,is,O
5321,78,really,O
5322,78,right,O
5323,78,It,O
5324,78,takes,O
5325,78,about,O
5326,78,40,O
5327,78,minutes,O
5328,78,from,O
5329,78,the,O
5330,78,airport,O
5331,78,past,O
5332,78,House,O
5333,78,",",O
5334,78,to,O
5335,78,Jalan,B-geo
5336,78,Besar,I-geo
5337,78,is,O
5338,78,BESAR,O
5339,78,is,O
5340,78,out,O
5341,78,of,O
5342,78,the,O
5343,78,right,O
5344,78,side,O
5345,78,of,O
5346,78,100,O
5347,78,meters,O
5348,78,",",O
5349,78,there,O
5350,78,is,O
5351,78,small,B-gpe
5352,78,India,I-gpe
5353,78,",",O
5354,78,24,O
5355,78,hour,O
5356,78,mall,O
5357,78,",",O
5358,78,late,O
5359,78,street,O
5360,78,",",O
5361,78,etc,O
5362,78,.,O
5363,78,We,O
5364,78,stay,O
5365,78,",",O
5366,78,the,O
5367,78,landlord,O
5368,78,is,O
5369,78,still,O
5370,78,very,O
5371,78,detailed,O
5372,78,introduction,O
5373,78,House,O
5374,78,",",O
5375,78,give,O
5376,78,me,O
5377,78,a,O
5378,78,boyfriend,O
5379,78,on,O
5380,78,the,O
5381,78,map,O
5382,78,.,O
5383,78,It,O
5384,78,is,O
5385,78,too,O
5386,78,grateful,O
5387,78,to,O
5388,78,the,O
5389,78,nearby,O
5390,78,attractions,O
5391,78,and,O
5392,78,lines,O
5393,78,.,O
5394,78,It,O
5395,78,is,O
5396,78,a,O
5397,78,good,O
5398,78,time,O
5399,78,The,O
5400,78,faucet,O
5401,78,can,O
5402,78,be,O
5403,78,directly,O
5404,78,drinked,O
5405,78,",",O
5406,78,configure,O
5407,78,a,O
5408,78,small,O
5409,78,balcony,O
5410,78,",",O
5411,78,but,O
5412,78,there,O
5413,78,is,O
5414,78,no,O
5415,78,position,O
5416,78,outside,O
5417,78,the,O
5418,78,balcony,O
5419,78,and,O
5420,78,rope,O
5421,78,to,O
5422,78,dry,O
5423,78,clothes,O
5424,78,",",O
5425,78,and,O
5426,78,find,O
5427,78,that,O
5428,78,there,O
5429,78,is,O
5430,78,almost,O
5431,78,no,O
5432,78,one,O
5433,78,is,O
5434,78,drying,O
5435,78,outside,O
5436,78,",",O
5437,78,so,O
5438,78,be,O
5439,78,careful,O
5440,78,The,O
5441,78,big,O
5442,78,wind,O
5443,78,will,O
5444,78,blow,O
5445,78,away,O
5446,78,the,O
5447,78,clothes,O
5448,78,There,O
5449,78,is,O
5450,78,also,O
5451,78,yourself,O
5452,78,with,O
5453,78,a,O
5454,78,brush,O
5455,78,",",O
5456,78,it,O
5457,78,is,O
5458,78,necessary,O
5459,78,.,O
5460,78,I,O
5461,78,hope,O
5462,78,everyone,O
5463,78,is,O
5464,78,a,O
5465,78,pleasant,O
5466,78,journey,O
5467,79,Very,O
5468,79,cosy,O
5469,79,and,O
5470,79,clean,O
5471,79,apartment,O
5472,79,.,O
5473,79,The,O
5474,79,location,O
5475,79,is,O
5476,79,great,O
5477,79,",",O
5478,79,quiet,O
5479,79,neighbourhood,O
5480,79,between,O
5481,79,the,O
5482,79,Orchard,B-geo
5483,79,road,I-geo
5484,79,and,O
5485,79,Little,B-gpe
5486,79,India,I-gpe
5487,79,so,O
5488,79,it,O
5489,79,is,O
5490,79,easy,O
5491,79,to,O
5492,79,get,O
5493,79,anywhere,O
5494,79,.,O
5495,79,I,O
5496,79,recommend,O
5497,79,staying,O
5498,79,here,O
5499,80,This,O
5500,80,is,O
5501,80,a,O
5502,80,good,O
5503,80,value,O
5504,80,for,O
5505,80,your,O
5506,80,money,O
5507,80,.,O
5508,80,Cannot,O
5509,80,ask,O
5510,80,for,O
5511,80,a,O
5512,80,better,O
5513,80,location,O
5514,80,since,O
5515,80,Little,B-gpe
5516,80,India,I-gpe
5517,80,",",O
5518,80,Mustafa,B-org
5519,80,Center,I-org
5520,80,and,O
5521,80,the,O
5522,80,Circle,O
5523,80,Line,O
5524,80,Mall,O
5525,80,is,O
5526,80,within,O
5527,80,walking,O
5528,80,distance,O
5529,80,.,O
5530,80,Everything,O
5531,80,was,O
5532,80,so,O
5533,80,convenient,O
5534,80,.,O
5535,80,Besides,O
5536,80,actually,O
5537,80,getting,O
5538,80,into,O
5539,80,the,O
5540,80,place,O
5541,80,initially,O
5542,80,we,O
5543,80,had,O
5544,80,no,O
5545,80,issues,O
5546,80,.,O
5547,80,The,O
5548,80,Indian,B-gpe
5549,80,stand,O
5550,80,downstairs,O
5551,80,is,O
5552,80,awesome,O
5553,80,Fresh,O
5554,80,orange,O
5555,80,juice,O
5556,80,vending,O
5557,80,machine,O
5558,80,is,O
5559,80,a,O
5560,80,plus,O
5561,80,.,O
5562,81,Very,O
5563,81,good,O
5564,81,location,O
5565,81,",",O
5566,81,walking,O
5567,81,distance,O
5568,81,from,O
5569,81,Bugis,B-geo
5570,81,MRT,O
5571,81,and,O
5572,81,other,O
5573,81,key,O
5574,81,places,O
5575,81,of,O
5576,81,interest,O
5577,81,.,O
5578,81,Was,O
5579,81,right,O
5580,81,next,O
5581,81,door,O
5582,81,to,O
5583,81,the,O
5584,81,National,B-org
5585,81,Design,I-org
5586,81,Gallery,I-org
5587,81,",",O
5588,81,where,O
5589,81,I,O
5590,81,wanted,O
5591,81,to,O
5592,81,go,O
5593,81,Very,O
5594,81,friendly,O
5595,81,roommates,O
5596,81,",",O
5597,81,and,O
5598,81,clean,O
5599,81,bathrooms,O
5600,81,.,O
5601,81,The,O
5602,81,only,O
5603,81,issue,O
5604,81,happened,O
5605,81,when,O
5606,81,I,O
5607,81,found,O
5608,81,a,O
5609,81,puddle,O
5610,81,of,O
5611,81,water,O
5612,81,in,O
5613,81,the,O
5614,81,room,O
5615,81,after,O
5616,81,my,O
5617,81,first,O
5618,81,night,O
5619,81,staying,O
5620,81,there,O
5621,81,due,O
5622,81,to,O
5623,81,aircond,O
5624,81,leaking,O
5625,81,",",O
5626,81,but,O
5627,81,it,O
5628,81,was,O
5629,81,swiftly,O
5630,81,dealt,O
5631,81,with,O
5632,81,.,O
5633,82,Rooms,O
5634,82,were,O
5635,82,clean,O
5636,82,",",O
5637,82,air,O
5638,82,conditioned,O
5639,82,.,O
5640,82,One,O
5641,82,I,O
5642,82,was,O
5643,82,allocated,O
5644,82,had,O
5645,82,3,O
5646,82,bunk,O
5647,82,beds,O
5648,82,.,O
5649,82,Bathrooms,O
5650,82,were,O
5651,82,well,O
5652,82,maintained,O
5653,82,.,O
5654,82,Roommates,O
5655,82,were,O
5656,82,good,O
5657,82,.,O
5658,82,Breakfast,O
5659,82,a,O
5660,82,bonus,O
5661,82,.,O
5662,82,Little,B-gpe
5663,82,India,I-gpe
5664,82,MRT,O
5665,82,station,O
5666,82,is,O
5667,82,very,O
5668,82,close,O
5669,82,",",O
5670,82,less,O
5671,82,than,O
5672,82,3min,O
5673,82,walk,O
5674,82,.,O
5675,82,Rochor,B-geo
5676,82,station,O
5677,82,for,O
5678,82,Downtown,O
5679,82,line,O
5680,82,is,O
5681,82,very,O
5682,82,close,O
5683,82,.,O
5684,82,Bugis,B-geo
5685,82,area,O
5686,82,is,O
5687,82,walking,O
5688,82,distance,O
5689,82,and,O
5690,82,all,O
5691,82,major,O
5692,82,places,O
5693,82,are,O
5694,82,readily,O
5695,82,accessible,O
5696,82,.,O
5697,82,Staff,O
5698,82,were,O
5699,82,helpful,O
5700,82,generally,O
5701,82,.,O
5702,82,Overall,O
5703,82,a,O
5704,82,good,O
5705,82,experience,O
5706,82,.,O
5707,82,I,O
5708,82,recommend,O
5709,83,Nancy,B-per
5710,83,is,O
5711,83,quaint,O
5712,83,little,O
5713,83,place,O
5714,83,near,O
5715,83,Farrer,B-geo
5716,83,Park,I-geo
5717,83,is,O
5718,83,a,O
5719,83,good,O
5720,83,place,O
5721,83,to,O
5722,83,use,O
5723,83,as,O
5724,83,your,O
5725,83,base,O
5726,83,when,O
5727,83,exploring,O
5728,83,Singapore,B-geo
5729,83,.,O
5730,83,It,O
5731,83,is,O
5732,83,accessible,O
5733,83,and,O
5734,83,sits,O
5735,83,on,O
5736,83,a,O
5737,83,quiet,O
5738,83,little,O
5739,83,neighborhood,O
5740,83,.,O
5741,83,The,O
5742,83,room,O
5743,83,itself,O
5744,83,is,O
5745,83,very,O
5746,83,quaint,O
5747,83,.,O
5748,83,Especially,O
5749,83,loveed,O
5750,83,the,O
5751,83,wall,O
5752,83,mirror,O
5753,83,.,O
5754,83,Best,O
5755,83,of,O
5756,83,all,O
5757,83,",",O
5758,83,however,O
5759,83,",",O
5760,83,is,O
5761,83,Nancy,B-per
5762,83,herself,O
5763,83,She,O
5764,83,is,O
5765,83,very,O
5766,83,communicative,O
5767,83,and,O
5768,83,replies,O
5769,83,very,O
5770,83,promptly,O
5771,83,It,O
5772,83,was,O
5773,83,such,O
5774,83,a,O
5775,83,joy,O
5776,83,to,O
5777,83,have,O
5778,83,her,O
5779,83,as,O
5780,83,our,O
5781,83,host,O
5782,84,The,O
5783,84,place,O
5784,84,is,O
5785,84,so,O
5786,84,near,O
5787,84,to,O
5788,84,Chinatown,B-gpe
5789,84,MRT,O
5790,84,Exit,O
5791,84,D,O
5792,84,.,O
5793,84,There,O
5794,84,are,O
5795,84,also,O
5796,84,a,O
5797,84,lot,O
5798,84,of,O
5799,84,good,O
5800,84,food,O
5801,84,around,O
5802,84,.,O
5803,84,But,O
5804,84,the,O
5805,84,only,O
5806,84,thing,O
5807,84,need,O
5808,84,to,O
5809,84,improve,O
5810,84,is,O
5811,84,the,O
5812,84,toilet,O
5813,84,appliance,O
5814,84,.,O
5815,84,The,O
5816,84,shower,O
5817,84,handle,O
5818,84,is,O
5819,84,leaking,O
5820,84,so,O
5821,84,the,O
5822,84,water,O
5823,84,is,O
5824,84,so,O
5825,84,small,O
5826,84,for,O
5827,84,bath,O
5828,84,.,O
5829,84,And,O
5830,84,it,O
5831,84,needs,O
5832,84,to,O
5833,84,climb,O
5834,84,one,O
5835,84,stairs,O
5836,84,up,O
5837,84,to,O
5838,84,level,O
5839,84,29,O
5840,84,.,O
5841,84,The,O
5842,84,rest,O
5843,84,is,O
5844,84,good,O
5845,85,Alex,B-per
5846,85,s,O
5847,85,place,O
5848,85,is,O
5849,85,a,O
5850,85,small,O
5851,85,apartment,O
5852,85,located,O
5853,85,near,O
5854,85,Clarke,B-geo
5855,85,Quay,I-geo
5856,85,and,O
5857,85,one,O
5858,85,stop,O
5859,85,away,O
5860,85,from,O
5861,85,Chinatown,B-gpe
5862,85,via,O
5863,85,MRT,O
5864,85,.,O
5865,85,The,O
5866,85,apartment,O
5867,85,was,O
5868,85,very,O
5869,85,convenient,O
5870,85,when,O
5871,85,travelling,O
5872,85,around,O
5873,85,Singapore,B-geo
5874,85,whilst,O
5875,85,also,O
5876,85,being,O
5877,85,very,O
5878,85,clean,O
5879,85,.,O
5880,85,Lia,O
5881,85,the,O
5882,85,house,O
5883,85,keeper,O
5884,85,was,O
5885,85,excellent,O
5886,85,and,O
5887,85,made,O
5888,85,herself,O
5889,85,readily,O
5890,85,available,O
5891,85,for,O
5892,85,when,O
5893,85,we,O
5894,85,needed,O
5895,85,her,O
5896,85,.,O
5897,85,The,O
5898,85,facilities,O
5899,85,in,O
5900,85,the,O
5901,85,kitchen,O
5902,85,are,O
5903,85,minimal,O
5904,85,whilst,O
5905,85,the,O
5906,85,bathroom,O
5907,85,had,O
5908,85,no,O
5909,85,amenities,O
5910,85,",",O
5911,85,so,O
5912,85,make,O
5913,85,sure,O
5914,85,to,O
5915,85,pack,O
5916,85,your,O
5917,85,own,O
5918,85,Overall,O
5919,85,we,O
5920,85,had,O
5921,85,a,O
5922,85,very,O
5923,85,pleasant,O
5924,85,experience,O
5925,85,and,O
5926,85,would,O
5927,85,recommend,O
5928,85,this,O
5929,85,apartment,O
5930,85,to,O
5931,85,anyone,O
5932,85,.,O
5933,86,This,O
5934,86,property,O
5935,86,is,O
5936,86,so,O
5937,86,centrally,O
5938,86,located,O
5939,86,to,O
5940,86,so,O
5941,86,many,O
5942,86,things,O
5943,86,from,O
5944,86,Sentosa,B-geo
5945,86,",",O
5946,86,China,B-gpe
5947,86,Town,I-gpe
5948,86,",",O
5949,86,and,O
5950,86,Bugis,B-geo
5951,86,Street,I-geo
5952,86,.,O
5953,86,A,O
5954,86,taxi,O
5955,86,can,O
5956,86,easily,O
5957,86,be,O
5958,86,hailed,O
5959,86,from,O
5960,86,right,O
5961,86,outside,O
5962,86,the,O
5963,86,residence,O
5964,86,.,O
5965,86,The,O
5966,86,apartment,O
5967,86,was,O
5968,86,well,O
5969,86,furnished,O
5970,86,",",O
5971,86,very,O
5972,86,clean,O
5973,86,and,O
5974,86,amenities,O
5975,86,adequately,O
5976,86,provided,O
5977,86,.,O
5978,86,Only,O
5979,86,note,O
5980,86,to,O
5981,86,add,O
5982,86,is,O
5983,86,that,O
5984,86,Club,B-geo
5985,86,St,I-geo
5986,86,is,O
5987,86,quite,O
5988,86,the,O
5989,86,party,O
5990,86,venue,O
5991,86,every,O
5992,86,evening,O
5993,86,",",O
5994,86,and,O
5995,86,into,O
5996,86,the,O
5997,86,early,O
5998,86,morning,O
5999,86,.,O
6000,86,We,O
6001,86,could,O
6002,86,hear,O
6003,86,noises,O
6004,86,but,O
6005,86,used,O
6006,86,the,O
6007,86,fan,O
6008,86,that,O
6009,86,was,O
6010,86,provided,O
6011,86,to,O
6012,86,drown,O
6013,86,out,O
6014,86,most,O
6015,86,of,O
6016,86,the,O
6017,86,noise,O
6018,86,.,O
6019,86,Overall,O
6020,86,the,O
6021,86,property,O
6022,86,was,O
6023,86,perfect,O
6024,86,.,O
6025,87,It,O
6026,87,is,O
6027,87,a,O
6028,87,small,O
6029,87,but,O
6030,87,cozy,O
6031,87,apartment,O
6032,87,with,O
6033,87,very,O
6034,87,good,O
6035,87,location,O
6036,87,",",O
6037,87,close,O
6038,87,to,O
6039,87,Orchard,B-geo
6040,87,Rd,I-geo
6041,87,and,O
6042,87,Little,B-gpe
6043,87,India,I-gpe
6044,87,.,O
6045,87,The,O
6046,87,host,O
6047,87,is,O
6048,87,very,O
6049,87,nice,O
6050,87,to,O
6051,87,answer,O
6052,87,all,O
6053,87,my,O
6054,87,questions,O
6055,87,almost,O
6056,87,and,O
6057,87,allowed,O
6058,87,us,O
6059,87,to,O
6060,87,check,O
6061,87,in,O
6062,87,early,O
6063,87,checkout,O
6064,87,late,O
6065,87,.,O
6066,87,It,O
6067,87,was,O
6068,87,a,O
6069,87,very,O
6070,87,pleasant,O
6071,87,stay,O
6072,87,.,O
6073,88,Great,O
6074,88,place,O
6075,88,.,O
6076,88,A,O
6077,88,few,O
6078,88,minutes,O
6079,88,walk,O
6080,88,to,O
6081,88,main,O
6082,88,malls,O
6083,88,on,O
6084,88,Orchard,B-geo
6085,88,road,I-geo
6086,88,.,O
6087,88,Had,O
6088,88,a,O
6089,88,slight,O
6090,88,problem,O
6091,88,but,O
6092,88,they,O
6093,88,were,O
6094,88,quick,O
6095,88,to,O
6096,88,help,O
6097,88,and,O
6098,88,fixed,O
6099,88,it,O
6100,88,Asap,O
6101,88,.,O
6102,89,Luxury,O
6103,89,apartments,O
6104,89,in,O
6105,89,a,O
6106,89,very,O
6107,89,good,O
6108,89,location,O
6109,89,",",O
6110,89,excellent,O
6111,89,tennis,O
6112,89,courts,O
6113,89,",",O
6114,89,including,O
6115,89,swimming,O
6116,89,pool,O
6117,89,gym,O
6118,89,tennis,O
6119,89,courts,O
6120,89,.,O
6121,89,Walking,O
6122,89,by,O
6123,89,Marina,B-org
6124,89,Bay,I-org
6125,89,Center,I-org
6126,89,and,O
6127,89,Chinatown,B-gpe
6128,89,It,O
6129,89,is,O
6130,89,a,O
6131,89,great,O
6132,89,location,O
6133,90,Thank,O
6134,90,you,O
6135,90,Kay,B-per
6136,90,for,O
6137,90,being,O
6138,90,so,O
6139,90,responsive,O
6140,90,The,O
6141,90,stay,O
6142,90,was,O
6143,90,much,O
6144,90,better,O
6145,90,than,O
6146,90,I,O
6147,90,expected,O
6148,90,.,O
6149,90,The,O
6150,90,best,O
6151,90,apartment,O
6152,90,I,O
6153,90,lived,O
6154,90,so,O
6155,90,far,O
6156,90,in,O
6157,90,Singapore,B-geo
6158,90,",",O
6159,90,with,O
6160,90,all,O
6161,90,the,O
6162,90,facilities,O
6163,90,provided,O
6164,90,by,O
6165,90,the,O
6166,90,managements,O
6167,90,and,O
6168,90,a,O
6169,90,very,O
6170,90,accomodating,O
6171,90,place,O
6172,90,in,O
6173,90,the,O
6174,90,centre,O
6175,90,of,O
6176,90,Orchard,B-geo
6177,90,shopping,O
6178,90,districts,O
6179,90,.,O
6180,90,The,O
6181,90,place,O
6182,90,was,O
6183,90,just,O
6184,90,a,O
6185,90,walk,O
6186,90,away,O
6187,90,from,O
6188,90,Wisma,B-org
6189,90,Atria,I-org
6190,90,",",O
6191,90,ION,B-org
6192,90,Orchard,I-org
6193,90,and,O
6194,90,Takashimaya,B-org
6195,90,",",O
6196,90,it,O
6197,90,was,O
6198,90,very,O
6199,90,convenient,O
6200,90,Really,O
6201,90,recommended,O
6202,90,Definitely,O
6203,90,will,O
6204,90,book,O
6205,90,here,O
6206,90,again,O
6207,90,for,O
6208,90,my,O
6209,90,next,O
6210,90,visit,O
6211,90,to,O
6212,90,Singapore,B-geo
6213,91,Jay,B-per
6214,91,is,O
6215,91,place,O
6216,91,was,O
6217,91,great,O
6218,91,",",O
6219,91,especially,O
6220,91,for,O
6221,91,a,O
6222,91,longer,O
6223,91,stay,O
6224,91,.,O
6225,91,The,O
6226,91,location,O
6227,91,is,O
6228,91,absolutely,O
6229,91,perfect,O
6230,91,",",O
6231,91,close,O
6232,91,to,O
6233,91,MRT,O
6234,91,5,O
6235,91,walk,O
6236,91,",",O
6237,91,less,O
6238,91,than,O
6239,91,10,O
6240,91,walk,O
6241,91,to,O
6242,91,Chinatown,B-gpe
6243,91,main,O
6244,91,area,O
6245,91,as,O
6246,91,well,O
6247,91,as,O
6248,91,Tanjong,B-geo
6249,91,Pagar,I-geo
6250,91,main,O
6251,91,road,O
6252,91,with,O
6253,91,lots,O
6254,91,of,O
6255,91,restaurants,O
6256,91,bars,O
6257,91,.,O
6258,91,The,O
6259,91,apartment,O
6260,91,was,O
6261,91,spacious,O
6262,91,with,O
6263,91,amenities,O
6264,91,useful,O
6265,91,for,O
6266,91,a,O
6267,91,longer,O
6268,91,stay,O
6269,91,like,O
6270,91,a,O
6271,91,washing,O
6272,91,machine,O
6273,91,",",O
6274,91,big,O
6275,91,wardrobe,O
6276,91,",",O
6277,91,pool,O
6278,91,",",O
6279,91,kitchen,O
6280,91,.,O
6281,91,Check,O
6282,91,in,O
6283,91,check,O
6284,91,out,O
6285,91,process,O
6286,91,was,O
6287,91,easy,O
6288,91,and,O
6289,91,accommodating,O
6290,91,for,O
6291,91,our,O
6292,91,late,O
6293,91,arrival,O
6294,91,.,O
6295,91,I,O
6296,91,would,O
6297,91,definitely,O
6298,91,pick,O
6299,91,this,O
6300,91,over,O
6301,91,a,O
6302,91,tiny,O
6303,91,hotel,O
6304,91,room,O
6305,91,any,O
6306,91,day,O
6307,91,.,O
6308,92,Best,O
6309,92,part,O
6310,92,of,O
6311,92,my,O
6312,92,stay,O
6313,92,was,O
6314,92,the,O
6315,92,location,O
6316,92,as,O
6317,92,it,O
6318,92,is,O
6319,92,right,O
6320,92,next,O
6321,92,to,O
6322,92,downtown,O
6323,92,and,O
6324,92,very,O
6325,92,close,O
6326,92,to,O
6327,92,Chinatown,B-gpe
6328,92,and,O
6329,92,MRT,O
6330,92,.,O
6331,92,All,O
6332,92,the,O
6333,92,amenities,O
6334,92,like,O
6335,92,kitchen,O
6336,92,",",O
6337,92,hair,O
6338,92,dryer,O
6339,92,",",O
6340,92,TV,O
6341,92,etc,O
6342,92,are,O
6343,92,provided,O
6344,92,.,O
6345,92,They,O
6346,92,also,O
6347,92,provide,O
6348,92,a,O
6349,92,mobile,O
6350,92,with,O
6351,92,local,O
6352,92,number,O
6353,92,which,O
6354,92,is,O
6355,92,a,O
6356,92,very,O
6357,92,nice,O
6358,92,gesture,O
6359,92,.,O
6360,92,Hosts,O
6361,92,were,O
6362,92,very,O
6363,92,courteous,O
6364,92,and,O
6365,92,responsive,O
6366,92,.,O
6367,92,The,O
6368,92,room,O
6369,92,was,O
6370,92,a,O
6371,92,bit,O
6372,92,small,O
6373,92,compact,O
6374,92,as,O
6375,92,to,O
6376,92,my,O
6377,92,initial,O
6378,92,expectation,O
6379,92,and,O
6380,92,ventilation,O
6381,92,was,O
6382,92,a,O
6383,92,bit,O
6384,92,of,O
6385,92,problem,O
6386,92,as,O
6387,92,we,O
6388,92,cooked,O
6389,92,food,O
6390,92,inside,O
6391,92,room,O
6392,92,.,O
6393,93,It,O
6394,93,is,O
6395,93,my,O
6396,93,second,O
6397,93,time,O
6398,93,staying,O
6399,93,in,O
6400,93,this,O
6401,93,room,O
6402,93,It,O
6403,93,is,O
6404,93,right,O
6405,93,in,O
6406,93,Chinatown,B-gpe
6407,93,and,O
6408,93,Elle,B-per
6409,93,is,O
6410,93,super,O
6411,93,friendly,O
6412,93,and,O
6413,93,welcoming,O
6414,93,Will,O
6415,93,always,O
6416,93,stay,O
6417,93,here,O
6418,93,if,O
6419,93,I,O
6420,93,come,O
6421,93,to,O
6422,93,Singapore,B-geo
6423,94,Very,O
6424,94,convenient,O
6425,94,location,O
6426,94,",",O
6427,94,accessible,O
6428,94,from,O
6429,94,Bugis,B-geo
6430,94,MRT,O
6431,94,.,O
6432,94,Good,O
6433,94,food,O
6434,94,places,O
6435,94,within,O
6436,94,walking,O
6437,94,distance,O
6438,94,",",O
6439,94,and,O
6440,94,close,O
6441,94,to,O
6442,94,major,O
6443,94,attractions,O
6444,94,.,O
6445,95,The,O
6446,95,place,O
6447,95,is,O
6448,95,even,O
6449,95,better,O
6450,95,in,O
6451,95,real,O
6452,95,life,O
6453,95,.,O
6454,95,Everything,O
6455,95,is,O
6456,95,perfect,O
6457,95,.,O
6458,95,The,O
6459,95,host,O
6460,95,is,O
6461,95,also,O
6462,95,very,O
6463,95,quick,O
6464,95,to,O
6465,95,respond,O
6466,95,as,O
6467,95,well,O
6468,95,as,O
6469,95,Bobby,B-per
6470,95,who,O
6471,95,took,O
6472,95,care,O
6473,95,of,O
6474,95,us,O
6475,95,during,O
6476,95,our,O
6477,95,stay,O
6478,95,.,O
6479,95,Request,O
6480,95,for,O
6481,95,additional,O
6482,95,pillows,O
6483,95,was,O
6484,95,granted,O
6485,95,without,O
6486,95,hesitation,O
6487,95,.,O
6488,95,My,O
6489,95,wife,O
6490,95,who,O
6491,95,is,O
6492,95,very,O
6493,95,picky,O
6494,95,with,O
6495,95,the,O
6496,95,places,O
6497,95,we,O
6498,95,rent,O
6499,95,out,O
6500,95,is,O
6501,95,very,O
6502,95,impressed,O
6503,95,.,O
6504,95,Location,O
6505,95,is,O
6506,95,also,O
6507,95,superb,O
6508,95,as,O
6509,95,it,O
6510,95,is,O
6511,95,next,O
6512,95,to,O
6513,95,a,O
6514,95,Hawkers,O
6515,95,center,O
6516,95,about,O
6517,95,3,B-tim
6518,95,minute,I-tim
6519,95,walk,O
6520,95,and,O
6521,95,is,O
6522,95,near,O
6523,95,to,O
6524,95,Orchard,B-geo
6525,95,Road,I-geo
6526,95,and,O
6527,95,Marina,B-geo
6528,95,Bay,I-geo
6529,95,.,O
6530,95,Highly,O
6531,95,recommended,O
6532,95,and,O
6533,95,well,O
6534,95,surely,O
6535,95,book,O
6536,95,this,O
6537,95,again,O
6538,95,in,O
6539,95,the,O
6540,95,future,O
6541,95,.,O
6542,95,Thanks,O
6543,95,Simon,B-per
6544,95,and,O
6545,95,Bobby,B-per
6546,96,Wink,O
6547,96,hostel,O
6548,96,is,O
6549,96,really,O
6550,96,great,O
6551,96,located,O
6552,96,only,O
6553,96,5mins,O
6554,96,walk,O
6555,96,to,O
6556,96,Chinatown,B-gpe
6557,96,MRT,O
6558,96,",",O
6559,96,easy,O
6560,96,to,O
6561,96,go,O
6562,96,to,O
6563,96,any,O
6564,96,place,O
6565,96,in,O
6566,96,Singapore,B-geo
6567,96,.,O
6568,96,Talking,O
6569,96,about,O
6570,96,safety,O
6571,96,",",O
6572,96,every,O
6573,96,room,O
6574,96,have,O
6575,96,a,O
6576,96,key,O
6577,96,card,O
